QuestDescription	Dear ranger <Ranger>, the government of <FromPlanet> has authorized me to make you an offer. An annual, open, super-high-speed foncer race championship will soon be held on planet <ToPlanet> in the <ToStar> star system. Our planet won the honor of taking part in the final race, but, unfortunately, the spaceship that was taking our racer to the competition was attacked by pirates, and so far we have no information about him. You are our last hope! We all know that you are one of the best pilots, so we believe you can handle a foncer too. You must arrive on <ToPlanet> by <Date>, or they will declare us losers. If you win the race, you will get a substantial material award in the amount of <Money> cr. Our resident representative will be waiting for you on planet <ToPlanet>. He will provide you with the details. Will you help us?
QuestSuccessGovMessage	On behalf of <FromPlanet> I express our deepest gratitude to you for your help and hand you the award in the amount of <Money> cr! Your triumphant victory in the foncer races proved that a space ranger is capable of everything. The Dominators don't stand a chance!!!
Par1-1	== Your foncer ==
Par2-1	The cheapest engine
Par2-2	Very bad engine
Par2-3	Bad engine
Par2-4	Average engine
Par2-5	Good engine
Par2-6	Excellent engine
Par2-7	Super engine!!!
Par3-1	Protection: <>
Par3-crit	The cursor of the forcefield generator indicator almost pointed to zero and entered the red area. "But it means death" - you thought desperately, trying to back off, but it was too late and the foncer crashed against the next obstacle. There was a small explosion on the track and the great ranger's life came to a close.
Par4-1	Terrible maneuverability
Par4-2	Very bad maneuverability
Par4-3	Bad maneuverability
Par4-4	Normal maneuverability
Par4-5	Good maneuverability
Par4-6	Excellent maneuverability
Par5-1	== Racers' time ==
Par6-1	Your time: {[p6] div 600} min {([p6] mod 600)div10},{([p6] mod 600)mod10} sec
Par8-1	Rasgush's time: {[p7] div 600} min {([p7] mod 600)div10},{([p7] mod 600)mod10} sec
Par8-2	Gonzar's time: {[p7] div 600} min {([p7] mod 600)div10},{([p7] mod 600)mod10} sec
Par8-3	Miatra's time: {[p7] div 600} min {([p7] mod 600)div10},{([p7] mod 600)mod10} sec
Par9-1	Korchenitsa's time: {[p7] div 600} min {([p7] mod 600)div10},{([p7] mod 600)mod10} sec
Par9-2	Shulman's time: {[p7] div 600} min {([p7] mod 600)div10},{([p7] mod 600)mod10} sec
Par10-1	You're in the lead!
Par10-2	Head to head
Par10-3	You're behind...
Par11-1	Flows left: {10-[p16]}
Par12-1	Competitor's engine: <>
Par13-1	Competitor's shield: <>
Par14-1	Competitor's maneuverability: <>
Par15-1	== Track information ==
Par16-1	Stages over: <>
Par17-1	Stages left: <>
Par18-1	== Section information ==
Par19-1	Short
Par19-2	Middle
Par19-3	Long
Par20-1	Minimal damages
Par20-2	Small damages
Par20-3	Middle damages
Par20-4	Big damages
Par20-5	Huge damages
Par21-1	Maneuverability: Minimal
Par21-2	Maneuverability: Low
Par21-3	Maneuverability: Average
Par21-4	Maneuverability: High
Par21-5	Maneuverability: Huge
Par22-1	The first day: {[p22] div 60} h {[p22] mod 60} min
Par22-2	The second day: {([p22]-1440) div 60} h {([p22]-1440) mod 60} min
Par22-3	The third day: {([p22]-2880) div 60} h {([p22]-2880) mod 60} min
Par22-4	The fourth day: {([p22]-4320) div 60} h {([p22]-4320) mod 60} min
Par22-5	The fifth day: {([p22]-5760) div 60} h {([p22]-5760) mod 60} min
Par22-6	The sixth day: {([p22]-7200) div 60} h {([p22]-7200) mod 60} min
Par22-7	The seventh day: {([p22]-8640) div 60} h {([p22]-8640) mod 60} min
Par22-8	The eighth day: {([p22]-10080) div 60} h {([p22]-10080) mod 60} min
Par22-9	The ninth day: {([p22]-11520) div 60} h {([p22]-11520) mod 60} min
Par22-10	The tenth day: {([p22]-12960) div 60} h {([p22]-12960) mod 60} min
Par23-1	Parameter number 17: <>
Par24-1	You're deadly tired
Par24-2	You're tired very much
Par24-3	You're tired
Par24-4	You're alright
Par24-crit	You were not able to overcome your weariness and met your doom!
Par25-1	Section time: <>
Par26-1	Experience: <>
Par27-1	Area type: <>
Par28-1	Your cash: <>
Par29-1	Maneuver: <>
Loc1-1	There are mechanics waiting in the boxes already. One of them must be the chief, he welcomes you and then recites a speech he obviously has memorized:
*	
*	- We have four basic foncer models to offer you.
*	
*	<clr>"Hurricane"<clrEnd> is the fastest foncer with excellent maneuverability. Its protection is minimal. 
*	<clr>"Tornado"<clrEnd> is the foncer with the highest maneuverability and possesses wonderful speed qualities. Its protection is minimal.
*	<clr>"Vortex"<clrEnd> is the best protected foncer but its maneuverability and speed leave much to be desired. 
*	<clr>"Breeze"<clrEnd> is the most prevailing foncer model. All its parameters are average.
*	
*	Also you have the possibility to configure your <clr>personal model <clrEnd>.
Loc1-2	The chief mechanic congratulates you asking:
*	- What will you drive in the semi-final race?
*	
*	<clr>"Hurricane"<clrEnd> is the fastest foncer with excellent maneuverability. Its protection is minimal. This foncer is for a real ace.
*	<clr>"Tornado"<clrEnd> is the foncer with the highest maneuverability and possesses wonderful speed qualities. Its protection is minimal. Only aces can manage it.
*	<clr>"Vortex"<clrEnd> is the best protected foncer but its maneuverability and speed leave much to be desired. This foncer is for an experienced racer.
*	<clr>"Breeze"<clrEnd> is the most prevailing foncer model. All its parameters are average. This foncer is for a novice.
*	
*	Or do you prefer to configure your <clr>personal model<clrEnd>?
Loc1-3	The chief mechanic congratulates you asking:
*	- What will you drive in the final race?
*	
*	<clr>"Hurricane"<clrEnd> is the fastest foncer with excellent maneuverability. Its protection is minimal. This foncer is for a real ace.
*	<clr>"Tornado"<clrEnd> is the foncer with the highest maneuverability and possesses wonderful speed qualities. Its protection is minimal. Only aces can manage it.
*	<clr>"Vortex"<clrEnd> is the best protected foncer but its maneuverability and speed leave much to be desired. This foncer is for an experienced racer.
*	<clr>"Breeze"<clrEnd> is the most prevailing foncer model. All its parameters are average. This foncer is for a novice.
*	
*	Or do you prefer to configure your <clr>personal model<clrEnd>?
Loc6-1	You see only a small straight track section in front of you. After it there is stage 1 but it can't be seen because of the light mist.
*	
*	A metallic voice starts counting:
*	- THREE... TWO... ONE... GO!!!
Loc7-1	<clr>Horizontal section of the track.<clrEnd> The racers are almost flying over the grass like over a green sea. Artificial obstacles are comparatively rare. Usually they are gates and poles.
Loc7-2	<clr>Canyon.<clrEnd> This is a gray corridor with stone walls. Precipitous cliffs on both sides are flitting with horrible speed.
Loc7-3	<clr>Stone plateau<clrEnd> Red tints of boulders remind you of blood. Sharp edged rocks seem to grow up right on the racers' way. Any collision will be mortal.
Loc9-1	Finish!!!
*	Your time: {[p6] div 600} min {([p6] mod 600)div10},{([p6] mod 600)mod10} sec
*	Your competitor's time: {[p7] div 600} min {([p7] mod 600)div10},{([p7] mod 600)mod10} sec
*	
*	You <clr>won<clrEnd> the race!!!
Loc9-2	Finish!!!
*	Your time: {[p6] div 600} min {([p6] mod 600)div10},{([p6] mod 600)mod10} sec
*	Your competitor's time: {[p7] div 600} min {([p7] mod 600)div10},{([p7] mod 600)mod10} sec
*	
*	Damn it! Your competitor seems to have been faster... You <clr>lost<clrEnd> the race.
Loc9-3	Finish!!!
*	Your time: {[p6] div 600} min {([p6] mod 600)div10},{([p6] mod 600)mod10} sec
*	Your competitor's time: {[p7] div 600} min {([p7] mod 600)div10},{([p7] mod 600)mod10} sec
*	
*	Garn! Same timing. Is it really a draw?
Loc9-4	Finish!!!
*	Your time: {[p6] div 600} min {([p6] mod 600)div10},{([p6] mod 600)mod10} sec
*	<clr>Your competitor has dropped out of the race.<clrEnd>
*	
*	You <clr>won<clrEnd> the race!!!
Loc10-1	The last segment of the track is finished and there is only the final straight lying in front of you.
Loc15-1	You showed no talent in the race and lost! You couldn't even pass  <clr>the qualifying round<clrEnd>.
*	
*	All you can do now is go back to your spaceship and leave <ToPlanet>.
Loc15-2	You didn't win glory and lost! You couldn't even win <clr>the semi-final race<clrEnd>.
*	
*	All you can do now is get back to your spaceship and fly away from <ToPlanet>.
Loc15-3	You did your best to win but failed! You lost only <clr>the final race<clrEnd>!
*	
*	All you can do now is get back to your spaceship and fly away from <ToPlanet>. Not all people are equally talented to become champions.
Loc16-1	Slyboots doesn't even try to hide his exultation. You won, <clr>you are the CHAMPION <clrEnd>!!!
*	
*	The crowd of fans quickly surrounded you, cheering your name. Then, the awards ceremony was held, followed by a banquet, and you were offered the luxury of a night in the best hotel on the planet. The night passed without incident, and you returned to the spaceport the next morning.
Loc18-1	Slyboots approached your foncer.
*	- Very bad, tied in the qualification test! What do you expect competing with more experienced racers?
*	Though it could have been worse. A tie is not a loss. Recollect your strength, <Ranger>! We trust in you. They will announce restart. Go to the boxes.
Loc18-2	Slyboots approached your foncer.
*	- Bad, tied in the semi-final race! What do you expect competing with a champion? Alright, we still have a chance, a tie is not a loss. Recollect your strength, <Ranger>! We trust in you. They will announce restart. Go to the boxes.
Loc18-3	Slyboots approached your foncer.
*	- Not bad, tied in the final race! Though it could have been better. A tie is not a win. Recollect your strength, <Ranger>! We trust in you. They will announce restart. Go to the boxes.
Loc19-1	You landed softly and left your spaceship quickly. Nearby you saw a huge holographic screen with changing shots of small machine races and welcoming words to all championship participants in all languages of the Galaxy. 
*	
*	You had hardly admired the nice pictures, some of which were rather alarming, by the way (small explosions with fragments flying in different directions, for example), when you noticed the Welcomer. He approached you and said:
*	
*	- Hello, <Ranger>! I'm the <FromPlanet>'s representative. I'm happy that you've come just in time, the race will start soon, and we should participate in the draw and then go the boxes to choose a foncer for you. Though, if you have any questions, I'll be glad to answer them. I'm Slyboots. I guess you realize that this is not my name, but a nickname. However, I'm used to it, so please call me by my nickname.
Loc19-2	- The track is divided into <clr>11 segments<clrEnd> of different complexity and length. You can pass each section using different tactics. Pay special attention to the segment length: the time it takes to pass it in different ways depends on it. That is, on a short segment you can win or lose much faster than on a long one. Each racer will be driving along their own track line, so there's no chance of any collisions with one another. Concentrating on avoiding obstacles is all that is necessary. To prevent disputes between racers, both lines are completely identical to each other.
Loc19-3	- Actually, a foncer is a small mountable vehicle with a powerful engine. Apart from the engine itself, it also has a forcefield generator, a feeble anti-gravity turbine and manoeuvring controls. The anti-gravity turbine gives enough power for the pilot to hover 3-5 meters above ground, so actually the pilots are competing in air-racing, not just motor-racing. The speed during the race can become as high as 1000 km/h. Since a living being's reflexes aren't quick enough to drive a foncer without hitting obstacles, it is equipped with <clr>the forcefield generator <clrEnd>. Any collision causes damage to the field. It is impossible to completely avoid collisions, even on the simplest track segments. If the cursor of the protection meter falls to zero, the foncer will simply destruct, along with the racer. So, if you are not sure of yourself, you ought to withdraw from the race.
Loc19-4	- The final part of the tournament consists of three stages. Namely: 
*	
*	<clr>First stage<clrEnd> - Qualification race. At this stage you may compete with an inexperienced racer.
*	<clr>Second stage<clrEnd> - Semi-final race. No more inexperienced competitors here. The winner will take part in the final race.
*	<clr>Third stage<clrEnd> - The final race. Its winner becomes the champion for the next four years. Your competitor will be very strong, and may be the champion himself.
*	By the way, now it is Mikhael Shulman.
*	
*	To win you must <clr>be the first to finish all three races<clrEnd>.
Loc23-1	You are in the machine shop; the chief mechanic needs the directions on power distribution and is giving necessary explanations:
*	
*	- The main generator's power can be divided into <clr>9<clrEnd> flows, and each flow can supply <clr>the engine<clrEnd>, <clr>the forcefield generator <clrEnd> or <clr>the manoeuvring controls<clrEnd>. No more than <clr>5<clrEnd> flows can supply each item.
Loc32-1	Slyboots approached your foncer:
*	
*	- Excellent! We were right trusting in you. If you want to stay in the current foncer model, it won't take long for our mechanics to get it ready for the next race. Or do you prefer to change the model? Then next race will start in an hour.
Loc33-1	The decor of the hall where the draw was to be held was imposing. A huge exposition was placed along the perimeter and around the seats. Old-fashioned models of foncers and past champions' hologram portraits were exhibited there along with wreckages and holograms framed in mourning. They reminded you how dangerous the sport was.
*	
*	All the seats in the hall were occupied by the racers, their representatives and guests of honor. At first the colorful opening ceremony was held, after which they made speeches quite uninteresting for you, and then finally, the organizers started the draw.
*	
*	You managed to pick out the following important information from what you heard. All together there are <clr>6<clrEnd> best sportsmen who have reached this final part of the tournament. Four of them are to race in the first stage, known traditionally as the Qualifiers. Two winners will then compete with the previously defined leaders in the Semi-final race, which is the second stage. Consequently, the Semi-final winners will take part in the Final race, which will define the champion.
*	
*	The arbiter calls you out to the stage together with the other three racers who will participate in the Qualifiers. They are Peleng Rasgush, Maloq Gonzar, and Faeyan Miatra.
Loc33-2	Peleng Rasgush answers your greeting and those sitting in the hall are applauding to this display of his respect.
*	In all appearances, this racer prefers <clr>speed and maneuverability <clrEnd> and loves <clr>taking risks<clrEnd> like all Pelengs.
*	
*	You are standing on the stage together with the other three racers, and there is a basket with the draw balls in front of you.
Loc33-3	Maloq Gonzar is roaring some dark things and a slight murmur runs through the ranks. The thing is that all the sportsmen respect competitions and their atmosphere. Legends say that some planets used to have the traditions of intermitting wars during sports festivals. So now they don't approve of Gonzar's behavior.
*	"This Maloq hardly pays much attention to his foncer's speed or maneuverability", - you thought. - But he surely has the maximum <clr>protection<clrEnd>!"
*	
*	You are standing on the stage together with the other three racers, and there is a basket with the pin palling lots in it.
Loc33-4	Faeyan Miatra answered your greetings with delicate kindness but his words were so grandiloquent, that there were only a few individuals in the hall who were able to enjoy all the style. Moreover, some attendants could hear veiled irony in his answer. Either way, an awkward silence settled in the hall for a short period of time.
*	Perhaps, this cunning Faeyan will consider <clr>maneuverability<clrEnd> to be the keystone of his victory in the race.
*	
*	You are standing on the stage together with the other three racers, and there is a basket with the pin palling lots in it.
Loc39-1	You take a lot out of the basket, so do the other racers. In the issue, you are going to compete with <clr>Peleng Rasgush <clrEnd>.
*	
*	Now you know your first competitor and according to the competition order, right now you need to choose your possible competitor for the second stage. It will be one of two earthlings: either: <clr>Vladimir Korchenitsa <clrEnd>, who is equally fast and maneuverable, or the current champion, <clr>Mikhael Shulman <clrEnd>, famous for his unusual <clr>speed<clrEnd>.
Loc39-2	You take a lot out of the basket, so do the other racers. In the issue, you are going to compete with <clr>the Maloq - Gonzar <clrEnd>.
*	
*	Now you know your first competitor and according to the competition order, right now you need to choose your possible competitor for the second stage. It will be one of two earthlings: either: <clr>Vladimir Korchenitsa <clrEnd>, who is equally fast and maneuverable, or the current champion, <clr>Mikhael Shulman <clrEnd>, famous for his unusual <clr>speed<clrEnd>.
Loc39-3	You take a lot out of the basket, so do the other racers. In the issue, you are going to compete with <clr>Faeyan Miatra <clrEnd>.
*	
*	Now you know your first competitor and according to the competition order, right now you need to choose your possible competitor for the second stage. It will be one of two earthlings: either: <clr>Vladimir Korchenitsa <clrEnd>, who is equally fast and maneuverable, or the current champion, <clr>Mikhael Shulman <clrEnd>, famous for his unusual <clr>speed<clrEnd>.
Path2	Choose "Hurricane"
Path3	Choose "Tornado"
Path4	Choose "Breeze"
Path5	Choose "Vortex"
Path10	Give full throttle
Path11	Give full throttle, sacrificing protection for speed
Path12	Move easily through the dangerous part of the track segment minding protection
Path13	Brake slightly in the most dangerous places but mind the speed
Path15	Pick up the maximum speed on the final straight
Path22	Fall back
Path29	Forget about speed and save your forcefield as much as possible
Path30b	Your competitor has dropped out of the race. Now you just need to finish!
Path31b	Your competitor has dropped out of the race. Now you just need to finish!
Path32b	Your competitor has dropped out of the race. Now you just need to finish!
Path41	Go to draw lots
Path42	Ask to tell you about the race
Path44	Ask to tell you about foncers
Path47	Ask to tell you about the track
Path49	Configure your personal model
Path50	Feed power to the engine
Path51	Feed power to the forcefield generator
Path52	Feed power to the manoeuvring sliders
Path53	Drop power from the engine
Path54	Drop power from the forcefield generator
Path55	Drop power from the manoeuvring sliders
Path56	Stop configuring the foncer
Path67b	You've made your choice. You don the racer's outfit. The foncer is driven to the starting-post. You mount it and start the engine. The generator purrs and your first race will start within a few seconds!
Path68b	You've made your choice. The foncer is driven to the starting-post again. Habitually, you mount it and start the engine without hesitation. The generator purrs, and <clr>the Final race<clrEnd> will start within a few seconds. Your concentration is maximum.
Path69b	You've made your choice. The foncer is driven to the starting-post again. You mount it habitually and start the engine. The generator purrs, and <clr>the Semi-final race<clrEnd> will start within a few seconds.
Path72	Change the foncer model
Path73	Drive the same foncer model during the next race
Path74	Greet the Peleng
Path75	Greet the Maloq
Path76	Greet the Faeyan
Path77	Take out a lot from the basket
Path84	Take one more lot
Path84b	You take one more lot from the basket. Now, if you win the Qualification, you will compete with <clr>the earthling named Vladimir Korchenitsa <clrEnd> in the Semi-final race.
Path85b	You take one more lot from the basket. Now, if you win the Qualification, you will compete with <clr>the earthling named Mikhael Shulman <clrEnd> in the Semi-final race. The current champion, by the way...
Path86	The draw is over, all you need to do now is go the boxes and choose the foncer
Path87b	You've made your choice. You don the racer's outfit. The foncer is driven to the starting-post. You mount it and start the engine. The generator purrs and your first race will start within a few seconds!
Path88b	You've made your choice. You don the racer's outfit. The foncer is driven to the starting-post. You mount it and start the engine. The generator purrs and your first race will start within a few seconds!
Path94b	You've made your choice. You put the racer's outfit. The foncer is driven to the starting-post again. You sit down habitually onto it and run the engine. The generator is purring, <clr>the Final race<clrEnd> will start within few seconds.
Path95b	You've made your choice. You put the racer's outfit. The foncer is driven to the starting-post again. You sit down habitually onto it and automatically run the engine. The generator is purring, <clr>the Semi-final race<clrEnd> will start within few seconds. Your concentration is maximal.
