QuestDescription	<Ranger>, we want to employ you on a mission. On planet <ToPlanet> of the stellar system of <ToStar> there is Rectal Island, which air is very good for Pelengs. Our government decided to establish a resort there. Our experts have already selected a location - the area of Hillside. All you have to do is go to planet <ToPlanet> and sign a 50-year leasing agreement of Hillside with the Ministry of Rectal Island. The assignment may seem easy, but our previous courier had no success due to the island's strange bureaucratic procedures. We could have sent another courier, but now we are in a hurry - we need to have the papers before <Date>. You should understand that every day of delay costs us money. So you better hurry. The award of <Money> cr will await you here.
QuestSuccessGovMessage	Finally! We were already going to terminate the project of building cottages for the members of the government of <FromPlanet>. What? You thought we were going to build a resort? You must have gotten something wrong. By the way, as a favour, we can build you a small house in Hillside for just 3 000 000 cr. No? That's a pity. Hey, the papers say Hillside is leased for 50 years, not for 250! We told you it should be leased for 250 years. You failed the mission, ranger. You should listen carefully to mission briefings. You say you have a recording of the briefing? You really can't be fooled that easily! Here is your <Money> cr. You truly deserved it.
Par1-1	You have nothing on
Par1-2	All you have on are underpants with hearts on them
Par1-3	You have underpants and boots on
Par1-4	You do not carry a ranger badge
Par1-5	You are dressed casually
Par1-crit	After you lost all your clothes, you could not proceed with the important mission. You quickly ran to your starship and left the location. Probably some time, when you are old, you will write a book like "Combat achievements, or how I got naked in public," but this time you just flew away with disgrace from a strange and mysterious Rectal Island.
Par2-2	You have a garrison cap on
Par3-1	You've got <> cr
Par5-1	Other things:
Par7-2	Watch
Par7-3	Watch and glasses
Par8-2	Fishing rod
Par8-3	Fishing rod with a bait
Par9-2	Crowbar
Par11-2	Papers (not stamped)
Par11-3	Papers (not stamped)
Par11-4	Papers (stamped)
Par12-2	Three-eye fish
Par13-1	Hand: {<> mod 100} pt.
Par14-1	Parameter 14: <>
Par15-1	Your bet: 10 cr
Par15-2	Your bet: 25 cr
Par15-3	Your bet: 40 cr
Par15-4	Your bet: 55 cr
Par15-5	Your bet: 70 cr
Par16-1	Parameter 16: <>
Par17-1	Parameter 17: <>
Par22-1	Current win: <> cr
Loc98-1	- So are we playing or not? - the secretary asked rudely while riffling the pack.
Loc98-2	- It's not the right time to explain it completely. Alright. To put it short. Each player takes cards in turns. At first - by two cards. If it's not enough, then take more from the pack, but not more than by five additional cards. The goal is to collect more points than your opponent. One should not collect more than 21. Well, let's just play, - the secretary gabbled.
Loc98-3	You already lost your worn out dirty <clr>boots<clrEnd>. Why would anyone need them except you? But judging from the happy face of your opponent, she needs your boots too.
Loc98-4	You took off the <clr>overalls<clrEnd>, and passed it over to the secretary. It looks like you gradually turn from a space hero into a space bum... Well, you should not gamble, kids.
Loc98-5	Reluctantly you took of the <clr>ranger badge<clrEnd>.
*	
*	- A nice thingy. Shiny, like the housemaster's bald head! - the secretary said.
Loc98-6	You did not enjoy your victory long. After a few sighs you returned <clr>the watch<clrEnd> to the secretary.
Loc98-7	- What do I give you? Alright, here is my <clr>watch<clrEnd>, - mumbled the secretary sadly, took off her watch and handed it over to you.
*	- What time is it? - you asked sarcastically, putting the trophy into your pocket.
*	- Funny, huh? You're going to regret that.
Loc98-8	Here comes your <clr>overall<clrEnd> back. How pleasant it is to return into this synthetic wonder. Ah, I can hardly describe it...
Loc98-9	Here come the <clr>boots<clrEnd> back. Worn out, dirty ones, anyway, they are yours. With pride you took them on your precious feet.
Loc98-10	Hurray! You made it! You won back your pride - the <clr>ranger badge<clrEnd>. Satisfied, you pinned it to your overalls. All galaxy girls are yours again!
Loc103-1	With a serious expression on her face, the secretary took a card from the top of the pack. 
*	Then she took another card from the pack and handed it to you with a grin. Looks like she does not wish you victory. By the way, you don't wish it to her either.
Loc103-2	With a grin, the secretary took a card from the pack and handed it to you. Looks like she does not wish you victory. By the way, you don't wish it to her either.
Loc109-1	- Another one, pilot? Or is that enough? - she said with a blow of smoke into your face.
Loc110-1	- Alright, what have you got? - Rachehanovna said casually. 
*	You opened your cards slowly - you've got [p13]. The tension rose. After looking at your cards, the secretary showed hers, with a discontent expression. She also has [p15]! <clr>Drawn<clrEnd>.
Loc113-1	- Alright, what have you got? - the secretary said seriously. 
*	You slowly turned your cards one by one - you've got [p13]. Overshoot. Then the secretary opened her cards - she also overshot - [p15]! <clr>Drawn<clrEnd>.
Loc117-1	You stand in a hall with pink speckled wallpaper. 
*	
*	To the left the commandant stands, frowning and wagging his finger at you. 
*	In front of you - the corridor.
*	To the right a small staircase goes down. There is a sign above it - "The Registry".
*	To the back - the exit
*	Right below you... Wow, here are your boots. One of the laces is untied, what a shame! But you're too lazy to tie it...
Loc117-2	You stand in a hall with pink speckled wallpaper. 
*	
*	To the left of you the commandant stands. He smiles at you. 
*	In front of you - the corridor.
*	To the right a small staircase goes down. There is a sign above it - "The Registry".
*	To the back - the exit
*	Right below you... Wow, here are your boots. One of the laces is untied, what a shame! But you're too lazy to tie it...
Loc118-1	A gloomy ragged basement. Torn wallpaper hangs from the walls. The floor is scratched, it looks like somebody was moving a lot of heavy furniture. But the most amazing thing was a huge hole in the floor, filled with water. But wait; there is a small door in the opposite wall.
Loc118-2	"Wait, - you said to yourself, - its not over yet. You're only going to have a bruise on the forehead..."
*	
*	A gloomy ragged basement. Torn wallpaper hangs from the walls. The floor is scratched, it looks like somebody was moving a lot of heavy furniture. But the most amazing thing was a huge hole in the floor, filled with water. But wait; there is a small door in the opposite wall.
Loc118-3	You cast the line in the hole with water, but nothing happened. You were going to take out the bait when the fishing line tightened. Out of surprise you pulled hard. And you found you caught a small fish. It was green and had three eyes though, but this fact did not worry you. 
*	The fish was on its side and did not move. Suddenly it started eating the line. You put down the fishing rod and waited what was going to happen next. And it happened - the monster ate the line, the fishing rod, hiccuped quietly and popped off the hooks. You reckoned it was indigestion. After a little while you came up to the fish and took it.
Loc118-4	You cast the line in the hole with water, but nothing happened.
Loc118-5	You carefully hooked the door with a crowbar and finally opened it. There was a lot of dust inside ... and a small envelope. You opened it and found <clr>100 cr<clrEnd> inside (you thought it was blackmail against the housemaster?). Not too much actually (to put it mildly), but it's better than nothing. You took the money and closed the door.
Loc118-6	"Splash", - and the crowbar vanished in deep waters like a cargo ship in hyperspace. Nothing else happened. What could happen anyway?
Loc118-7	You carefully inspected the wallpaper, crumpled it and even tasted a small piece. This looks like ordinary wallpaper - nothing special. You decided against taking a sheet and putting it in your pocket - it is not appropriate for a stout ranger. Also it may stain the overalls.
Loc118-8	You carefully looked into the hole. Something moved there. You assumed the worse - it was Babai! But can it be just ripple on the water? Anyway you should better stay away from the hole.
Loc119-1	You bravely came up to the door and pulled the handle. The door did not open. You pulled harder; the handle came off, slipped from your hand and hit you right in the forehead!
*	"It's all over, - you thought. - My family will receive an insurance of <clr>10000<clrEnd> cr, and the fame of the galaxy liberator will go to other rangers..."
Loc121-1	After you graciously landed, you stepped down on to Rectal Island and into a cowpat. A nice start indeed... Shaking the dirty foot you jumped to the administrative building. It was strangely painted pink. 
*	
*	The walls inside were covered with (again!) pink wallpaper. Even the watchman's booth. That's the watchman you needed. You approached a 9*12 cm window and prepared to speak, but...
*	"What the hell, strictly speaking, you came here for, your highness?" - asked the watchman. 
*	You were so confused that you did not know how to respond. 
*	"Remember this, punk. They call me commandant Ge Chevara here. Or simply commandant. And now - batten down!"
*	Then the window spectacularly shut right before your nose. Hm... Who's going to tell me now how I can agree the lease of Hillside?
Loc122-1	"Commandant, sorry to disturb you, but..." - you began.
*	"How you dare to speak with me, punk? When I fought enemies of the galaxy, you were in pinafores..."
Loc124-1	A clean and tidy corridor, bright with the light from the window in the end. There are doors and doors on both sides. There are plates on every door. 
*	
*	"Housemaster (The Master of the House)"
*	"Secretariat"
*	"Head of the transportation shop"
*	"Brush and Hammer Manager"
*	"WC"
Loc125-1	You stand at a dirty window looking outside. Silly thoughts come to your mind: "Who am I?" "What is my purpose?" Exactly! "Why I was responsible for catching fleas with forceps at school? It was much more exciting to feed fish, but yellow-faced Ga-Notsri always did that! What a tough childhood... Wait, what is that nonsense I'm thinking about" - you called yourself down.
Loc125-2	It's peace and quiet outside. It's so good!
Loc125-3	The window is dirty by the way. Why don't you wash it? There is something written on it: "The housemaster is bounder! What a bounder! He hasn't paid my salary for three months!!!" And another one below: "OK, a bounder, but I have a villa on Venus. And have meal three times a day".
Loc127-1	You stand on a beach of a swamped lake. A warm wind blows into your pink-cheeked face, the rush moves with waves. It's beautiful alright!
Loc127-2	"Splash!" - you have obviously lost your tool forever.
Loc127-3	You cast the line and waited. For nothing. You just made sure that you can't get fish without a bait.
Loc127-4	You cast the line and waited. Fish just won't bite. Looks like there are no fish in the lake.
Loc127-5	You began walking out of the water and a bloodsucker bit you on the hand and you dropped this little monster in the lake. 
*	
*	You stand on a beach of a swamped lake. A warm wind blows into your pink-cheeked face, the rush moves with waves. It's beautiful alright!
Loc127-6	There was no hook with the fishing rod and you just wrapped the bloodsucker with the line. It won't come off this time!
Loc129-1	The secretary is staring at the table. She is obviously not busy and you can ask her about something.
Loc129-2	- As you wish, - the secretary said.
Loc129-3	- Fish? Auh! Disgusting! Fish makes me fat. 
*	Well, it's not fish, but the fact that you eat seven times a day.
Loc129-4	- Thank you. What a kind ranger. Would you like me to kiss you for your kindness? - gabbled Rachehanovna sweetly.
*	- No thanks.
*	- As you wish.
Loc129-5	- What do you mean no? Have you checked the right basement? Go to the lobby and then downstairs, - she said.
*	- I did go down the stairs, the Registry was not there. 
*	- Dear sir, you are beginning to annoy me. I told you that it is in the basement. Should I repeat? 
*	The secretary is obviously unaware that the registry is not there anymore. But you'd better not prove it to her. You'd save some health, as your grandfather said.
Loc129-6	"Rules? Alright, - the secretary replied. - It is played with a 36 card pack. Players are dealt by two cards and then they count points. Counting is easy: six is six points, seven is seven points, and so on until ten, which is ten points. Jack is two points, Queen is three, King is four and Ace is eleven points. 
*	
*	If after the first deal I have 21 points, I automatically win, no matter how many points you have. Sorry mate: my pack - my advantage. But if I do not get 21 points with 2 cards and you do, then you automatically win. Usually, though, neither player gets 21 with two cards, and then each of us can take 1 more card at a time from the pack. By the way, one can take up to five additional cards. Here you go. There is an opportunity to collect 21 points. If a player has more than 21 points - it is called an overshoot. But you can refuse to take an additional card when you think you may collect more than 21 points. 
*	
*	After both of us stop taking cards, the game is over. We show our cards to each other and compare collected points. If the numbers of points are equal, then it is drawn. If anyone has more points and there is no overshoot, that one is the winner. That's it. 
*	
*	In general, the rules are not complicated, but sometimes it's hard to realise them at once. You'll get it when you play."
Loc129-7	"In the lobby, take the stairs down - and you are there", - she replied.
Loc129-8	- Fill out the papers at the Registry and come back here. I will stamp them. Then you will have to go to the housemaster. He will review the application, set quotas, align points and sub-points, - the secretary uttered still staring at the table.
Loc129-9	- Alright. Here are the <clr>glasses<clrEnd>, - the secretary said.
*	- Thanks a lot.
*	- Hey, wait! I can hardly see without them. Give them back at once! 
*	- Yeah, you wish. You lost the game and you had to pay, - you said and for some reason put your tongue out.
*	- Fine. But I'm not going to play with you anymore, you cheater! 
*	Hurt, the secretary put the cards away in the drawer. The game is really cancelled.
Loc131-1	You stand in the middle of a square room, illuminated with a green chandelier. Light flares around the room prevent you from focusing. 
*	A secretary of a considerable size, immense as our galaxy, sits at a table. She is dressed in a weird multicoloured dress imprinted with sunflowers. She has huge glasses with thick lenses. There is a large lit cigar in her mouth. 
*	The mistress of the stamp and coffee-machine pays absolutely no attention to you. After another quick look around, you noticed a small trash can in the corner - a useful thing when one has to throw away something.
Loc131-2	The setting is usual. A chandelier, trash can, secretary at a table. Only <clr>she does not have glasses on<clrEnd>.
Loc132-1	- Dunia Rachehanovna! - uttered the heavyset secretary.
*	- What a beautiful name.
*	- You'd better not say otherwise. I'd crack your skull like a coconut, hohoho - laughed the fat woman falsely.
*	- Oh come on, - you said with some awe of this large woman. - Isn't it rather dull to stay here all days long? 
*	- Dull? Yes, it is dull sometimes. Well, astronautie. Why beating about the bush? Let have some fun, so to say? - the secretary pronounced the last words with a mysterious look in her eyes. 
*	- Err. I think we should not hurry, - you mumbled.
*	- Don't you get embarrassed, pal. It won't take long, just one little game, - the secretary said and put a pack of cards on the table.
*	That was a great weight off your mind.
*	- What do we play?
*	- Let's play 21.
Loc133-1	"Rules? Alright, - the secretary replied. - It is played with a 36 card pack. Players are dealt by two cards and then they count points. Counting is easy: six is six points, seven is seven points, and so on until ten, which is ten points. Jack is two points, Queen is three, King is four and Ace is eleven points. 
*	
*	If after the first deal I have 21 points, I automatically win, no matter how many points you have. Sorry mate: my pack - my advantage. But if I do not get 21 points with 2 cards and you do, then you automatically win. Usually, though, neither player gets 21 with two cards, and then each of us can take 1 more card at a time from the pack. By the way, one can take up to five additional cards. Here you go. There is an opportunity to collect 21 points. If a player has more than 21 points - it is called an overshoot. But you can refuse to take an additional card when you think you may collect more than 21 points. 
*	
*	After both of us stop taking cards, the game is over. We show our cards to each other and compare collected points. If the numbers of points are equal, then it is drawn. If anyone has more points and there is no overshoot, that one is the winner. That's it. 
*	
*	In general, the rules are not complicated, but sometimes it's hard to realise them at once. You'll get it when you play.
*	So, are we playing?"
Loc134-1	- Alright, what have you got? - Rachehanovna said casually. 
*	You opened your cards slowly - you've got [p13]. The secretary smiled and opened hers - she had [p15]. Well. <clr>You've lost <clrEnd>. Maybe you will be lucky next time?
*	
*	- Once you lose - you give something away. I mean your <clr>clothes<clrEnd>. That's the rules, - said Rachehanovna rubbing her hands.
Loc134-2	- Alright, what have you got? - Rachehanovna said casually.
*	You opened your cards slowly - you've got [p13] - overshoot. The secretary smiled and opened hers - she had [p15]. Well. <clr>You've lost <clrEnd>. Maybe you will be lucky next time?
*	
*	- Once you lose - you give something away. I mean your <clr>clothes<clrEnd>. That's the rules, - said Rachehanovna rubbing her hands.
Loc134-3	- You have lost, birdie. I have 21 with two cards! - the secretary exclaimed and showed her cards. 
*	
*	- Once you lose - you give something away. I mean your <clr>clothes<clrEnd>. That's the rules, - said Rachehanovna rubbing her hands.
Loc135-1	"Shouldn't I fry some nails for you instead? Give me the clothes!" - the secretary was in a decisive mood.
*	
*	Looks like you will have to give away your dear clothes. Or not?
Loc136-1	- Fine, give it to me, - she replied.
Loc137-1	She reacted to your careless answer in a flash - the secretary jumped up from her chair, hopped over the table and brought you down on the floor with a powerful uppercut. You have not seen so many stars before, even in the most picturesque locations of the galaxy. You shook your head, stood up and saw the secretary moving in your direction with two legs of a chair in her hands. You panicked and ran outside to your ship. Fortunately, Rachehanovna did not run so well and you had time to reach your starship. After you waved your hand to the card player, you left the location.
Loc139-1	- Come on, what have you got? - the secretary said seriously. 
*	You opened your cards slowly - you've got [p13]. The hurt secretary dropped her cards on the table. She has only [p15]. <clr>You won!<clrEnd>!
*	
*	- Alright, alright. I lost and will give you something. Rules are rules, - the secretary muttered.
Loc139-2	- Come on, what have you got? - the secretary said seriously. 
*	You opened your cards slowly - you've got [p13]. The hurt secretary dropped her cards on the table. She has [p15] - an overshoot. <clr>You won!<clrEnd>!
*	
*	- Alright, alright. I lost and will give you something. Rules are rules, - the secretary muttered.
Loc139-3	- 21 points with two cards! Rangers begin and win! - you cried cheerfully and showed your cards.
*	
*	- Alright, alright. I lost and will give you something. Rules are rules, - the secretary muttered.
Loc141-1	You stand in the middle of a room, full of rubbish. In the centre, a heavyset fellow sat and smiled cunningly. This must be the hammers manager.
Loc141-2	- Do I look like a pen-pusher, huh? I've no crappy stamp. Even if I had it, I would not give it to you, got it?
Loc141-3	- You don't bumble me. The Secretariat deals with papers, damn you.
Loc141-4	- Don't you also want to get inside my pants, dude? - he replied.
Loc141-5	- Why am I supposed to know, huh? We're ain't no info booth here. We paint the crappy paint and drink alky here.
Loc141-6	- What rod? Do I look like a fisherman? I like fish with beer, cool that.
Loc141-7	- Ah. Good crows that, - the fellow said taking the box away.
Loc141-8	- Great crow! Drop by if you need more.
*	- I don't think so, - you replied taking your purchase.
Loc141-9	- Alright, alright, - the fellow began raking about in the box searching for a crowbar (he obviously tried to find the worst one, but it was stupid of him, because all the crowbars were equally rusted). - Now, here you go. Gimme money like. You broke. 
*	You swallowed all his swearing, gave out the money and received the desired purchase.
Loc143-1	- Here, - said the fellow, taking out a dirty box, - great crows, only 50 cr. Take that? 
*	- Anything else?
*	- Nothing else like, got it? 
*	- Sure, bloody got it like, - you answered mockingly.
Loc144-1	You stand in the middle of a WC. It does not look so dirty. Anyway you saw much worse toilets. On the left you see two cubicles. The floor is tiled. Wow you can even see a reflection of yourself in the tiles! You haven't washed your face for a long time... Or is this floor dirty?
Loc144-2	- Taken, - you heard from inside.
Loc144-3	You inspected the toilet inch by inch. No hiding places, no butts, no papers. It's a pity.
Loc144-4	As soon as you went out of the cubicle, the clerk closed the door behind you with a latch.
*	
*	You stand in the middle of a WC. It does not look so dirty. Anyway you saw much worse toilets. On the left you see two cubicles. The floor is tiled. Wow you can even see a reflection of yourself in the tiles! You haven't washed your face for a long time... Or is this floor dirty?
Loc145-1	"The secretary is a damned fool!"
Loc145-2	"Robby + starship = death to pirates".
Loc145-3	"x^4 + Ln(x) + exp(x) = 10. I can't solve it, help me!!!"
Loc145-4	"I feel so bad. July 12, 2987, Ga-Notsri 
*	PS: Kids, don't mix ekup with kinza".
Loc145-5	"Those who haven't been to the crap-house - haven't seen the beauty".
Loc145-6	"Don't flatter yourself - come closer".
Loc145-7	"Let this crap-house be the rampart in our righteous fight for peace!"
Loc145-8	"Robby with the spaceship - we will get ya! The free corsairs"
Loc145-9	"Anton "Ragnar" Mikhailov. Kaliningrad. Russia. 3003"
Loc145-10	You inspected the walls but did not find any new writing. Looks like you'll have to develop your intelligence in some other place.
Loc146-1	You stand in a VERY tiny room. Right in front of you there is a lavatory with a water tank. A chain with a handle hangs to the right. Every wall and the ceiling are covered with writings. With writings in various galaxy languages. You can even discern some inscriptions.
Loc146-2	The lavatory chunked, but soon became silent. You flushed water, that's all. Did you expect a secret passage to open? So silly of you!
Loc146-3	You cast the line into the lavatory. Nothing happened. Only the bait died. You had to untie it.
Loc146-4	For some obscure reason, you cast the line into the lavatory. Probably, out of desperation. You feared than someone may notice you and put away your fishing gear.
Loc146-5	You have finished your sloppy business.
Loc146-6	You failed! Partitions between the cubicles reach the ceiling.
Loc150-1	You hauled off and hit the booth with the crowbar. Nothing happened. There was not even a crack. Only the commandant is beaming. It looks like he is happy with your failure. But it turned out he was happy with completely another thing. He took an old plasmagun from below the table and got out of the booth.
*	- Dear forest brothers! The hunting season is declared open! - shouted the commandant and shooting at you. 
*	Damn, the watchman must be mad! You darted away from the ministry in panic. "Yahoo!" - shouted the commandant and shoots at you, but misses all the time. 
*	After you reached you iron bird, you left the damned Rectal Island.
Loc151-1	Looks like your swearing was not convincing enough for the fellow. 
*	- 20? What the? It's worth 60!
Loc152-1	You tried to open the door, turned the handle but it did not work. You knocked, picked in the keyhole with your nail, and even tromped your feet, all for nothing. "It must be closed" - you thought.
Loc153-1	The commandant looks at you with his wide open surprised eyes. He must be waiting for you to say something.
Loc153-2	- Fish? I tried fishing in the lake nearby, but got nothing. I can give you a fishing rod if you like. Probably you will have more luck.
*	- Sure, - you replied in an instant.
*	The commandant brought a small folding fishing rod from below the table and handed it over to you through the window. A label on the handle said "Instance FisherMann GMbH". But on the rod itself you noticed another label "private entrepreneur Marmyshkine (basement #5)". Interesting...
Loc153-3	- The Registry? - responded the watchman - It used to be in the basement. But the floor crumbled there and they moved to the toilet. Second cubicle. There was no other room for them like. A rather naggy clerk works over there - he locks himself up and never opens the door. Tell him you gotta important government business. I guess he'll open then.
Loc153-4	- Oh come on. Deadly dullness! - the commandant replied. - I remember we hit a truck with guanawa when I was in a guerilla force. We...
*	He set off. Bum Bam. Soldiers here, guerrillas there. Factories to the workers, land to the peasants. You already imagine hot jungle, shooting all around. Mortar fire to the left and to the right. And then - kaboom! You see stars. 
*	What? Where? You found yourself on the floor. A small bump on the back of your head. The first thought is who did this to me? Nobody - you just fell asleep with the commandant's tales, your legs gave away and you fell on the floor. 
*	You quickly brushed up and stood up.
Loc153-5	- I will do anything for the revolution, my forest brother. But I am of no help in this business of yours. I don't have the stamp. But according to intelligence out of nowhere, - the commandant pointed to the ceiling, - the stamp can be at the Secretariat.
Loc153-6	- Regarding all the paper issues go to the Secretariat, bro, - commandant Ge Chevara replied to you.
Loc155-1	- Taken, - you heard a voice from inside.
*	- I am on a very important government assignment!
*	- The first cubicle is also vacant by the way.
*	- Not that assignment. I need to perfect some documents.
*	- Fine. Just a moment.
*	You heard a click and the cubicle door opened. The floor of the cubicle was covered with various papers and reports. A hairy man with a typewriter on his knees sat on the lavatory. The typewriter jumped with every stroke. 
*	
*	- Tell me what exactly you need. I got work to do, - chattered the clerk.
Loc155-3	- I am a minority peoples expert, not a fishing industry expert. So please excuse me.
Loc155-4	- No. I don't have the stamp. I have paper, but no stamp.
Loc155-5	- Do you have anything else? - the clerk asked.
Loc157-1	- No problem. We're going to perfect it perfectly, the clerk said and inserted a new blank. - Here we go, field 1 - Sex.
Loc158-1	- I see. That's what I fill in, - his fingers hit the keys. - Now field 2: nationality.
Loc159-1	- Absolutely clear. Filled in. Fields 3, 4 and 5 are to be filled in by the official. Field 6: for what purposes the land will be used.
Loc160-1	- Alright. Name of company or individual that will be the lessee of the Hillside.
Loc161-1	- Ready, - the clerk said joyfully, taking out the paper from the typewriter and handing it over to you.
*	Now you have the lending papers for Hillside. At least something. All you have to do is stamp them in the Secretariat and go to the housemaster.
Loc162-1	As soon as you entered the room, a thick bass hit your ears:
*	- Is it reserved for you? - asked a man sitting in a luxurious armchair at a carved table. 
*	- Of course. I came regarding the lease of Hillside, - you replied.
*	- Ah, certainly. Please come in. Have a seat, - the housemaster said, inviting you to sit on a small soft chair. - Let me introduce myself first, my name is Bobchinsky. You can call me Dobchinsky. I am glad that the government of <FromPlanet> is interested in leasing Hillside. But I believe you understand that we can not issue all the required documents to a stranger. Who knows how he may deal with such important document: he may sell it to pirates or use it in a toilet for some mysterious purpose. Thus you will have to take a test of credibility, the results of which will let me decide whether you are trustworthy.
Loc163-1	- I guess we misunderstood each other. Leave the premises and never come back here! Do you hear me - never, NEVER!!! - shouted the housemaster.
*	
*	After you left the room you realised that by arguing with the housemaster you lost the opportunity to obtain the lease certificate. Disappointed you left the island. You mother taught you not to argue with authorities...
Loc164-1	- OK... Here we go, - the housemaster said and took out a notebook with a pencil. 
*	<clr>What is required to start a starship?<clrEnd>
Loc166-1	Are you sure about that? I will inform the authorities that issued you the permission for space travel. No way, you can't change your answer!!!
*	
*	Alright. Next question:
*	<clr>How do you fry a penchekryak?<clrEnd>
Loc167-1	What do you say? A Faeyan told me that penchekryaks are not suitable for eating in any form. One has to eat mineral fertilisers and drink ekup! But the authors of the test may have a different opinion. We will see later. 
*	
*	Alright, another question:
*	<clr>It does not howl, does not bite, but does not let you inside the house. What is it? <clrEnd>
Loc168-1	Ah, damn it, I ticked off in a wrong column! Does not matter...
*	
*	The fourth question:
*	<clr>Finish the phrase: "All politicians are..."<clrEnd>
Loc169-1	By the way, I would like to warn you that all conversations in this room are constantly recorded by the secret service of the government of <ToPlanet>. But it does not worry you, does it? 
*	
*	Alright. And now - the last question:
*	<clr>Every Maloq loves to...<clrEnd>
Loc172-1	- Fine, so you have passed the test, - Bobchinsky went on.
*	- And now, are your going to sign the lease documents for Hillside? - you asked.
*	- No.
*	- What do you mean no? 
*	- That's what I mean. I am not authorised to deal with leases.
*	- Who is authorised then? - you asked.
*	- Head of the transportation shop, who else?
*	- Why head of the transportation shop?
*	- Because that's his business, - the housemaster replied, crumpling the papers you just brought and throwing them into the trash can.
*	- Why you've just thrown away the papers I brought to you?! - you exclaimed.
*	- These papers had nothing to do with leasing. - was the answer.
*	- Then what has?
*	- Please contact head of the transportation shop regarding all issues. By the way, - the housemaster glanced at his computer screen, - he has just arrived at the ministry and is now in his office. And now excuse me, I have work to do.
*	- But what about...
*	- Leave the room please.
*	"Damn those bureaucrats" - you said to yourself, holding back dirty language.
Loc173-1	- So, hmmm. You've got [p22]. Bad, really bad. According to the tables, you are not a trustworthy member of the galactic society. I am very sorry, but any further co-operation is out of the question. Those who do not pass the test, can not work with the ministry of Rectal Island, - the housemaster said, shaking his head.
Loc174-1	Hopeless to obtain the Hillside lease papers, you returned to your ship, sadly started the engines and flew away from Rectal Island. 
*	
*	Your mission has failed.
Loc175-1	- Well, only out of respect for you, I'd rather have a look at some papers, - Bobchinsky took out a large pack of documents and began searching them.
*	After several minutes he took out a sheet and said:
*	- According to paragraph 31-345, clause 4, individuals, mentally retarded from the birth, can operate in the ministry without successfully passing the test. In such case they are required to pay an amount, proportional to amount of missing points, required to pass the test. In your case it is {(20-[p22])*12} cr.
Loc176-1	You stand outside at the entrance to the pink building. There is a plate above the doors: "Ministry for various affairs of Rectal Island". To the North there is a small lake. You starship is shining in the sun nearby.
Loc176-2	You slowly moved around the building. You found nothing interesting on your way. Except for the windows. But they were all too high to have a look inside or climb in. After you completed a full circle, you arrived at your starting point.
Loc176-3	You roamed about the ship, but haven't found anything useful or at least anything that could be carried in your hands.
Loc178-1	You got knee-deep into the water, but could not extract anything but mud from the bottom. Wait! Something is moving in your hands. It is a small <clr> bloodsucker<clrEnd>.
Loc180-1	As soon as you entered, a heated person ran up to you.
*	- Fish samples. Have you brought them? 
*	- Sure. Here they are, - You handed your three-eyed trophy to the official.
*	- What is it?
*	- A fish.
*	- It has three eyes... Why didn't you disembowel it? - the man said and began shaking the fish.
*	And then the fish, which turned out to be alive, shivered, slid from the hands, broke the window glass and got out to the street. Surprised, you and the official ran to the window and watched the fish jumping towards the lake. 
*	- Are they all like that at your warehouse? We don't deliver anything like that.
*	- What warehouse? I came here to discuss lease of Hillside. 
*	- Lease? You should have said from the very beginning. Instead you come here with a fish... For how many years you want the lease?
*	- Fifty, - you said calmly
*	- No problem, - the head of the transportation shop sat at the table, filled in several blanks and handed them over to you. - Alright, you can go now. Do not disturb me anymore.
*	Satisfied, you headed to your steel eagle and in a few minutes left Rectal Island in a jolly mood and with the lease documents!
Loc181-1	You got into your lovely starship and left Rectal Island. That was right. Meddling with papers is not appropriate for a real ranger.
Loc182-1	The housemaster watches you carefully. He must be waiting for you to pay him.
Path531b	With a serious face, the secretary took a card from the top of the pack. 
*	- I think I stop at this one - the secretary said calmly.
Path540b	- Seven rounds are over. The game is over according to the rules, - the secretary declared.
Path541b	- Seven rounds are over. The game is over according to the rules, - the secretary declared.
Path543	Enough
Path544	More
Path551	Next
Path563	Take the card and look at it
Path563b	Six of diamonds.
Path564b	Ace of clubs.
Path565b	Seven of diamonds.
Path566b	King of clubs.
Path567b	Eight of diamonds.
Path568b	Queen of clubs.
Path569b	Nine of diamonds.
Path570b	Jack of clubs.
Path571b	Ten of diamonds.
Path572b	Ten of clubs.
Path573b	Jack of diamonds.
Path574b	Nine of clubs.
Path575b	Queen of diamonds.
Path576b	Eight if clubs.
Path577b	King of diamonds.
Path578b	Seven of clubs.
Path579b	Ace of diamonds.
Path580b	Six of clubs.
Path581b	Six of hearts.
Path582b	Ace of spades.
Path583b	Seven of hearts.
Path584b	King of spades.
Path585b	Eight of hearts.
Path586b	Queen of spades.
Path587b	Nine of hearts.
Path588b	Jack of spades.
Path589b	Ten of hearts.
Path590b	Ten of spades.
Path591b	Jack of hearts.
Path592b	Nine of spades.
Path593b	Queen of hearts.
Path594b	Eight of spades.
Path595b	King of hearts.
Path596b	Seven of spades.
Path597b	Ace of hearts.
Path598b	Six of spades.
Path600	Next
Path602	Could you remind the rules please?
Path604	Go down the stairs
Path604b	After you cheerfully went down the stairs, you found yourself in the basement and suddenly stepped on your shoelace. The brave ranger sprawled out on the floor like a medusa on the pavement. You stood up, shook the dust off and, oh god! Instead of the expected tidy room you were looking at a ragged basement with a huge hole in the middle. The Registry is anywhere but here. Looks like it was transferred to another room... Or the bureau was sucked into this hole. Right down to hell!!! 
*	
*	"Alright, enough fantasising", - you said to yourself with a smile.
Path606	Approach the door and try to open it
Path607	Game over
Path608	Peek into the hole
Path609	Inspect wallpaper
Path611	Look around
Path612	Talk to the commandant
Path613	Hit the watchman's booth with a fist
Path613b	You hauled off and hit the booth glass. "Bang" - a pleasant sound flew across the lobby. But the glass was not broken. You looked at the commandant, and he only smiled, exposing his only three rotten teeth. Then he suddenly changed his expression and shook his finger at you. Looks like it was the middle finger. 
*	"Be happy as long as you can" - you thought.
Path614	Leave the commandant alone with his memories
Path615	Leave the commandant alone with his memories
Path616	Go to the corridor
Path617	Look outside through the window
Path618	Look at the window
Path620	Back to the lobby
Path621	Back to the lobby
Path622	Go see head of the transportation shop
Path623	Go to the housemaster
Path623b	As soon as you entered the room, a thick bass hit your ears:
*	- Is it reserved for you? - asked a man sitting in a luxurious armchair at a carved table. 
*	- What do you means? - you said.
*	- Have you registered?
*	- As a ranger?
*	- Do you always answer with another question? 
*	- Why do you ask?
*	- Young man, you are beginning to annoy me - leave the room and close the door. 
*	To avoid further problems, you carefully closed the door, although you wished you could slam it.
Path624	Back to the corridor
Path625	Come up to the window
Path626	Back
Path627	To the Secretariat
Path628	Could you tell me where the Registry is? It is not in the basement...
Path629	Can you tell me please how do I find the Registry?
Path631	Approach the secretary
Path632	I came here on a mission from the government of <FromPlanet>. I have to perfect documents for lease of Hillside. How can I do that?
Path633	Step away from the secretary
Path634	Can I ask you, what is your name?
Path635	Probably some other time
Path636	Could you please explain me the rules of 21?
Path637	21? Never heard of it. Can you tell me the rules...
Path638	No, I'm not in the right mood
Path639	Go out to the corridor
Path640	Alright! I love cards!
Path641	Deal faster
Path642	Rather no than yes. I'd rather say definitely no. I mean no, period!
Path643	I love cards, let's play a game or two
Path644	Why don't we play some cards?
Path645	Can you take money instead? Is 100 cr enough?
Path646	Next
Path648	Yeah, you wish! I'm not giving away my stuff!
Path649	You want to leave me naked? No way!
Path653	Give away the clothes
Path654b	You took off the last piece of clothes and gave THAT to the secretary. Rachehanovna only cackled (or was she laughing?). Anyway there was nothing funny for you. You have surrendered you flag, your banner - your <clr>underpants with hearts<clrEnd>!!!
Path656	Alright, here is "something" for you
Path658	Take the thing
Path663b	- Do you want to undress me naked? - cried the secretary.
*	- Yes!
*	- You won't make it!
*	- Mmkey.
Path664	See the brushes manager
Path664b	The manager's office was some kind of a depot, filled with rubbish. A hairy dude in greasy overalls sat in the middle on a paint jar.
*	- Wanna drink? - said the inhabitant.
*	- Alright, - you responded immediately. You did not have to pay anyway.
*	- Take it out then.
*	- Take out what?
*	- Then why do you say "alright"? You all come here with your empty crappy hands.  
*	No, forget about freebies with the dude.
Path667	Can I borrow something here? Anything from the shelves?
Path668	Look, can you sell me anything? You've got a lot of stuff here.
Path669	Fine, I take one for 50 cr
Path670	50? But this crowbar is hardly worth 20!
Path671	I came here on a mission from the government of <FromPlanet>. I have to perfect documents for lease of Hillside. How can I do that?
Path672	Can you tell me please how do I find the Registry?
Path673	Go out to the corridor
Path674	Thank you for the offer, but I don't need it
Path675	Break the door with the crowbar
Path676	Toss the crowbar in the hole with water
Path677	To WC
Path678	Read writings on the walls
Path679	Back
Path680	Enter the first cubicle
Path682	Push the handle
Path684	Take a leak
Path685	Look what's going on in the nearby cubicle
Path686	Enter the second cubicle
Path688	Look around the toilet more carefully
Path689	Leave the cubicle
Path690	To the corridor
Path691	Rock on the chandelier
Path691b	That's your nature. You can not live without flying. Even in such a primitive form. The secretary did not understand your fine nature and prevented you from catching the chandelier. Not this time then.
Path693	Rummage in the trash can
Path693b	- Hey, what are you doing with the trash can? - the secretary shouted.
*	- I'm just looking for some butts, - you tried to justify yourself.
*	- Find yourself another trashcan. All butts in this one are mine. Got it? 
*	- Got it.
Path694b	As long as the secretary had no glasses on, you grabbed the chandelier and started to rock. Whitewashing falls on your head, the chandelier squeaks disgustingly, but you endure that all. Suddenly you hear the secretary's loud baritone: 
*	- I can hear it, stop rocking on the chandelier or I'll hit you with a chair. 
*	"And she means that" - you thought descending on the floor.
Path695b	You quietly came up to the small trash can and put your hand inside. Looks like there is nothing inside but torn papers and useless garbage. Wait! There is something. You looked at it - it was a <clr>garrison cap<clrEnd>. It looked fine. You always liked caps like this one. You wiped off the dust and put the cap on.
Path696b	You quietly came up to the small trash can and put your hand inside. Looks like there is nothing inside but torn papers and useless garbage. Indeed. Nothing else.
Path697	Hit the booth with the crowbar
Path698	As you wish. I'm not giving you more than 20
Path699	60 or 20, I don't care. I don't need your crowbars anyway
Path700	Fine, here is 50 cr
Path701	Back to the corridor
Path702	Break the door with a crowbar
Path702b	You desperately tried to open the door, but the crowbar was useless with such a massive door. What a pity.
Path703	Take your clothes. I don't really need them
Path704b	"Commandant, sorry to disturb you, but..." - you started.
*	"I can see you are wearing the garrison cap of the resistance, soldier. Just let me know what you need. I'm always happy to help you my forest brother!"
Path705	Was a pleasure talking to you. No passaran! We will win!
Path706	And how is it working here? Good?
Path708	Commandant, where is the Registry?
Path709b	- I don't want to play cards, they make me sick, - the secretary said.
Path713	I need to perfect documents for the lease of Hillside
Path714	Tiled
Path715	Masculine
Path716	Feminine
Path717	I am the citizen of the whole galaxy
Path718	I'm from the Rurick family
Path719	I have no nationality because of ideology reasons
Path720	Establishing of training camps to prepare forces for capturing of planet <ToPlanet>
Path721	Building of a resort for members of government of planet <FromPlanet>
Path722	Establishing of a resort and its use for the primary purpose
Path723	At the name of <Ranger>, of course
Path724	At the name of Frecken-Bock - my grandmother is from Urupinsk
Path725	Perfect them in the name of the government of <FromPlanet>
Path726	Thank you!
Path727	Leave the Registry
Path728	Could you please stamp my papers?
Path728b	- Alright, give it to me, - the secretary said. - But wait. I can't find my stamp. Where is it? 
*	- Let me help you to find it.
*	- You wish! Stay away from my stuff!
*	- OK, OK.
*	- Listen up, once I have my stamp, I will stamp your documents. Not now.
Path729b	- Err. Wait! Where is the stamp? Ah, here it is - under the table. - the secretary took the papers from you and stamped every of them. Even where they were not required. - Here you go! Now you only have to see the housemaster.
*	Rachehanovna bend to a small stereophone, took the handset and started talking some gibberish: 
*	"Here for you. Yeah, Charlie, Yes. No! I'm not buying the chrysanthemum. No. The wife have not called. No. Fine. I write him down in the register. That's it."
*	Hanging down the receiver the secretary looked back at you: 
*	- The housemaster is waiting, so you'd better hurry.
Path730	Don't you have the stamp by any chance?
Path731	Don't you have a stamp?
Path732	Comandante, the stamp is required for the revolution. Urgently.
Path734	I'm not answering your questions. Just make the papers!
Path735	Alright, go ahead with your questions
Path737	Spit at the control board, cross yourself and break the key in the ignition lock
Path738	Sitting in the pilot chair, sigh at the desperate situation, forget about it and go looking for a pilot to start this damned starship
Path739	Get out of the starship, come to its front, insert a steel handle into the hole and rotate it quickly until the starship starts.
Path740	Cross yourself, spit over the left shoulder and turn the ignition key
Path745	Alive, scorching it skilfully
Path746	The recipe is simple: toss it into the nozzle of the starship, turn it on and in two seconds - ready! Penchekryak in gasoline sauce with acetates
Path748	Penchekryak meat is too rough for frying. It can only be cooked
Path749	Wife
Path750	Lock
Path751	Code lock
Path752	Toothless and numb dog
Path754	Live at the people's expense
Path755	Bastards!
Path756	Take bribes
Path761	Sit on a traditional Maloq stool and discuss the meaning of life
Path762	Dish out a nuisance
Path763	Smash this Faeyan/Gaalian/Human face
Path764	Get hit in the face
Path765b	- You result is [p22], and, according to the tables, you are quite a trustworthy ranger, - concluded the housemaster.
Path766	Go out to the corridor
Path768	Well, this test obliterated all your efforts. It is time to fly away from this island, drowned in bureaucratic delays.
Path769	But maybe there is something else to be done?
Path770	Are you kidding? I am not retard!!! I am not paying this stupid fee
Path770b	- You can say whatever you want, but we prefer to trust in tests. And not in you, - Bobchinsky said. 
*	After you said everything you thought about the test, the ministry and personally comrade Bobchinsky, you got out of the office and slammed the door, burying the last hope to obtain the leasing papers.
Path771	I do not thing that the amount you mentioned is suitable for me. A can not pay it
Path771b	- I am sorry then. We can not help you, - Bobchinsky said. - Please leave the office.
Path772	Alright, here is the money
Path773b	As soon as you entered, a heated person ran up to you.
*	- Fish samples. Have you brought them? 
*	- What fish?
*	- I ain't doing anything before I have the samples. And now - don't bother me, - the man pushed you outside. You just had no time to respond. 
*	What kind of ministry is that?...
Path774	Don't you have a fish or a fishing rod?
Path775	I need fish. Don't you have some?
Path776	Don't you have a fish by any chance?
Path777	Listen comandante, where do I find some fish here?
Path778	Go outside
Path779	Enter the ministry
Path780	Walk around the building
Path782	Look for something useful in the starship
Path783	Go to the lake
Path784	Go back to the entrance of the ministry
Path785	Get into the lake and look for something on the bottom
Path786	Throw away the bloodsucker and get back to the beach
Path787	Go back to the beach with the bloodsucker
Path788	Attach the bloodsucker to the line and go to the beach
Path789	Cast the line
Path792	Cast the line into the hole with water
Path793	Cast the line in the lavatory
Path795	Toss the crowbar into the lake
Path799	I am sick of this stupid mission. Time to leave the island
Path800	I came here on a mission from the government of <FromPlanet>. I have to perfect documents for lease of Hillside. How can I do that?
Path801	Turn on the vector, energy and navigation systems, check all parameters and start the engines
Path803	Who told you penchekryaks can be fried at all? I always eat them fresh...
Path804	Associated with the mafia
Path805	I have no idea
Path807	Expensive weapon
Path808	I am processing papers for the government of planet <FromPlanet>. They are the ones to pay the official compensations
Path808b	- Alright, I will make a call, - Bobchinsky took the handset, pressed several keys and began speaking with somebody. After a few minutes he replaced the handset. - They checked your account on planet <FromPlanet> and said you could pay the fee.
Path809b	- Alright, I will make a call, - Bobchinsky took the handset, pressed several keys and began speaking with somebody. After a few minutes he replaced the handset. - They checked your account on planet <FromPlanet> and decided to reimburse a part of the fee. All you have to do is pay [p3] cr.
Path810b	- Alright, I will make a call, - Bobchinsky took the handset, pressed several keys and began speaking with somebody. After a few minutes he replaced the handset. - It's all settled. They checked your account at <FromPlanet> and decided to pay the fee.
Path811	That's a mere robbery! I'm not paying this stupid fee!
Path811b	- I am sorry then. We can not help you, - Bobchinsky said. - Please leave the office.
Path812	Pay
Path814	Dead, turning slowly.
Path815	Swearing
