QuestDescription	Yes, <Ranger>, we've got some job for you! You see, our colleagues headed for planet <ToPlanet> of the <ToStar> system to participate in the amateur "Clerks without Borders" competitions. Sounds stupid of course, but for us, simple office employees, these competitions mean a lot. Well, alright. This is still not what I want you to do. The point is that our guys do not understand a thing about sport (they were selected by casting lots). They surely need to have a trainer, but due to red tape delays we failed to hire anyone.  Now, you must have understood what I am driving at, we propose that you occupy yourself in moving our guys to victory. Don't show me a face like that - you, rangers, are so audacious and athletic. Why do you shake your head - I saw this in a stereomovie! To sum it up, if you manage to lead our team to first place, we will pay you a compensation of <Money> cr. Yeah! But only for first place, and not just any place. Moreover, they will wait for you only until <Date>. So what? Will you do that?
QuestSuccessGovMessage	Here he is! <Ranger> - the winner! From the Ranger Negotiations Department to the winner - hip-hip-hurrah! Well, we finally out-pointed them upstarts from the <ToPlanet> planet. Yep! We finished the celebration only yesterday. We almost drank your bonus, oops, almost used your bonus to cope with an emergency situation. But I managed to stop that before action was taken. The agreement is the agreement. So, as agreed I transfer <Money> cr to your bank account.
Par1-1	Money: <> cr
Par2-1	Everything just begins<br>
Par2-2	Day 1<br>
Par2-3	Day 2<br>
Par2-4	Day 3<br>
Par2-5	Day 4<br>
Par2-6	Day 5<br>
Par2-7	Final Day<br>
Par3-1	Ashot cannot move
Par3-2	Ashot flakes out
Par3-3	Ashot's strength: <>%
Par4-1	{[p4] div 100000000 mod 10} {[p4] div 1000000 mod 10} {[p4] div 10000 mod 10} {[p4] div 100 mod 10} {[p4] mod 10}
Par5-1	Bibik cannot move
Par5-2	Bibik flakes out
Par5-3	Bibik's strength: <>%
Par6-1	{[p6] div 100000000 mod 10} {[p6] div 1000000 mod 10} {[p6] div 10000 mod 10} {[p6] div 100 mod 10} {[p6] mod 10}
Par7-1	Cutter cannot move
Par7-2	Cutter flakes out
Par7-3	Cutter's strength: <>%
Par8-1	{[p8] div 100000000 mod 10} {[p8] div 1000000 mod 10} {[p8] div 10000 mod 10} {[p8] div 100 mod 10} {[p8] mod 10}
Par9-1	Domer cannot move
Par9-2	Domer flakes out
Par9-3	Domer's strength: <>%
Par10-1	{[p10] div 100000000 mod 10} {[p10] div 1000000 mod 10} {[p10] div 10000 mod 10} {[p10] div 100 mod 10} {[p10] mod 10}
Par11-1	Elfer cannot move<br>
Par11-2	Elfer flakes out<br>
Par11-3	Elfer's strength: <>%<br>
Par12-1	{[p12] div 100000000 mod 10} {[p12] div 1000000 mod 10} {[p12] div 10000 mod 10} {[p12] div 100 mod 10} {[p12] mod 10}
Par13-1	Sparrings are over
Par13-2	Number of sparrings left: <>
Par14-1	Parameter number 14: <>
Par15-2	Blue: Ashot
Par15-3	Blue: Bibik
Par15-4	Blue: Cutter
Par15-5	Blue: Domer
Par15-6	Blue: Elfer
Par16-2	Red: Ashot
Par16-3	Red: Bibik
Par16-4	Red: Cutter
Par16-5	Red: Domer
Par16-6	Red: Elfer
Par18-1	Parameter number 18: <>
Par19-1	Parameter number 19: <>
Par20-1	Parameter number 20: <>
Par21-1	Points achieved: <>
Par22-1	Planet <ToPlanet> points: <>
Par23-1	Parameter number 23: <>
Par24-1	Parameter number 24: <>
Par25-1	Parameter number 25: <>
Par26-1	Parameter number 26: <>
Par27-1	Parameter number 27: <>
Par28-1	Parameter number 28: <>
Par29-1	Parameter number 29: <>
Par30-1	Parameter number 30: <>
Par31-1	>>> Ashot's mission <<<
Par31-2	>>> Bibik's mission <<<
Par31-3	>>> Cutter's mission <<<
Par31-4	>>> Domer's mission <<<
Par31-5	>>> Elfer's mission <<<
Par31-6	Ashot is your player
Par31-7	Bibik is your player
Par31-8	Cutter is your player
Par31-9	Domer is your player
Par31-10	Elfer is your player
Par32-2	Ashot - is preparing to go to sleep
Par32-3	Ashot - strength
Par32-4	Ashot - craftiness
Par32-5	Ashot - creativity
Par32-6	Ashot - knowledge
Par32-7	Ashot - IQ
Par32-8	Ashot - has taken energine
Par32-9	Ashot - special
Par32-10	Parameter number 32: <>
Par33-2	Bibik - prepares to go to sleep
Par33-3	Bibik - strength
Par33-4	Bibik - craftiness
Par33-5	Bibik - creativity
Par33-6	Bibik - knowledge
Par33-7	Bibik - IQ
Par33-8	Bibik - has taken energine
Par33-9	Bibik - special
Par33-10	Parameter number 33: <>
Par34-2	Cutter - is preparing to go to sleep
Par34-3	Cutter - strength
Par34-4	Cutter - craftiness
Par34-5	Cutter - creativity
Par34-6	Cutter - knowledge
Par34-7	Cutter - IQ
Par34-8	Cutter - has taken energine
Par34-9	Cutter - special
Par34-10	Parameter number 34: <>
Par35-2	Domer - prepares to go to sleep
Par35-3	Domer - strength
Par35-4	Domer - craftiness
Par35-5	Domer - creativity
Par35-6	Domer - knowledge
Par35-7	Domer - IQ
Par35-8	Domer - has taken energine
Par35-9	Domer - special
Par35-10	Parameter number 35: <>
Par36-2	Elfer - is preparing to go to sleep
Par36-3	Elfer - strength
Par36-4	Elfer - craftiness
Par36-5	Elfer - creativity
Par36-6	Elfer - knowledge
Par36-7	Elfer - IQ
Par36-8	Elfer - has taken energine
Par36-9	Elfer - special
Par36-10	Parameter number 36: <>
Par37-1	Parameter number 37: <>
Par39-1	You are as sober as a judge
Par39-2	You are a bit exhilarated
Par39-3	You are tipsy
Par39-4	You are drunk
Par39-5	You are dead drunk
Par39-6	You pass out!
Par40-1	Energine: <> pc.
Par46-1	Parameter number 46: <>
Par47-1	Parameter number 47: <>
Par48-1	Parameter number 48: <>
Loc1-1	The bluish airbus was flying quietly somewhere up ahead, weaving from one air corridor to another. You could see the sights of the mega-polis in the window: neon lights glinting with aqua colours, suspended bridges with walkers small as ants, going on their business, sunbeams trying hard to get to these city levels. You have already seen this many times before. But in spite of this, the scenery was very pleasant to your weary ranger's eyes.
*	
*	A multicolour booklet suddenly came in sight, it was lying in the plastic reading box in front of you. You started to scan through it having nothing better to do:
*	"Clerks without Borders - the competitions of office employees, second in scope only to the Olympics. Clerks and office employees in an atmosphere of sport competition which is alien to them, sudden revealing of talents - these are the main features that attract the attention of hundreds of billion of spectators to this event... As usual, the championship will consist of five classic sports and the Marathon which is changing from time to time..."
*	A usual booklet. Or, maybe it's better to read it more attentively?
Loc7-1	Suddenly, the airbus reduced speed and landed at a small blacktop platform. The passengers started taking their baggage and rolling out into the street like peas. Noting that, you took your small belongings and also left the airbus fast. 
*	
*	You've reached your destination. In front of you is a huge skyscraper of a strange octagonal form with a sign at the top saying "Prism Paradise". According to your data, here is where your trainees stay. 
*	
*	You were talking with them within five minutes already. All future contestants that were entrusted to your care turned out to be small and puny, as if hand-picked. But who knows, maybe they have got some latent talents? Continuing the conversation with such a pleasant company you learned that their names were <clr>Ashot, Bibik, Cutter, Domer and Elfer<clrEnd>. One of those smart sportsmen told you that in fifteen minutes <clr>the whole team will have to go downstairs for a briefing<clrEnd> or something like that.
Loc8-1	You made it fast to the hotel on one of the last airbuses. Merrily discussing the day, all your company occupied their rooms and sat down on the sofas. Tomorrow will be a hard day. You should be very well prepared to it.
Loc8-2	Having reached your floor, your company occupied their rooms and sat down on the sofas. Tomorrow will be a hard day. You should be very well prepared.
Loc8-3	So, what are the plans for tonight?
Loc10-1	- So, what sport do we want to test? - a Peleng asked you, gaping with self-satisfaction.
Loc10-2	You very quickly found the Peleng responsible for familiarising newcomers with sporting equipment at the site and headed for the gym.
*	
*	Having switched on all the equipment, the Peleng asked you tiresomely:
*	- What competition type will we test today?
Loc10-3	A tough Peleng in sporting outfit waited for you downstairs. Having approached you he started to say:
*	- Hello, contestants! My name is Tsvacek. I will be your guide today. Please follow me...
*	The Peleng took a lot of time introducing you to the neighbourhood, showing you where the laundrette, Chinese restaurant and barber's shop were located.  He walked you through picturesque alleys, telling stories from the history of the city and even showed you a monument to the great Chvakher, who killed the last Klissan in the <ToStar> system. 
*	
*	In the evening Tsvacek led you to the sports complex where the championship will take place.
*	- Know what, - the Peleng said. - <clr>You can try all the five sports<clrEnd> that will be presented at the championship. They are: wrestling, swamp games, energy modelling, encyclopaedic and Iike-Baana. According to the procedures, the number of the sparrings at sporting equipment is limited, so you have a total of [p13] <clr>runs-up<clrEnd>. And what I understand by run-up is the following: you quickly put on competition outfit, get to one of the competition simulators, and I quickly conduct the competition as a referee. You know the time is late already. <clr>You can postpone several of your competition sparrings for subsequent evenings.<clrEnd>
*	
*	You headed for the Gym. Having switched on all equipment the Peleng tiresomely asked you:
*	- What competition type do you wish to test?
Loc11-1	<clr>Wrestling.<clrEnd>
*	Who will put on the <clr>blue<clrEnd> outfit?
Loc11-2	<clr>Swamping games.<clrEnd>
*	Who will put on the <clr>blue<clrEnd> outfit?
Loc11-3	<clr>Energy modelling.<clrEnd>
*	Who will put on the <clr>blue<clrEnd> outfit?
Loc11-4	<clr>Encylopedica.<clrEnd>
*	Who will put on the <clr>blue<clrEnd> outfit?
Loc11-5	<clr>Iike-Baana.<clrEnd>
*	Who will put on the <clr>blue<clrEnd> outfit?
Loc13-1	Fine. But <clr>wrestling<clrEnd> - is the competition for two competitors. So you have to choose your opponent who will put on the <clr>red<clrEnd> outfit...
Loc13-2	Fine. But <clr>Swamping games<clrEnd> - is the competition for two competitors. So you have to choose your opponent who will put on the <clr>red<clrEnd> outfit...
Loc13-5	Fine. But <clr>Iike-Baana<clrEnd> - is the competition for two competitors. So you have to choose your opponent who will put on the <clr>red<clrEnd> outfit...
Loc16-1	Blue guy was wrestling as a snake. Red one as soon as he was able to get up was being thrown to the opposite corner of the tatami at the same very moment. <clr>The Blue had the absolute advantage.<clrEnd>
Loc16-2	The fight was dashing. The Red was hardly fanning off his opponent but even this could not last long. Once, and a second time - and the Blue smartly placed the Red on the tatami. Another match - and Red is pinned once again. Yep... <clr>The Blue is wrestling far better than the Red.<clrEnd> That's a fact.
Loc16-3	The wrestling was tense. It seemed that no one will let the victory flee from them, but now the Red was caught nodding and the Blue threw him on the floor at once. And that situation repeated a couple of times. Only at the end the Red managed to flip over his blue contestant (or has he just slipped down?). Anyway, the fight shows that the <clr>Blue is stronger that the Red<clrEnd>.
Loc16-4	The wrestling was sluggish and dull, but it was anyway seen that <clr>the guy in blue was wrestling a bit better than the red one <clrEnd>. We'll take this into account.
Loc16-5	Your trainees were wrestling <clr>with equal strength<clrEnd>, not being inferior to each other in anything. There was no winner in this fight. At last the Peleng was so bored to look at that, that he kicked out both away from the tatami.
Loc16-6	The guys were wrestling slowly and carefully. But the Red attacked more frequently than the Blue and at last he managed to flip him over. This is definite - if you do not throw your opponent, he will throw you. But anyway, the blue was not at all bad. <clr>The Red has just a little advantage over the Blue.<clrEnd>
Loc16-7	The initiative was apparently with the Red - and that was true both figuratively and in the proper sense of the word. He was constantly trying to catch the Blue and throw him on the floor, but the latter was trying his best to resist that. But the initiative pays, so the Blue was several times down. <clr>The red is wrestling better that the blue.<clrEnd> Definitely.
Loc16-8	The red was easily winning over the blue, who could only gain time. Getting tired from looking at the attempts of the blue to win, the Peleng stopped the fight. Well. <clr>The red is far better than the blue<clrEnd> - that was the verdict you've made for yourself.
Loc16-9	The red was fantastic. He was throwing the blue wherever and whenever he wished. As if he were a bag filled with ... potatoes. <clr>The Red has an absolute advantage over the blue.<clrEnd> Definitely.
Loc17-1	The silt was constantly going up from the bottom, so it was very hard to discern at the screen who's where, but when the time was up, and both contestants resurfaced, it turned out that the blue was as clean as a new astracopter. Meanwhile the red did not have a clean spot to blot. No doubt, <clr>the blue fully outmatched the red <clrEnd> in this type of sport.
Loc17-2	The red was swimming in the swamp as a blind kitten, receiving blotches from the blue through the waterweeds. In a couple of times he managed to get the paint over the blue but that was more of an exception than the law. <clr>The blue was far better than the red in the swamping game.<clrEnd>
Loc17-3	The Blue was smarter and was staining the red more often than he himself was stained. The same situation continued until the end of the competition. The fact is that <clr>the blue turned out to be far better than the red<clrEnd>.
Loc17-4	The contestants were doggedly staining each other with a special paint. But <clr>the blue was doing it a bit better<clrEnd>.
Loc17-5	The screens were showing that both of your trainees were hiding behind the hillocks in the muddy waters, trying to stain the opponents. But no one managed to do anything. <clr>It all ended in a draw.<clrEnd>
Loc17-6	The contestants were doggedly staining each other with a special paint. But the <clr>red was doing it a bit better<clrEnd>.
Loc17-7	The red was smarter and was staining the blue more often than he himself was stained. The same situation continued until the end of the competition. The fact is that <clr>the red turned out to be far better than the blue<clrEnd>
Loc17-8	The blue was swimming in the swamp as a blind kitten, receiving blotches from the red through the waterweeds. In a couple of times he managed to get the paint over the red but that was more of an exception than the law. <clr>The red was far better than the blue in the swamping game.<clrEnd>
Loc17-9	The silt was constantly going up from the bottom, so it was very hard to discern at the screen who's where, but when the time was up, and both contestants resurfaced, it turned out that the red was as clean as a new astracopter. Meanwhile the blue did not have a clean spot to blot. No doubt, <clr>the red fully outmatched the blue <clrEnd> in this type of sport.
Loc18-1	Wielding cryonic gloves, your trainee started to mould the energy into some composition, but his imagination was only fast enough to create a formless tortilla-like thing. Yeah, what a mess. This guy <clr>just cannot model at all <clrEnd>.
Loc18-2	Your trainee was slowly moving his gloves around the mass, creating a... mud-pie. Yep. As children do in the kindergarten. Well. Looks like, <clr>the guy has got serious problems with modelling.<clrEnd>.
Loc18-3	The face of the guy in blue was constantly distorted with different grimaces. Looks like he's stretched to the max, and this brought definite results. They were an intricately looking techno structure. From the esthetical standpoint this was done for a C, but, all in all, <clr>the guy has got some makings.<clrEnd>.
Loc18-4	Your trainee's actions were bold and at the same time easy. Even in the middle of the energy composition development process it was seen that he is doing something worthy. And it really ended thus - a very worthy flower composition with petals gleaning over with all colours of the rainbow. The mainstream of the energy work. Well, <clr>the guy has really got very good capabilities<clrEnd>.
Loc18-5	The guy in blue quickly created a considerable piece of the energy and started to model some large work out of it. But he finished work surprisingly quick... Wow! A nice statue of a fabulous being, made very ably. Well, nothing more to say. <clr>The guy has got a talent!<clrEnd>
Loc19-1	You trainee was providing very stupid answers for very simple questions. And all this with a very serious countenance! What a thing! Looks like his <clr>encyclopaedic knowledge is null<clrEnd>.
Loc19-2	The guy put on blue outfit and took a seat at the interview chair. He somehow managed to answer simple questions, but when something more difficult came about, your trainee started to sink. Looks like <clr>he is not much of an erudite<clrEnd>.
Loc19-3	The clerk was providing sensible answers. He was keeping very well. But now the questions from astronomy and physics started to be asked... Well. Your trainee made one mistake after another. But the overall result was not so bad. In general his <clr>erudition is normal<clrEnd>.
Loc19-4	One, two, three. The clerk was cracking the questions like guanava nuts. He was very rarely making mistakes. But this was excusable - you did not know answers to many of the questions 50 questions before that! So, the guy's <clr>erudition is very good<clrEnd>.
Loc19-5	Your trainee was quickly answering all the questions. There seemed to be nothing that he did not know! He made a mistake only once, and this was due to a catch in the wording. (You yourself even did not understand the question, therefore you had to take it at his words). Amazing!. <clr>The guy is fantastically learned!<clrEnd>
Loc20-1	<clr>The blue's advantage was absolute.<clrEnd> The Red was just scratching his head and making absolutely stupid moves. At last, the Peleng referee got tired of such an uncompromising match and gave the sign to stop.
Loc20-2	The blue was making very successful and considered moves, so that the Red player was desperately trying to save the situation. But he was failing in that and was constantly losing. Definitely, <clr>the blue plays far better<clrEnd> than the red in the Iike-Baana.
Loc20-3	The game was going with varying success, but after several matches the blue managed to get ahead in the number of wins after which he enjoyed a constant advantage. In the final matches the depressed red was opposing the opponent's moves sluggishly, not even trying to get use of the latter's lapses. Well, the conclusion is obvious - <clr>the blue plays apparently better<clrEnd> than the red.
Loc20-4	It was a hot fight. No one wanted to concede, but the red was giving a small number of wins over to his opponent. Well, looks like the <clr>blue plays Iike-Baana a bit better<clrEnd>.
Loc20-5	It was an obstinate fight. This time one took the lead, this time the other. The game resulted in <clr>a draw<clrEnd>... The eager accountants were wishing to see the continuation of the fight, but the Peleng showed with a sign that it was the time to stop.
Loc20-6	It was a hot fight. No one wanted to concede, but the blue was giving a small number of wins over to his opponent. Well, looks like the <clr>red plays Iike-Baana a bit better<clrEnd>
Loc20-7	The game was going with varying success, but after several matches the red managed to get ahead in the number of wins after which he enjoyed a constant advantage. In the final matches the depressed blue was opposing his opponent's moves sluggishly, not even trying to get use of the latter's lapses. Well, the conclusion is obvious - <clr>the red plays apparently better<clrEnd> than the blue.
Loc20-8	The red was making very successful and consistent moves, so that the blue player was desperately trying to save the situation. But he was failing in that, and was constantly losing. Definitely, <clr>the red plays far better<clrEnd> than the blue in Iike-Baana.
Loc20-9	<clr>The red's advantage was absolute.<clrEnd> The blue was just scratching his head and making absolutely stupid moves. At last, the Peleng referee got tired of such an uncompromising match and gave the sign to stop.
Loc26-1	- Well. You've exploited your training limit. Now the entrance to the gym is denied you in the evening. But you can have a couple of short training bursts today. Sure, it will not come for free. Say, <clr>50<clrEnd> cr, - the Peleng said.
Loc34-1	For whom will we be thinking out a mission?
Loc35-1	What mission?
Loc47-1	In the morning, after having a bite you brushed yourself up and left the hotel together with your team. The airbus transferred you to your destination very quickly. Having found the contestants' seats, you sat down quickly.
*	
*	- Today is the <clr>Wrestling Day<clrEnd>. No. Not some trifling Sumo. The real Rartan Maloq fighting! - someone's voice was spreading across the huge sporting complex, packed to the max by a motley crowd. - Today we here present will see who is the strongest in this ancient sport. In the times when the Faeyans have not yet devised the stereovision, the Great Rartan was already winning over his...
*	
*	The voice continued to tell about today's activities. You and your magnificent five were sitting yawning on the bench near the action field, waiting for it to begin. There was nothing special to do, and you occupied yourself observing the pretty girls in the front rows. Finally a spiny person in a cap with a lightning emblem came to you and asked to name your contestant for today's competition.
Loc47-2	You spent much time trying to wake up your trainees. But you coped with it. Washing, breakfast, and your are already going down in the elevator. 
*	
*	Having reached the sport complex and showed your tiny badges, you found yourself inside the main arena without any trouble and headed for the contestants' seats. 
*	
*	In the middle of the arena there was already a dozen of swamps prepared. People in canvass-latex suits were plunging some instruments into the water and were making some notes in watertight minicomps. The check of the mudding level was on to comply with the Galaxy standards. The oval plasmoscreen under the ceiling showed the sign: <clr>"Plumpush Day - Peleng swamping contest"<clrEnd>. 
*	
*	Arrived at the place you came up to one of the receptionists to tell the name of a contestant on behalf of your team. The clerk took off a transparent plasmopen, gleaning with a bluish light from inside, and prepared to listen to you.
Loc47-3	You woke up your trainees in the morning and, after necessary washing and breakfast, you dragged them energetically to the competitions.
*	
*	Approaching the main arena you have noticed a large hologram, spinning above the snow-white dome - "<clr>Energy Modelling Day<clrEnd>" - the hologram was made in beautiful orange-yellow shades. The organisers placed a large energy sculpture of an angel delicately spreading wings inside of the building. Commentator voice was spreading across the huge hall. You gave ear to what it said:
*	
*	- When the great human and creator Repin-Aquadansky created his work of genius - the sculpture of an angel, the remake of which is in our hall now, the world realised that a new art was born, as monumental as trackography and chemical reaction poetry. Yes. The Humans once again proved their reputation as the most creative nation of the Galaxy Commonwealth. But the most impressive thing is that energy work cannot be cloned faultlessly, unlike the situation in painting, architecture and trackography, where it is very easy. The problem is the unstableness of energy under the impact of...
*	
*	You got sick and tired of hearing all that, therefore you got completely buried in your own thoughts on the way to the contestants' seats. Finally you and your company reached the destination and started a conversation with the receptionist who was trying to learn who will contest in energy modelling on behalf of your team. Well. Whom will you designate?..
Loc47-4	Morning rays of the <ToStar> star are harsh for your eyes, but, stepping over yourself, you woke up your magnificent five and dragged them to the competitions. 
*	
*	Having reached the sport complex without any problems, you reached into the main arena building, getting trough the crowded passageways. On your way you had to tolerate the most dreary of commentators, who was covering today's events, because you just had no way of getting away from that voice:
*	
*	- Today we interview a renowned encyclopaedist, laureate, winner of several championships and - simply a good Faeyan - dalani Samimurakami. Mister Sami, why the encyclopaedic takes its origins from you, the Faeyans?
*	- This is no secret, - another dreary voice appeared, - that we honour knowledge. The one who possesses knowledge possesses the world. You know. Well, take a hamburger, for instance, can you start eating it, knowing nothing about its biochemical composition, its cooking procedure, conservation, its history - to mention just a few things? Right you are, you cannot. And that's how things stand absolutely with all things. 
*	- Fine. But let's get back to our subject. What do you think, will this <clr>Encyclopaedic Day<clrEnd> be successful?
*	- Naturally, today's contest does not interest me as a specialist. But as an individual I will be interested in hearing stupid answers of the bulk of, well, of all the competitors, if you have it. This competition is not professional... And do you recall the question on the number of Makhpella's eyes?..
*	
*	Suddenly someone grabbed you by the hand. You woke up from trans. 
*	- Who will be taking part in the Ecyclopaedica on behalf of your team? - the receptionist inquired.
Loc47-5	You made some callisthenics in the morning, having made a couple of push-ups. After that you headed to wake up your fighters. Having made quick preparations, you and all your team got down to hotel's lobby...
*	
*	The airbus was approaching the sport complex, but the pilot chose not to get down, but made special flight above and around the huge arena, demonstrating it to the passengers. The whole dome of the gigantic building was spangled with millions of speckled and dappled flowers that were dangling in the wind, resembling an ocean during slight breeze. In the middle of a composition of flamed flowers a sign read "<clr>Gaalian Iike-Baana Day<clrEnd>".
*	Aerobus touched down soon, and you, headed for the entrance with all your trainees, greatly impressed by what you saw.
*	Everything was also decorated with an incredible amount of flowers inside, they put in spirals and hanging just above spectators' heads throughout the hall. In the middle, on the main platform, the table was already set and ready for hot fighting of the intellects. 
*	
*	Gazing at all this beauty and thus constantly bumping at passers-by, you made it to the contestants' seats and even managed to find the receptionist without any trouble. So, who will fight today this intellectual battle?
Loc50-1	Your trainee was wrestling worse than bad, was constantly pinned, and therefore scored only [p30] out of 15 available points.
Loc50-2	Your trainee was wrestling rather mediocre, loosing this time, winning that. As a result - [p30] points out of 15.
Loc50-3	Your fighter showed master class today. He won over most of his competitors and had [p30] points out of 15 in your collective hoard.
Loc55-1	Your trainee was acting very ineffectually in the Plumpush. Therefore his score was only [p30] out of 15 available points.
Loc55-2	Your fighter was deftly ducking in the swamp and frequently had some wins. But the opponent was not just slumbering there in the swamp. Therefore the score was [p30] out of 15 points.
Loc55-3	Your trainee was very smart. Not many contestants could reach him with their paint. Therefore the result was imposing - [p30] out of 15 point.
Loc56-1	Energy modelling was going very poor with your protégé this day. The referees evaluated his work only as [p30] out of 15 available points.
Loc56-2	Your trainee was toiling hard creating his work. But the referees evaluated it only as [p30] out of 15. Probably they were right, probably no.
Loc56-3	Your sportsman was modelling with fire kindling in his eyes. It was seen that something serious would come out. In the end the referees were generous enough during their evaluation. Your collective hoard was replenished by [p30] points out of 15 available.
Loc57-1	You sportsman tried hard but was constantly providing wrong answers to very simple questions. As a result, today you had just [p30] out of 15 available points.
Loc57-2	Your trainee was rather good in answering questions and went ahead of most of the players. And his score thanks to it was [p30] points out of 15 available.
Loc57-3	The fighter of your army was mightily answering all the questions, almost making no mistakes. As a result his score for today was [p30] out of 15.
Loc58-1	Iike-Baana was going totally amiss with your sportsman today. In all the meanings.  And so the result was just [p30] out of 15 available points.
Loc58-2	Your protégé was acting rather successfully today: he was winning many times, although there were also lost battles. The result was - [p30] out of 15.
Loc58-3	Your trainee was effervescent today. There were few who could worthily oppose him. As a result of this your collective hoard was replenished by [p30] out of 15 available points.
Loc62-1	In the morning you got up quickly and headed to the competitions with your team. 
*	
*	The airbus reached the sport complex fast. Having got outside you noticed that the crowd was larger than usual today. And this was not surprising - today is the main day of the competitions. The Marathon. Having reached the contestants' seats via the well-known route, you found the receptionist. It turned out that the first contest for today will be the "<clr>Stone Sculpture Making<clrEnd>".
*	
*	So who will be the contestant for this particular competition?
Loc62-2	The second was <clr>Encyclopaedic Cheats<clrEnd>. Someone has to take part in this contest from your team. You have to decide who.
Loc62-3	The third competition will be the <clr>Cyborgdrom<clrEnd>. The contestants will be making up robots, program their intellects and lead to the arena to fight. 
*	
*	Who will be participating from your team?
Loc62-4	<clr>Air bat Scuffles<clrEnd> - was the next competition. Someone has to represent you team. But who?
Loc62-5	Now the time for the final contest has come - the <clr>Virtual Space Orientation<clrEnd>. You should select a contestant. Who will that be?
Loc67-1	Your contestant was diligently trying to make some stone sculpture, but very little was coming out of it. As a result - [p30] out of 15.
Loc67-2	Your fighter was somehow making something out of a stone that was then evaluated as [p30] out of 15. Well, that's something.
Loc67-3	Your team sportsman was assuredly implementing his thought. He was unremittingly finishing every detail. The result exceeded all the expectations (not yours, of course) - the referees evaluated him as [p30] out of 15.
Loc68-1	Your protégé was trying hard but his opponents were able and cheated him frequently. Your fighter lacked either knowledge or craftiness. Or, maybe, it was all because of the fatigue... But, anyway, it all does not matter now, for the result was more than modest - [p30] out of 15.
Loc68-2	Your protégé was keeping himself assured and often cheated his opponents, asking questions with catches. But the opponents were not dreaming. Therefore the result was not the best available - [p30] out of 15.
Loc68-3	Sportsman of your team was winning over everyone. It was hard to oppose him. Therefore the result was worthy - [p30] out of 15.
Loc69-1	The cyborg, your team managed to make, turned out to be stupid, the robots a bit cleverer were kicking it all the way. As a result the work of your protégé was evaluated as [p30] out of 15.
Loc69-2	The cyborg, your team managed to make, was not awful. It managed to destroy several badly screwed prototypes of the opponents. But in the end, smarter robots overcame your tin fighter. The result was - [p30] out of 15. Well, not that bad.
Loc69-3	Your protégé created an almost ideal cyborg, who was outperforming all the opponents' prototypes without any trouble. The result was - [p30] points out of 15.
Loc72-1	Your trainee was constantly kicked out of the narrow fighting ground. Light handed opponents beat him as they found fit, cheated him as they wanted... The result was - [p30] out of 15.
Loc72-2	Your "gladiator" was looking not that bad. He overcame several opponents without much fuss. But he was also beaten several times. The result of [p30] points out of 15 was good enough, but not excellent.
Loc72-3	Your fighter was beating everyone who was approaching him on the way. When he could not overcome by strength, he used craftiness. In general, his performance was excellent. And the result was the like - [p30] out of 15.
Loc73-1	Your newly made ranger was acting too bad. He was always flying to the wrong direction, refilling on the wrong planets. Well, what can be said. He received the result that well matched his performance - [p30] out of 15.
Loc73-2	Your protégé was ably coping with the space orientation, he even finished with good timing. The result of the evaluation was - [p30] out of 15.
Loc73-3	Your fighter was well ahead of the others from the very beginning and that situation continued until the end. It looks like the knowledge of our galaxy, together with judicial calculation during the rally played their part. Your team's collective hoard was replenished by [p30] out of 15 available.
Loc80-1	In the evening all the teams gathered in the assembly hall. The head of the referee board was proclaiming the results against the backdrop of some solemn music. But <clr>you were not the winner<clrEnd>, the winner was the team of planet <ToPlanet>, who scored [p22] points. Well, you had to get back with empty hands. Saying goodbye to your trainees, you headed for the spaceport.
Loc80-2	In the evening all the teams gathered in the assembly hall. The head of the referee board was proclaiming the results against the backdrop of some solemn music. But <clr>you were not the winner<clrEnd>, the winner was a team from the planet <ToPlanet>, who scored [p22] points. Well, you had to get back with empty hands. Saying goodbye to your trainees, you headed for the spaceport.
Loc80-3	In the evening all the teams gathered in the assembly hall. The head of the referee board was proclaiming the results against the backdrop of some solemn music. But <clr>you were not the winner<clrEnd>, the winner was the team of planet <ToPlanet>, who scored [p22] points. Well, you had to get back with empty hands. Saying goodbye to your trainees, you headed for the spaceport.
Loc81-1	In the evening all the teams gathered in the assembly hall. The head of the referee board was proclaiming the results against the backdrop of a solemn music. And, oh, miracle, the <clr>first place was occupied by your team <clrEnd>! You made them all, including the favourite - the team from planet <ToPlanet>. Hooray! Your trainees were awarded with platinum medals, and the officials solemnly shook your hand (they could've given you a couple of credits instead). After which a march of the <FromPlanet> planet was playing...
*	
*	After this, already leaving the sport complex you overheard that your team failed to beat the record of the championship - <clr>124 points<clrEnd>. <clr>You could have got a prize in the amount of 2000 cr<clrEnd> for that. Well, that was not my goal, anyway, - you comforted yourself, leaving the place. 
*	
*	After the award ceremony ended you barged yourself into your room and celebrated the victory by the book. You never suspected that the clerks were capable of drinking so much. Late in the night you said farewell to your championship fellows and headed for the spaceport. Each extra day spent on this planet will delay the rendezvous with your <Money> cr.
Loc82-1	Today's competition ended. The evening shades spread out across the mega-polis. You and your team stand at the gates of the sport complex. You have <clr>several test sparrings left<clrEnd>. Maybe, it's better to use the opportunity? Or fly to the hotel at once?
Loc83-1	You reclined at ease at a small sofa in a room lighted by a dim yellowish light coming from two lamps. There is a stereovision system hanging on the opposite wall, a hatchball match is on. A graviboat is prowling here and there with various drinks. Looking around you, you noticed other visitors to the recreation room sitting on black leather sofas. <clr>A Human drawing something<clrEnd> in his notebook, <clr>a sportsmanlike Peleng<clrEnd> who was constantly throwing up his hands and murmuring something every time the match was turning hot, and a <clr>Maloq in a sports outfit decorated with many medals<clrEnd>.
Loc83-2	You reclined at ease at a small sofa in a room lighted by a dim yellowish light coming from two lamps. There is a stereovision system hanging on the opposite wall, a hatchball match is on. A graviboat is prowling here and there with various drinks. Looking around you, you noticed other visitors to the recreation room were sitting on black leather sofas. <clr>A Human drawing something<clrEnd> in his notebook, <clr>an anaemic Faeyan<clrEnd>, tiresomely following the match, and a <clr>fat bald Human<clrEnd>, who was sleeping leaning on a small table, that was standing close to his little sofa.
Loc83-3	You reclined at ease at a small sofa in a room lighted by a dim yellowish light coming from two lamps. There is a stereovision system hanging on the opposite wall, a hatchball match is on. A graviboat is prowling here and there with various drinks. Looking around you, you noticed other visitors of the recreation room, who were sitting on black leather sofas: <clr>an anaemic Faeyan<clrEnd>, tiresomely following the match, <clr>a wild and woolly Maloq <clrEnd> in county-like brown overall, and a <clr>Maloq in sports outfit <clrEnd>.
Loc83-4	You are reclining at ease at a small sofa in a room lighted by a dim yellowish light coming from two lamps. There is a stereovision system hanging on the opposite wall, a hatchball match is on. A graviboat is prowling here and there with various drinks. Looking around you, you noticed other visitors to the recreation room itting on black leather sofas. s<clr>A sportsmanlike Peleng<clrEnd>, who was constantly throwing up his hands and murmuring something every time the match was turning hot, <clr>a wild and woolly Maloq <clrEnd> in county-like brown overall, a <clr>fat bald Human<clrEnd>, who was sleeping leaning on a small table, that was standing close to his little sofa, and a <clr>Gaalian in yellow suit <clrEnd> with a red badge on the breast.
Loc83-5	You are reclining at ease at a small sofa in a room lighted by a dim yellowish light coming from two lamps. There is a stereovision system hanging on the opposite wall, a hatchball match is on. A graviboat is prowling here and there with various drinks. Looking around you, you noticed other visitors to the recreation room sitting on black leather sofas: <clr>a wild and woolly Maloq <clrEnd> in county-like brown overall, a <clr>fat bald Human<clrEnd>, who was sleeping leaning on a small table, that was standing close to his little sofa, and a <clr>Gaalian in yellow suit <clrEnd> with a red badge on the breast.
Loc86-1	Having looked through the booklet thoroughly, you discerned four data sections:
*	
*	CHAMPIONSHIP SCHEDULE:
*	
*	Day One:
*	<clr>Wrestling<clrEnd>. We'll see how <clr>strong<clrEnd> our contestants are.
*	
*	Day Two:
*	<clr>Plumpush: Swamping games<clrEnd>. The main rule: <clr>Crafty<clrEnd> clerk is good clerk. Who will be the best?
*	
*	Day Three:
*	<clr>Energy Modelling<clrEnd>. Real, not stereotyped, <clr>creativity<clrEnd>.
*	
*	Day Four:
*	<clr>Encyclopedica<clrEnd>. As the saying goes, <clr>knowledge<clrEnd> is power. And for a clerk the more so.
*	
*	Day Five:
*	<clr>Iike-Baana<clrEnd>. IQ and <clr>Logical<clrEnd> Thinking. The smartest will win.
*	
*	Day Six(Pentathlon):
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Stone Sculpture Making.<clrEnd> Only the <clr> strong and creative<clrEnd> contestant will reach success.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Encyclopedic cheats.<clrEnd> It is not enough to be <clr>erudite<clrEnd>, when your opponents constantly try to <clr> outsmart<clrEnd> you.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Cyborgdrom.<clrEnd> Use all your <clr>IQ and creative capabilities<clrEnd>, in order to create the smartest robot.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Air Bats.<clrEnd> A narrow track, two fighters, huge air bats. The winner will be the <clr>strongest and craftiest<clrEnd>.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Virtual Space Rallies.<clrEnd> Ideal <clr>knowledge<clrEnd> of our Galaxy and <clr>logic<clrEnd> - this is the key of victory.
Loc86-2	Having looked through the booklet thoroughly, you discerned four data sections:
*	
*	CHAMPIONSHIP SCHEDULE:
*	
*	Day One:
*	<clr>Iike-Baana<clrEnd>. IQ and <clr>Logical<clrEnd> Thinking. The smartest will win.
*	
*	Day Two:
*	<clr>Energy Modelling<clrEnd>. Real, not stereotyped, <clr>creativity<clrEnd>.
*	
*	Day Three:
*	<clr>Encyclopedica<clrEnd>. As the saying goes, <clr>knowledge<clrEnd> is power. And for a clerk the more so.
*	
*	Day Four:
*	<clr>Wrestling<clrEnd>. We'll see how <clr>strong<clrEnd> our contestants are.
*	
*	Day Five:
*	<clr>Plumpush: Swamping games<clrEnd>. The main rule: <clr>Crafty<clrEnd> clerk is good clerk. Who will be the best?
*	
*	Day Six(Pentathlon):
*	This year the organisers have the following competitions for the contestants:
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Stone Sculpture Making.<clrEnd> Only the <clr> strong and creative<clrEnd> contestant will reach success.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Encyclopedic cheats.<clrEnd> It is not enough to be <clr>erudite<clrEnd>, when your opponents constantly try to <clr> outsmart<clrEnd> you.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Cyborgdrom.<clrEnd> Use all your <clr>IQ and creative capabilities<clrEnd>, in order to create the smartest robot.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Air Bats.<clrEnd> A narrow track, two fighters, huge air bats. The winner will be the <clr>strongest and craftiest<clrEnd>.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Virtual Space Rallies.<clrEnd> Ideal <clr>knowledge<clrEnd> of our Galaxy and <clr>logic<clrEnd> - this is the key of victory.
Loc86-3	Having looked through the booklet thoroughly, you discerned four data sections:
*	
*	CHAMPIONSHIP SCHEDULE:
*	
*	Day One:
*	<clr>Energy Modelling<clrEnd>. Real, not stereotyped, <clr>creativity<clrEnd>.
*	
*	Day Two:
*	<clr>Plumpush: Swamping games<clrEnd>. The main rule: <clr>Crafty<clrEnd> clerk is good clerk. Who will be the best?
*	
*	Day Three:
*	<clr>Iike-Baana<clrEnd>. IQ and <clr>Logical<clrEnd> Thinking. The smartest will win.
*	
*	Day Four:
*	<clr>Encyclopaedica<clrEnd>. As the saying goes, <clr>knowledge<clrEnd> is power. And for a clerk the more so.
*	
*	Day Five:
*	<clr>Wrestling<clrEnd>. We'll see how <clr>strong<clrEnd> our contestants are.
*	
*	Day Six(Pentathlon):
*	This year the organisers have the following competitions for the contestants:
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Stone Sculpture Making.<clrEnd> Only the <clr> strong and creative<clrEnd> contestant will reach success.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Encyclopedic cheats.<clrEnd> It is not enough to be <clr>erudite<clrEnd>, when your opponents constantly try to <clr> outsmart<clrEnd> you.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Cyborgdrom.<clrEnd> Use all your <clr>IQ and creative capabilities<clrEnd>, in order to create the smartest robot.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Air Bats.<clrEnd> A narrow track, two fighters, huge air bats. The winner will be the <clr>strongest and craftiest<clrEnd>.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Virtual Space Rallies.<clrEnd> Ideal <clr>knowledge<clrEnd> of our Galaxy and <clr>logic<clrEnd> - this is the key of victory.
Loc86-4	Having looked through the booklet thoroughly, you discerned four data sections:
*	
*	CHAMPIONSHIP SCHEDULE:
*	
*	Day One:
*	<clr>Encyclopaedica<clrEnd>. As the saying goes, <clr>knowledge<clrEnd> is power. And for a clerk the more so.
*	
*	Day Two:
*	<clr>Iike-Baana<clrEnd>. IQ and <clr>Logical<clrEnd> Thinking. The smartest will win.
*	
*	Day Three:
*	<clr>Plumpush: Swamping games<clrEnd>. The main rule: <clr>Crafty<clrEnd> clerk is good clerk. Who will be the best?
*	
*	Day Four:
*	<clr>Energy Modelling<clrEnd>. Real, not stereotyped, <clr>creativity<clrEnd>.
*	
*	Day Five:
*	<clr>Wrestling<clrEnd>. We'll see how <clr>strong<clrEnd> our contestants are.
*	
*	Day Six(Pentathlon):
*	This year the organisers have the following competitions for the contestants:
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Stone Sculpture Making.<clrEnd> Only the <clr> strong and creative<clrEnd> contestant will reach success.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Encyclopedic cheats.<clrEnd> It is not enough to be <clr>erudite<clrEnd>, when your opponents constantly try to <clr> outsmart<clrEnd> you.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Cyborgdrom.<clrEnd> Use all your <clr>IQ and creative capabilities<clrEnd>, in order to create the smartest robot.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Air Bats.<clrEnd> A narrow track, two fighters, huge air bats. The winner will be the <clr>strongest and craftiest<clrEnd>.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Virtual Space Rallies.<clrEnd> Ideal <clr>knowledge<clrEnd> of our Galaxy and <clr>logic<clrEnd> - this is the key of victory.
Loc86-5	Having looked through the booklet thoroughly, you discerned four data sections:
*	
*	CHAMPIONSHIP SCHEDULE:
*	
*	Day One:
*	<clr>Iike-Baana<clrEnd>. IQ and <clr>Logical<clrEnd> Thinking. The smartest will win.
*	
*	Day Two:
*	<clr>Encyclopaedica<clrEnd>. As the saying goes, <clr>knowledge<clrEnd> is power. And for a clerk the more so.
*	
*	Day Three:
*	<clr>Wrestling<clrEnd>. We'll see how <clr>strong<clrEnd> our contestants are.
*	
*	Day Four:
*	<clr>Plumpush: Swamping games<clrEnd>. The main rule: <clr>Crafty<clrEnd> clerk is good clerk. Who will be the best?
*	
*	Day Five:
*	<clr>Energy Modelling<clrEnd>. Real, not stereotyped, <clr>creativity<clrEnd>.
*	
*	Day Six(Pentathlon):
*	This year the organisers have the following competitions for the contestants:
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Stone Sculpture Making.<clrEnd> Only the <clr> strong and creative<clrEnd> contestant will reach success.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Encyclopedic cheats.<clrEnd> It is not enough to be <clr>erudite<clrEnd>, when your opponents constantly try to <clr> outsmart<clrEnd> you.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Cyborgdrom.<clrEnd> Use all your <clr>IQ and creative capabilities<clrEnd>, in order to create the smartest robot.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Air Bats.<clrEnd> A narrow track, two fighters, huge air bats. The winner will be the <clr>strongest and craftiest<clrEnd>.
*	<format=left,2>-</format><clr>Virtual Space Rallies.<clrEnd> Ideal <clr>knowledge<clrEnd> of our Galaxy and <clr>logic<clrEnd> - this is the key of victory.
Loc88-1	Uncombed young man was drawing something in his notebook, and seemed to be fully concentrated on his work. You were not wishing to distract the artist from his work, but still...
*	- Excuse me, I would wish to know... - you started with all manner of aristocratic intonation.
*	- Yeah, whaddayawant? I mean... What can I help you? - the artist responded.
Loc88-2	- Blast you into the swamp mud! Where d'ya think you're getting?! - the Peleng was outrageous. - Hit him at the knees, at the knees, will you! Well, that again. Assume that you will punch in the belly, and then make a left hook. This is elemental. No, I can't stand that... These yellow-green players just cannot play. Who trained them, I wonder!
Loc88-3	As soon as you approached the Faeyan, he addressed you amiably:
*	- Hello! My name is Aikanaut. Do you want to take part in my experiment?. <clr> I will pay you 20 cr<clrEnd> for that.
Loc88-4	- Hi, there, - you saluted the husky fellow.
*	- Hi, sportsman! You are a sportsman? - the Maloq inquired.
*	- Not quite. I am a trainer. At least for today.
*	- Wow! What a coincidence. I am a trainer myself, I mean - the breeder. I breed penchecrakuses. And sometimes not only penchecrakuses, - the huge guy roared a good laugh.
Loc89-1	- Trainee... Well. OK. It's deadly dull here anyway, so just for the interest's sake I will show your protégé a couple of tricks. It may even considerably <clr>develop his perception of art, if he understands not a thing in art and creative work.<clrEnd>.
*	
*	So, whom it's best to send for the artist's lesson?
Loc89-2	- OK. Whom will we be training? Have you decided that? - the Peleng inquired.
*	
*	And really whom?
Loc89-3	- I don't need several. This does not fit into the experiment frame. I need just one Humanoid.
*	
*	The conditions are clear. Whom will we select?
Loc89-4	- Well, well, what do you think I am having here, a food economy? I have a portion only for one mouth for today. 
*	- OK, let it be one, - you replied.
*	- Deal. Take your buddy and get here. I have everything ready.
*	
*	So who will you select for the treatment?
Loc93-1	- And what I am talking about? Hit him in the kidney. No team will face up to good hatching. By the way, who are you? Have I seen you someplace? - the Peleng said noticing you at last.
*	- I am a trainer of one of the team, - you said.
*	- Wow! And I am a trainer. And not just a trainer, but the trainer of the Wild Fruggiesss team. The discovery of hatchball season of the year before last! 
*	
*	Your face showed admiration and deference, although you have heard absolutely nothing about a team like that, it was present neither in the major nor in the higher leagues. 
*	
*	- I have been awarded a letter of acknowledgement of the third degree for a special training method: "Scoop and Win". <clr>A very effective method for training strength and craftiness<clrEnd>. And this is the main thing in hatchball. You know...
*	- If you are so good a trainer could you somehow whip my team into shape? 
*	- A team - no. The method will not work... I could've trained one person perhaps, you know. But I am a professional, I don't work for free. But as you are my colleague, I will not charge you high, say, some <clr>150<clrEnd> cr.
Loc93-2	- How they are bred? Tenderly, - the Maloq laughed once again. - First feed the critter to repletion with one supplement, then the other. Well, why am I telling you this. You will not understand it anyway. Better hear this. I am here for the annual Best Breeders Forum. And I also brought here my new supplement - Yum-Yum. It increases penchecrakuses' <clr>IQ level<clrEnd>, but that's not all, it also works on Humans and Maloqs. I nourish my wife with this supplement, so that she saves more money. And - can you believe me - it works! Honestly, she <clr> loses some strength<clrEnd>, but she is not supposed to carry penchecrakuses that weigh some 500 kg. And I get an extra crate of kinza every week. Dig that? Well, I somehow guess that you do not... You would benefit from my supplement. What? Alright, I'll charge only the base price - <clr>30<clrEnd> cr.
Loc94-1	- Yes. I am a maniac. But I am a maniac of science. I am its servant, eternal slave. And concerning the stereo-programs... Know what, I do not watch them. So how about taking part? <clr>The deal about 20 cr remains in force!<clrEnd>
Loc94-2	- I am the developer of the general knowledge testing system. Therefore, my experiments consist of testing my testing system on all the beings. So what about my proposal on taking part in my experiment?
Loc96-1	A Maloq is sitting tiresomely viewing hatchball. Looks like he is confused. Most probably because of the end of his sporting career. Maybe, its best to leave him alone?
Loc96-2	Fat man was lying face on the bar.
*	- I am beeeastly drrrunk again, whooo-whaa, - he announced when you approached him. Then started murmuring something like: - Well shirigim duraham da. Wack for my daddy oh, wack for my astracopter... There's whiskey in the jar.
Loc96-3	- Hello, - you addressed the Gaalian, but he did not react. He was plunged deep in the match.
*	- Hello!!! - you yelled, so that the callers started to look back at you.
*	- Why do you bother the doctor at the time you do not need aid? What a gaucherie. I think you better leave me alone with the Game.
Loc98-1	Is the yellowish dot following the bluish dot, or vice versa?
Loc98-2	The camera's close-up showed one player leisurely kicking the other in the ham, thus getting a notice from the referee. What a brutal game, my boy!
Loc98-3	A fanatic scuffle started in the seats. It was soon stopped by the coppers.
Loc98-4	G-o-a-l! The player who won a point for the team climbed into the fan seats out of joy. The security pulled him out of there in the underwear. The fans have taken his cryoboots, t-shirt and shorts as souvenirs.
Loc98-5	One of the players was fast running with a ball to the flank. But what's that? Oops. He's gone into the changing room, leaving the ball on the field. Well, yes, when you're all set for a whiz, you will perform gimmicks even more exorbitant.
Loc98-6	The game was on, and suddenly one player knocked down another.
*	- Foul play! - you exclaimed.
*	- What are you talking about? This is real hatching, - someone corrected you.
*	You would not argue.
Loc98-7	The stereovision was showing a commercial of some formula. After this airing of the hatchball match will be continued.
Loc100-1	- Gee whiz, you are almost zonked out! -  exclaimed the Gaalian sensing the smell coming out of your mouth. Having sucked in the air once again, he pronounced a verdict: A critical concentration of alkaloids. You are in need of immediate aid!
*	Having inquired with difficulty where your room was located, the Gaalian led you out of the recreation room, and led you to your hotel room, again with difficulty. 
*	- Here. Take this <clr>energine pill<clrEnd> prior to going to bed. You will be vigorous as Forshmacek Vulgaris.
*	Having said that the Gaalian headed in an unknown direction.
Loc108-1	In the evening all the teams gathered in the assembly hall. The head of the referee board was proclaiming the results against the backdrop of some solemn music. And, o miracle, <clr>your team won the first place<clrEnd>! You made them all. Hurrah! Moreover - <clr>your team managed to beat the record of the championship - 124 points<clrEnd>. The names of the contestants and that of their trainer will be now included into the records book. Three cheers!!! Additionally, <clr>they gave you a trainer monetary reward to the tune of 2000 cr<clrEnd>. This pleased you incommensurably more than being recorded in the records book of the Clerks without Borders championship. 
*	
*	After the award ceremony ended you barged yourself into your room and celebrated the victory by the book. You never suspected that the clerks were capable of drinking so much. Late in the night you said farewell to your championship fellows and headed for the spaceport. Each extra day spent on this planet will delay your rendezvous with your <Money> cr.
Loc110-1	"PREREQUISITES FOR SELECTING COMPETITION TYPES":
*	The scholars all over the world agree that the <clr>main contestant characteristics are - strength, craftiness, creative capabilities, knowledge and IQ<clrEnd>. Based on that we selected the <clr>corresponding<clrEnd> five classic competition types: Rartan wrestling, Plumpush - Swamping games, Energy Modelling, Encyclopedica and Iike-Baana. If a competitor possesses the aforementioned qualities, he will gain success. 
*	
*	It's noteworthy, by the way, that the capabilities, used in one classic sport <clr>provide absolutely no impact<clrEnd> on other classic types. As a matter of course this rule does not apply in marathon, because of the interfacing character of the competitions. Moreover, <clr>in marathon competitions the low level of one of the competition characteristics will lead to rather bad overall performance, even if the level of the other characteristic would be substantially high<clrEnd>. For instance, if we take the air bats, you cannot win this game only by sheer force. You must use craftiness frequently, otherwise a strong sportsman will be outplayed by his more crafty opponents.
*	
*	Another important factor is the competitors' fatigue. <clr>Even a most talented but tired sportsman can be knocked down by a mediocre opponent who is in good form <clrEnd>. Yep. <clr>half<clrEnd> tired sportsman will be performing <clr> two times<clrEnd> worse than that who had a 100 percent rest. And very tired one will show no result at all. Therefore all trainers, when the time of the competition is approaching, are trying to give their sportsmen some rest, so that they could restore after the trainings..."
*	
*	...this section was further describing philosophic aspects of each of the competition types, but you skipped it. 
*	
*	TEAM ORGANIZATION:
*	The teams are organised by the computer based on all-embracing week-long testing of the aspirants. As the result <clr>the competitors are randomly selected but so that the sums of team's abilities be equal<clrEnd>. For example, if three team member lack any abilities in, say, creative work, the remaining two will necessarily be able (and maybe just one, but in this case he has to be smashingly talented.). The same thing concerns all the competitive characteristics. 
*	
*	WHO WINS:
*	In each of the classical sport the competitor can score <clr> up to 15 points<clrEnd>, that are placed in the team's collective hoard. The competitor can also wing <clr>no more than 15 points<clrEnd> at each stage of the marathon. Its noteworthy that <clr>as a rule the competitor who possesses more than one talents, required for the competition, and that are on the acceptable level, can win the marathon.<clrEnd>..."
*	
*	Next was the chronology of the championship and the champion list, after which a huge space was dedicated to some armpit spray ad. You noticed only that the main favourite of this year's competitions is the team of the <ToPlanet> planet. 
*	
*	"I should follow their performance very closely", - you said to yourself.
Path2	Study the booklet thoroughly
Path9	Fifteen minutes? So what are we waiting for! Let's get forward for the briefing
Path11	Energy modelling
Path12	Swamping games
Path13	Encyclopedica
Path14	Wrestling
Path15	Iike-Baana
Path16	I changed my mind. I wish to chose another competition type
Path17	Cutter
Path18	Bibik
Path19	Domer
Path20	Ashot
Path21	Elfer
Path23	Cutter
Path24	Bibik
Path25	Domer
Path26	Ashot
Path27	Elfer
Path28	Stop. We'll assign the blue for another...
Path29	I changed my mind. I wish to chose another competition type
Path37	Further
Path38	Further
Path39	Further
Path40	Further
Path41	Further
Path59	Well, I think, it's enough for the familiarisation with the sporting equipment. Its time to get to the hotel. For a rest deserved.
Path60b	As soon as you trainees got back to the seats, the hall was filled with someone's hoarse voice, saying:
*	- Who would perch out here? The arena is closed. Sitting here at that hour is proscribed!!!
*	Looking back you noticed a bearded man in a winter earflap hat with a hydraulic broom in his hands, who was running in your direction. Turning to the seats of your trainees you saw none of them there, for they were running to the exit already. You were not hesitant in following suit - considering that when a hydraulic broom bumps your head it will not be perfectly inappropriate.
*	
*	Within half an hour you were heading to your hotel in a comfortable airbus.
Path61	Give a bribe of 50 cr and continue familiarisation with the simulators
Path61b	- Can we continue? - you said, giving the money over to the Peleng.
*	- Hmm. The watchmen here can get vicious, and there may also arise problems with the bosses, but if you insist, well, let it be so... - Tsvacek retorted grabbing the money.
Path71	Appoint the missions for late evening early night
Path72	Cutter
Path73	Bibik
Path74	Domer
Path75	Ashot
Path76	Elfer
Path77	I changed my mind. The mission stays as it was
Path78	The study of endshpil Iike-baana sets with the use of houseplants - for the development of IQ.
Path79	Reading, listening to and possibly even watching lectures in GuideNet to increase your knowledge
Path80	Give an energine pill to your trainee
Path80b	You gave an energine pill to your trainee and he was out in a minute. You somehow dragged him to the sofa. After all night's sleep he will be fresh as new.
Path81	Creative experiments with the leaven dough for overall development of creative abilities
Path83	Training of cheating manoeuvres in a swamp lavatory in order to master craftiness (including military ruse)
Path85	Lifting up stools and sofas, wrestling with the curtains to improve physical form
Path86	Plain and healthy sleep
Path96	Explain the missions to them and go to sleep yourself
Path134	Domer
Path135	Cutter
Path136	Elfer
Path137	Bibik
Path138	Unfortunately I've got no contenders for today's competition
Path138b	Baffled receptionist headed in an unknown direction. The only thing you can do is to watch today's competition that's all. When it ended, all of you went to your hotel rooms in a regressed mood.
Path139	Ashot
Path164	Cutter
Path165	Bibik
Path166	Domer
Path167	Ashot
Path168	Elfer
Path193	Unfortunately, there will be no competitor from our team today
Path193b	- That means that you drop out of the remaining part of the competitions, - the receptionist informed you leaving.  
*	
*	The remaining part of the day you occupied yourself watching the performance of other teams waiting for the results.
Path196	No missions. All go to bed!
Path198	Get back to your hotel rooms
Path199	We will remain here to familiarise ourselves with the equipment! We need to use the chance of sparring simulation.
Path200	Well, that's enough sparring. Time to go to the hotel. To have a rest that all well deserved.
Path202	Finish reading
Path207	Put the booklet in your pocket, just in case you might need it, and continue gazing at the city
Path211b	Getting down in the lobby, you noticed a sign over a large two-leaved door, saying: "Recreation room: hatchball matches 24 hours.". A ticket-taker was sitting at the door stupidly staring at nothing. <clr>Having paid him 25 cr,<clrEnd> you got inside with no problems and placed yourself on one of the little sofas.
Path213	Come up to the Human with a notebook
Path214	Sorry, just checking
Path215	I would like to talk to you about art. Take for instance a punctured astracopter that burns in the atmosphere while crashing. Or a beaten Maloq's snoot. Is there anything more beautiful?
Path215b	- A bold Maloq by Snicker - yes, that a magnificent sculpture work. But don't forget about the Lame Peleng by the Humster Horsegrove. And how nice is the Galatea with a tachyon cutter...
*	You talked with the artist for several hours about the art, cultural disintegration of the nation, and on the general strengthening of one's body by means of urinal therapy. When the morning came the security asked you to leave civilly. You obeyed. Saying goodbye to the artist, you went to bed.
Path216	You are an artist, I gather. And not bad, it looks. Can teach one of my trainees to create something artistically?
Path217	Don't take anyone. Say goodbye to the artist and get back to your seat
Path222	Cutter
Path223	Bibik
Path224	Domer
Path225	Ashot
Path226	Elfer
Path227b	Taking your trainee you easily found the breeder's room. Having paid him the agreed upon amount you placed yourself on a sofa waiting for the events to develop. At last the Maloq dragged a barrel and a huge scoop. Seeing these instruments, your trainee rushed to the door. It was closed. He rushed to the window, but then the Maloq gripped your sportsman professionally by the scruff. 
*	- Where d'ya think your goin'? You are not fed yet. 
*	He started to regale you protégé.
*	- This one's for the daddy, this one's for the mommy, this one's for the Yam-Yam bush, - the Maloq was saying feeding your trainee with a greenish fluid.
*	The Maloq's actions were slow, so that the ... foodstuff would digest well. Therefore the treatment ended only in a couple of hours. Your trainee crumpled to the sofa, his strength left him. Surprisingly he started to do some arithmetic exercise at once. 
*	- Look here. <clr>He grew wiser.<clrEnd> And what I was saying. This is an alright slop. <clr>He will lose some strength though<clrEnd>. Has been tested. And no he needs to get fast into his stall. I mean to the room. He's got to digest it properly. 
*	Saying this, the Maloq showed you the door. Well, it was nothing doing. You had to drag your well-fed fighter to the team's headquarters.
Path228b	Agreed upon everything with the Faeyan you visited him in his room together with your trainee. The testing took quite a time. During all this period you were closely following the process, sitting in a soft terry cloth armchair. You were being caught by the slumber, but the constant beeping of the Faeyan' computer was raising you up. 
*	
*	The morning came, and the first rays of the <ToStar> star were getting inside through the jalousie, being pleasant to the eye. Looking at this spectacle you understood that the testing ended. 
*	- Alright, - the Faeyan said. - The experiment is completed. Now I will got to sleep.
*	- And what about the result?! - you shouted suddenly.
*	- Well, do you need it that bad? OK, I'll tell you. According to the results of my testing, <clr>the general IQ of your protégé is <clrEnd> {(([p18] div 100 mod 100)>=8)*60+(([p18] div 100 mod 100)<8)*(([p18] div 100 mod 100)*6+(1 to 6))} <clr>out of 60<clrEnd>. But you should take it into account, that the testing is not approbated yet, there is some inaccuracy, inexactitude of the results. But <clr>for my system it is not important whether the tested being is tired or not <clrEnd>. OK. Now its time to get to bed. 
*	
*	The Faeyan gave you the agreed upon <clr>20<clrEnd> cr, helped you to the exit and went to sleep. You and your sportsman were not slow to follow suit. You went into your room to sleep the remaining hours.
Path230b	Having determined the trainee you gave the money to the trainer. 
*	
*	Within fifteen minutes you were staying near a swamp, located at the back of the hotel. A boisterous Peleng armed himself with a long stick and ordered your protégé to duck into the muddy guck. After this he started to pierce him with that same stick. At first the poor trainee was constantly getting it in the ribs but soon your fighter <clr>started to act with more craftiness<clrEnd>, and now the trainer was missing him frequently. But in general the training affected your protégé for the swimming in the Peleng swamp required <clr>good physical training<clrEnd>. When at last the morning came and the Peleng finished the training, you and your trainee that exhausted to the max went to your rooms.
Path232b	Having found your trainee, you cancelled all his missions for today and took him to the "artist cell". The artist was busy with you was protégé for several hours. All this time you were looking at how the member of the artistic intelligentsia tried to drub into the clerk's head something useful, demonstrating him different work of arts and various drawing and sculpture making techniques. Looked like your trainer already knew many elementary tricks, which caused a great deal of admiration on the part of the artist. 
*	
*	Finally the artist said:
*	- Your trainee is not so bad - for a clerk I mean, - he said. - I could not teach him that many things in such a short time. But he <clr>learned a thing or two<clrEnd> and now is more enlighten in the arts. 
*	
*	Interesting, but it looked like the tired out artist conked out as soon as he uttered these words. You left his room on tiptoes.
Path234b	Having found your trainee, you cancelled all his missions for today and took him to the "artist cell". The artist was busy with you was protégé for several hours. All this time you were looking at how the member of the artistic intelligentsia tried to drub into the clerk's head something useful, demonstrating him different work of arts and various drawing and sculpture making techniques. 
*	
*	Finally the artist sat down in the chair and put a yellow towel on his head, showing that he is weary:
*	- Oh, boy, I was doing all that I could, - he uttered. - This unenlightened human has learned many things. <clr>Some headway was definitely made.<clrEnd> Oh. That's all. I need to go to sleep now.
*	
*	Looks like the artist really conked out. You left his room on tiptoes.
Path236	Looks like the Peleng is frustrated
Path237	Go in the direction of the Peleng
Path238	Bad, bad, bad. What d'ya think your doing?! Think first, than kick. And not just the air, get it in his kidney, in his kidney!!!
Path239	No. For me its too expensive. I better get back to my place.
Path240	OK!
Path241	I changed my mind. The training is cancelled. Sorry for the trouble
Path241b	Strange but the Peleng was not listening to you. He was all kept by the game.
*	- Go, go, go... G-o-a-l!!!
*	
*	Not waiting for the reaction of the seasoned trainer, you got back to your place. Good that you haven't given him the money.
Path242	Experiments? Well, and who are you, not a manic of course? I think I saw your hologram in the "Wanted by the Police" stereoprogram.
Path243	I am a member of the Experiment Banning Society. Taking part in such events contradicts the society's charter and my personal moral beliefs. So, please excuse me
Path244	I am a member of the Experiment Banning Society. Taking part in such events contradicts the society's charter and my personal moral beliefs. So, please excuse me
Path245	Agree!
Path245b	Aikanaut <clr>spent three ours for all-embracing testing of your knowledge <clrEnd>, he asked you various questions and put down the results into a small notebook. Finally, he completed his activity, thanked you for taking part in it, <clr>gave you 20 credits<clrEnd> and headed for the exit.
*	- And what about the results?! - you shouted to his back.
*	- You don't really want to know them? I think that would impact your self-esteem. 
*	Saying this, the scientist decamped, and you were gone to your room.
Path246	What kind of an experiment?
Path248	What kind of an experiment?
Path249	I personally do not thirst for taking part myself. But I got several humans that could be of help to you
Path250	Refuse to take part in the experiment and get back to your seat.
Path251	All that you say is very interesting but it is time for me to go
Path252	Penchecrakuses? So, how do you breed them?
Path253	Honestly, I don't need that. But there are several candidates who would be greatly moved by such a treatment
Path254	You cannot feed anyone with penchecrakus cans - this is banned by the Humanoid Rights Treaty! This will not happen. Good bye.
Path255	Well, know what? We all had good supper tonight, we will not have place for penchecrakus food, sorry.
Path256	Make tracks for the be-medalled guy
Path257	Get back to your seat
Path258	Talk to the Maloq
Path258b	- Hello! - you said.
*	- Hi there. I think you do not recognise me. I was known in any shabby village five years ago...
*	The Maloq started to tell you about his sporting achievements. You were listening to him at first out of courtesy, but soon tried to escape. But the Maloq was always nipping your escape attempts in the bud.
*	- No. Listen to me. You ain't know nothing. - he was saying amiably grappling you around the neck. Your neck-bones were almost cracking...
*	The Maloq finished his narrative only in the morning. You have nothing left to do but to get back to your room.
Path259	To the fat human
Path260	Sing the song together
Path260b	You took up the song with the drunken fat human. Quiet at first, the buddy let himself go and started squalling the song out loud. The security appeared out of nowhere and took the fat man out of the room. Together with you. You started to protest, but they quashed you by the stunner.
*	You recovered in your room on the morning after. You cannot get back to the recreation room anyway. It's better to sleep the remaining ours...
Path261	Approach the Gaalian
Path262	Looks like the graviboat has free bear. You have to order a tankard for you
Path262b	The graviboat delivered the free beer to you. Having tried it, you exclaimed that you tasted better. But you would be pleased even with soda water as a freebie. Having finished your drink, you saw that you started to get drunk. Looks like the <clr>brew was too strong<clrEnd>.
Path263	Watch hatchball match
Path265	Take a break
Path266	Continue to watch
Path269b	Fat man was lying face on the bar.
*	- I am beeeastly drrrunk again, whooo-whaa, - he announced when you approached him. Then started murmuring something like: - Well shirigim duraham da. Wack for my daddy oh, wack for my astracopter... There's whiskey in the jar.
*	Having heard a familiar tune you could not restrain yourself from repeating it. Especially in your condition. At first you and the fat buddy were singing the song quietly, but then the buddy let himself go and started squalling the song out loud. The security appeared out of nowhere and took the fat man out of the room. Together with you. You started to protest, but they quashed you by the stanner.
*	
*	You recovered in your room on the morning after. You cannot get back in time. Its better to sleep the remaining ours...
Path270	Put the pill in the pocket
Path270b	having put the pill in the pocket, you entered the room and got down on the sofa. You were sleeping like that until the morning. As usual for the morning after your had a good headache <clr>but now you have an energine pill in your reserve<clrEnd>.
Path271	Take the pill and go to sleep
Path271b	Having taken the pill, you felt that you were conking out, and merely managed to get to the sofa. But in the morning you were extraordinary vigorous. <clr>The pill took out all the fatigue!<clrEnd> And the hangover effect as well...
Path272	Try to get back to the recreation room
Path272b	Turning around you went down on the stairs, but could not hold the walls and... Regaining conscience in the morning you barely made it to your room where you slept the remaining hours right on the floor. You had no strength to crawl to the sofa.
*	Waking up in the morning, <clr>you could not find the pill <clrEnd>. It must have been lost somewhere. <clr>You should put tiny things like this in the pocket.<clrEnd>
Path284	Join the Faeyan
Path285	Get to the rough Maloq
Path286b	The graviboat got you the beer another time. You did not want to drink, but the freebie was irresistible... <clr>You conked out<clrEnd> after the fifth sip.
*	
*	You recovered on the sofa in your room. Thanks God, - security had not pushed you outside, or put in a garbage container, but dragged you here. Having realized that you conked out once again. This time until the morning..
Path287	Send all to sleep, and get down to the recreation hall yourself. (25 cr for a pleasant time spending is a trifle)
Path288	Get back to your room and go to sleep
Path292b	- You have not exhausted you training limit, so you can come tomorrow if you wish, - the Peleng said, helping you to the airbus stop.
*	
*	Having reached the hotel with no problems, you got inside. Waiting for the elevator you looked around the lobby and saw a double-leaved wooden door with a sign sating: "<clr>Recreation Room<clrEnd>". A tablet was hanging below saying - "Always <clr>free beer<clrEnd> and hatchball match broadcasting. Opens at night. <clr>Entrance fee - 25 cr<clrEnd>". You should not this.
Path293b	Having reached the hotel with no problems, you got inside. Waiting for the elevator you looked around the lobby and saw a double-leaved wooden door with a sign sating: "<clr>Recreation Room<clrEnd>". A tablet was hanging below saying - "Always <clr>free beer<clrEnd> and hatchball match broadcasting. Opens at night. <clr>Entrance fee - 25 cr<clrEnd>". You should not this.
Path297	There is a booklet about the championship in the overall. You should look into it.
Path298	Explain the missions to them and then go down to recreation lobby (25 credits for pleasant leisure is an easy expence)
Path300	I've got the booklet about the championship on me. I better look into it.
Path301	I've got the booklet about the championship on me. I better look into it.
Path308	There is a booklet about the championship in the overall. You should look into it.
Path313	Read further
Path314	Return to the beginning of the booklet.
Path315	Finish reading
