QuestDescription	We offer you the most honorable mission, <Ranger>. The fact is that the crown prince of our planet showed brilliant abilities in all areas of science and would like to continue his studies at the famous Gaalian University of the planet <ToPlanet>, which is located in the <ToStar> system. Unfortunately, the prince cannot take the entrance exams, because according to the ancient tradition of our planet, no one has the right to ask questions to members of the royal family. Since your strength, intelligence and ingenuity are widely known, we invite you to fly to the planet <ToPlanet> and, on behalf of the prince, pass the entrance exams to Gaalian University. If you accept our offer, you will have to bring your university admission document to our planet <FromPlanet> (<FromStar>) no later than <Date>. Then your reward for completing this quest will be <Money> cr. Good luck!
QuestSuccessGovMessage	You did a great job, <Ranger>! The king of our planet expresses his sincere gratitude to you and transfers well-deserved <Money> cr. Good luck to you!
Par1-1	Strength: <> (terrible)
Par1-2	Strength: <> (bad)
Par1-3	Strength: <> (middle)
Par1-4	Strength: <> (good)
Par1-5	Strength: <> (ingeniously)
Par2-1	Intellect: <> (terrible)
Par2-2	Intellect: <> (bad)
Par2-3	Intellect: <> (middle)
Par2-4	Intellect: <> (good)
Par2-5	Intellect: <> (ingeniously)
Par3-1	Agility: <> (terrible)
Par3-2	Agility: <> (bad)
Par3-3	Agility: <> (middle)
Par3-4	Agility: <> (good)
Par3-5	Agility: <> (ingeniously)
Par4-1	You have a "secret weapon"
Par5-1	Passed exams: <>
Par7-crit	Your mission has failed miserably!
Loc1-1	The huge building of the University of the Planet <ToPlanet> immediately struck you with its size, decoration, harmony and interior decoration of this temple of science. "But first things first!" - you decided and went through the door with the inscription "Admission Committee". Behind it, you found a large hall, along which applicants walked, busy with paperwork. You turned to one of the clerks at the far end of the hall for clarification. He agreed to help you.
*	
*	- First you must complete the application form for admission to the entrance examinations in two copies. You can take any of the slips on that table over there. Then you will have to put three seals on it and certify it in the office of the University. Then you will need to take the completed forms to the document reception room, where you will be given an examination sheet and an applicant's badge.
Loc4-1	Thanked the clerk, you spent an hour filling out the application, after which you went out into the inner garden of the university. Walking among exotic plants and exchanging meaningless phrases with other applicants, you were able to evaluate your own intelligence, strength and agility according to the five-point system adopted here.
*	
*	Then you noticed that at the far end of the garden there is a large podium, on which a respectable-looking Gaalian professor has just climbed. It looks like you need to hurry there, so as not to accidentally miss any important information.
Loc5-1	After a good night's sleep, you went to the University the next morning. The first thing that caught your eye was an intersection of five gaseous arrows - pointers to the pavilions where exams were held in one or another subject. Somehow, the mist swirling around under your feet held a clear shape. It looked pretty impressive.
Loc6-1	You have come to the very beginning of the professor's speech, missing only his name. But you managed to understand that this is none other than the rector of the university himself!
*	
*	 - ... at our University! - said the rector. - To do this, you only need to pass two exams. Moreover, adhering to the ancient democratic tradition, we allow applicants to choose the exams that are most suitable for them. You can even change your exam if you accidentally came to the wrong place. But no retakes! The level of the University of the planet <ToPlanet> does not allow us to accept any losers. After all, such famous humanoids came out of the walls of our University as...
*	
*	After arguing for an hour and a half about the glory, greatness, prestige and richest traditions of the University, the rector finally ended his speech with the words:
*	
*	- I remind you that exams begin tomorrow, and today you can relax as you wish. So, see you tomorrow, and BREAK A LEG!!!
Loc7-1	Applicants dispersed in all directions, and you thought: how to spend today?
Loc8-1	Walking around the beautiful capital of the planet <ToPlanet>, you suddenly saw the rector studying the theater poster with great attention. In the rector's pocket, you noticed a small red notebook.
*	
*	"These must be questions for tomorrow's exam!" - you guessed it. "They would be very useful to me!"
*	
*	Your actions?
Loc9-1	The library was located at the other end of the university campus. You decide to take a shortcut and go past the wasteland behind the university garages. At the same time, you accidentally saw how three hooligans mocked a chick of alcaris - a small but very smart bird race from Orion, one of the satellites of the planet <ToPlanet>. Having tied a large heavy piece of iron to the chick's paws, they shot at it from slingshots, trying to hit it directly in the head. alcaris managed to dodge the shots so far, but it was clear that his strength was running out, and he would not last long.
*	
*	What did you decide to do?
Loc10-1	Aha! Have you forgotten that alcohol is prohibited on the gaalian planets?! All pubs here are non-alcoholic!
*	
*	You were served a glass of voodka, the most disgusting gaalian drink, which, nevertheless, held the galaxy record for specific calorie content per unit cost. Luckily, your personal flask is always with you. You sat in a corner and quietly began to sip your favorite drink, unnoticed by the gaalians.
*	
*	As your eyes adjusted to the half-darkness of the bar, you noticed a middle-aged bald man at the next table. By the characteristic reddish cyanosis of his nose and the general swelling of his face, you easily identified him as a lover of strong drinks.
*	
*	What will you do?
Loc11-1	A strange sight met your eyes on your way to the spaceport: a dozen youths of different races were dragging heavy stones from place to place under the guidance of a faeyan worker. The guys were clearly exhausted. Your decision?
Loc12-1	You walked around the city until dark. The beauty and grandeur of the capital of the planet <ToPlanet> made an indelible impression on you. You especially liked the gas fountains that seem to hang right in the air here and there. In fact, computers hidden from prying eyes changed the colors of the intersecting streams of various gases, due to which absolutely fantastic pictures appeared to the observers.
*	
*	A long walk improved your health and you felt a little stronger.
*	
*	Finally, remembering the upcoming exams, you decide to go to bed.
Loc13-1	The good-natured robot librarian gave you a mass of educational microfilms equipped with a search minicomputer and a semantic hypnotizer. Immersed in an artificial trance, you learned a lot of new and useful things. Among the films you studied were such authoritative publications as "One Hundred Ways to Cheat a Human Examiner", "Peculiarities of Faeyan Psychology", "Methods of Physical Influence on Pelengs", "How to Defeat Dominators" and even the thoroughly watched "How to Justify Yourself to Your Sponsor in failure in the entrance exams to Gaalian University".
*	
*	You were in the library until closing time. But now you feel a little smarter.
*	
*	It's probably time for bed.
Loc14-1	Your mission has failed miserably!
Loc15-1	You sat in a bar until you drank all the contents of your flask. You also imperceptibly poured a glass of voodka into a tub of a gaalian palm tree of an unknown species standing nearby, after which, as it seemed to you, it's leaves immediately turned yellow and withered (in fact, palm trees of the noelemakh species changed color of their leaves depending on the time of day). As you exited the bar, you swayed slightly from side to side, but your spirits were upbeat.
*	
*	"Drinking alcohol all evening in front of a dozen gaalians, and not one of them suspected anything!" - you thought with delight. - "Oh, and you're a smart guy, <Ranger>, I swear!"
*	
*	However, in order to think any good tomorrow, you have to go to bed.
Loc16-1	You worked together with everyone without sparing yourself, and by evening all the stones were moved to the right place. It was easy and pleasant for you to work, only the heavy, suspicious glance of the faeyan was somewhat embarrassing. What is it for?
*	
*	Intense work strengthened your spirit, and you felt stronger, more agile and smarter than in the morning. Maybe you should still go to the exams tomorrow? ..
Loc17-1	Due to a heavy thunderstorm, the student ID ceremony was cancelled. Everything went on as usual. The same clerk who helped you complete your paperwork handed you a student ID that smelled like fresh ink.
*	
*	"I immediately understood what you would do," he confessed to you in confidence. - "I have such an intuition!"
*	
*	You got the feeling that with the issuance of your student ID, the inhabitants of the planet began to respect you more.
*	
*	Leaving the University building, you hurried to the spaceport - after all, you still need to take this student ID to the real prince of the planet <FromPlanet> no later than <Date>.
Loc18-1	The inscription above the arrows-indicators read:
*	                                            
*	
*	S E L E C T     Y O U R     E X A M
Loc19-1	To pass the exam in mathematics, applicants were called in turn to a small room. Judging by the faces coming out of there, they had a hard time inside. When it was your turn, you saw the only alcaris examiner in the room, sitting on a narrow perch. This did not surprise you too much, since you already knew from the University's advertising booklet that mathematics is taught there by a small race of intelligent birds - alcaris, living on Orion, a satellite of the planet <ToPlanet>.
*	
*	Staring at you with unblinking yellow eyes, the examiner asked a single question:
*	
*	"How much is 2+2?"
Loc20-1	Most of the gym, where the physical education exam was held, was occupied by a huge boxing ring. In the middle of the ring hung a massive punching bag, which was furiously beaten by a big trainer-maloq. Each of his blows forced the pear to deviate at a significant angle from the vertical.
*	
*	Pale-looking applicants stood uncertainly along the wall. For some reason, none of them was eager to enter the ring and box with a coach to pass the exam.
*	
*	Looking around, you, involuntarily thought about what you should do.
Loc21-1	The literature exam was taught by two humanoids: an elderly gaalian professor, whom you were surprised to recognize as the rector, and a young peleng assistant. To whom will you take the exam?
Loc22-1	The chemist turned out to be a bald, middle-aged man with a blue-red nose and a puffy face. He was standing in front of a table laden with a bunch of all sorts of cones, beakers and test tubes with all kinds of reagents. In front of each of the applicants who came to the chemistry exam, there was exactly the same table.
*	
*	- Attention! the examiner said. - Now I will show you a simple chemical experiment, and you will all have to repeat it. So, we take trepalium dioxide, add confucium bicarbonate, having previously mixed it with radium hydropyrite (do not confuse it with rhodium hydropyrite, the test tube with which stands between 3-methyl-decibulin and sulfuric acid), and put it all on an alcohol lamp, and in the meantime a mixture of magnesium and iron dioxide are treated with decibellic acid, - the reagents flashed faster and faster over the chemist's table, like cards in the hands of an experienced card sharper, the explanations became more and more slurred, - adding caustic soda and a drop of glycerin here ... we use 99% potassium permanganate as a catalyst ...remember to shake well...evaporate over the fire...separate the potassium and sodium...add the arsenic...remove the spirit lamp...add...divide...add...multiply...now everything is the same, only in reverse order... And what will we get as a result?
*	
*	The examiner looked around at the applicants, but only dead silence was his answer.
*	
*	"Pile of gold!" he shouted, turning over the largest flask. And indeed, a small pile of golden sand spilled out of the flask.
*	
*	- Now it's your turn, - the chemist said ominously.
Loc23-1	The labor examiner was a bile-pedantic faeyan, dressed in work overalls.
*	
*	- See that pile of rocks? - he began his briefing. - You must take exactly 50 of them and drag them over there. In short, you will carry stones from the fence until lunch. All clear? The countdown is on!
Loc24-1	You calmly and accurately dragged exactly 50 stones in a couple of hours. After making sure that everything was done correctly, the examiner gave you an "excellent" mark.
*	
*	"Who do you have to be in order not to pass this exam ?!" - you thought in amazement.
Loc25-1	"Of course I remember you," the chemist was obviously happy to see you. - "You certainly deserve an "excellent" rating, because at least one chemical compound you love and appreciate as much as I do!"
*	
*	With these words, the person put "excellent" in your examination sheet.
Loc26-1	You have successfully passed the math exam.
Loc27-1	Your conscientiously made bandage convinced the trainer. As an exception, he agreed to replace your boxing match with another martial art. What sport do you prefer to compete in?
Loc28-1	Physical education exam is over!
Loc29-1	When you were a casino croupier on your home planet, earning your first starship, you performed trickier tricks. With amazing agility, you completely duplicated not only the professor's experiment, but also his comment, only inserting a small change at the very end:
*	
*	- And what will we get as a result? - you asked, turning over a large flask. - Yes, a pile of gold and 100 cr on top!
*	
*	And indeed, the banknote of 100 cr you pulled out of your sleeve in time fell exactly on top of a pile of golden sand.
*	
*	Having laughed at your joke, the examiner gave you a well-deserved "excellent".
Loc30-1	Alcaris was furious at your answer. Beside himself with rage, he yelled:
*	
*	- OUT!!! GET OUT OF HERE, STUPID BEAST!!! How dare you enter the University of the Planet <ToPlanet> without even knowing the basics of arithmetic?! So that your legs are no longer here !!!
*	
*	Your appeals to the administration were rejected. Apparently, the authority of the Alcaris as mathematicians was indisputable in the eyes of gaalians.
*	
*	Your mission failed...
Loc31-1	"Pathetic attempt!" - hissed the alcaris, stomping with anger with all three paws, - "answer my question immediately and do not try to drag out any more time!"
*	
*	And then suddenly, as if some kind of intuitive insight flashed through your brain. Exactly! The correct answer clearly flashed in your head! But which one is correct?
Loc32-1	Five minutes of talking with you was enough for the professor to make a verdict:
*	
*	"You, young man, understand modern Gaalian poetry, like dominators in trade!"
Loc33-1	Gazing at you with an arrogant, contemptuous look, the assistant asked:
*	
*	"What is the quintessence of the immanent-allegorical rationalism of contemporary Gaalian poetry?"
*	
*	What are you going to do?
Loc34-1	The rector just turned green with pleasure. 
*	
*	Either the gaalians are also defenseless against flattery, like any other race, or the rector was just very happy about the return of the notebook... In general, you got "excellent" in literature!
Loc35-1	The frustrated assistant called for the help of a professor
*	
*	What are your next steps?
Loc36-1	After the Literature exam, you felt like a squeezed lemon. And yet, you did it!!!
Loc37-1	Near the hostel you met a group of senior students. After hanging out with them for an hour, you learned a lot of useful information about the upcoming exams, namely:
*	
*	- Only the dumbest, weakest, or most awkward guys can fail the LABOR;
*	
*	- Fools in MATHEMATICS have nothing to do, as well as weaklings in PHYSICAL CULTURE;
*	
*	- Only very agile guys can pass CHEMISTRY;
*	
*	- It’s better not to meddle in LITERATURE at all, since only outstanding personalities can hand it over to a professor, and a professor’s assistant is a cowardly snob who doesn’t put "excellent" on anyone at all.
Path11	Go to sleep
Path12	Hurry to the professor
Path13	THANKS!!!!
Path14	Go for a walk around the city
Path15	Go study in the library
Path16	Go relax in a tavern
Path17	Go to the spaceport and fly away so that you don't disgrace yourself tomorrow
Path18	Just walk on by
Path18b	"Probably not worth the risk," you decided and continued your walk.
Path19	Try to stealthily pull out a notebook from the rector's pocket while he is reading the poster (how to do it more cleverly?)
Path19b	Your attempt to pick out the rector's pocket was so clumsy that even a slow gaalian professor managed to catch your hand!
*	
*	After your tearful tales of a difficult childhood and a hungry youth, he agreed not to call the police, on the condition that you leave the planet <ToPlanet> before midnight. Of course, there could be no question of any admission to the university ...
Path20b	A slight movement of the hand, and the book changed its owner!!!
*	
*	Quickly lost in the crowd, you took a closer look at your trophy. But you were in for a bitter disappointment: instead of exam questions, the whole book was filled with handwritten poems about the role of morality in the learning process. Judging by the abstruseness, boringness and intricacy of the verses, only the rector himself could be it's author.
*	
*	However, you put the book in your pocket so as not to waste a good thing!
Path21	Try to sneak past before the hooligans get the idea to play with YOU the same way
Path21b	Completely absorbed in their occupation, the hooligans did not notice you. "Poor alсaris," you thought, glad you didn't suffer his fate.
Path22	Rush to the aid of the alсaris (soberly assessing your strength)
Path22b	Shouting "Long live Orion!!!" you rushed into battle, but the first bully easily knocked you down, and the second hit you on the head with brass knuckles. What the third bully did to you, you were able to establish only from the conclusion of the forensic medical examination, which you read a couple of days later, while lying in the hospital. Of course, the entrance exams had already passed by that time ...
Path23b	Slowly approaching the hooligans, you calmly and weightily said: "And now, RUSTY DOMINATORS, get out of here!" To the question of one of the hooligans: "Who are you?" you answered with such a blow to the jaw that his friends hurried away without any questions ...
*	
*	"Thank you, Prince!" - said the chick you saved. In response to your puzzled look, he explained: "Your name and title are on the applicant's badge that you wear on your chest. By the way, I may be able to thank you at the entrance exams. The probability of this event is 20-25%."
*	
*	You decide to take Alсaris with you to your exams - what if he brings you good luck?
Path24	Go to sleep
Path25	Continue drinking without paying any attention to the alcoholic person
Path25b	After glancing a few times in your direction and realizing that he had nothing to catch, the man soon left the bar.
Path26	Invite a person to join you (since alcohol is illegal, such an offer must be made wisely).
Path26b	Unfortunately, your invitation turned out to be so rude and clumsy that it caused distrust in a person. Deciding that you are a spy provocateur, he called the police to avert any suspicions from himself ...
*	
*	Oh, how bitterly he repented, realizing his mistake! But it was even worse for you when you were expelled from the planet <ToPlanet> for a day for violating the Prohibition...
Path27b	You politely and tactfully invited the person to join you and he gladly agreed.
*	
*	- You are lucky that the Gaalians have a weak sense of smell, - your drinking companion said after the first glass. - After all, as soon as you entered, I understood by the smell of WHAT you have in your flask. But don't think that I'm an alcoholic! No, I just can smell dozens of substances...
*	
*	After a couple of hours, your new acquaintance, citing urgent matters, got up from the table. Before leaving, he said:
*	- Thank you friend for a wonderful evening! - and, leaning closer, he whispered, pointing to your badge: "You're an applicant, right? Come to my exam tomorrow, I'll put you "excellent"!"
*	
*	You were so happy to hear these words that you even forgot to ask what exam he was taking tomorrow.
Path36	Go to sleep
Path37	Yes, you need to go to sleep before tomorrow's exam
Path39	Come closer and read the names of subjects
Path40	C H E M I S T R Y
Path41	M A T H E M A T I C S
Path42	P H Y S I C A L   C U L T U R E
Path43	L I T E R A T U R E
Path44	L A B O R
Path45	Get started
Path46b	You began to slowly drag stones, trying to save energy and not lose count. But while carrying the 13th stone, you accidentally tripped and dropped it right on the examiner's foot! Deciding that you did it on purpose, he achieved your exclusion from the list of applicants ...
Path47b	Using your superiority in strength and agility over the rest of the participants in the exam, you completed the task in 30 minutes, and calmly rested in the shade, cheerfully watching efforts of other applicants.
*	
*	However, at the end of the exam, you were not laughing: it turned out that in the process of work you lost count, and there were 51 stones in your pile. The relentless examiner meticulously gave you a "failed".
Path48b	You cheerfully began to carry the stones... But, damn it, they were so heavy!.. And to drag them as much as 200 meters... Soon you felt that you were exhausted...
*	
*	On the 39th stone, the forces finally left you. The labor exam failed.
Path49	Go to the second exam
Path50	Hooray!!! Two exams are over!!!
*	Go to the Student ID Ceremony
Path51	Having recognized your yesterday's drinking companion in the examiner, quietly sneak into the laboratory and remind him of yesterday's promise
Path52	Go to the second exam
Path53	Hooray!!! Both exams are over!
*	Go to the Student ID Ceremony
Path54	Try to repeat
Path54b	Slowly and timidly, you tried to reproduce the actions of a chemist:
*	So, we take trepalium dioxide, add radium bicarbonate (or rhodium? Oh, God knows), put it on a spirit lamp... add arsenic and a drop of potassium permanganate... use 99% nitroglycerin as a catalyst... don't forget to shake...
*	
*	                                 BBBBBOOOOOOOOOOMMMM!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
*	
*	The first thought that came to your mind when you finally woke up was surprisingly correct: "Looks like I flunked my chemistry exam..."
Path56	Exams are over!!! HURRAH!!!
*	Go to the Student ID Ceremony
Path57	Go to the second exam
Path58	4
Path59	And that was the last exam! Hooray!!!
*	Go to the Student ID Ceremony
Path60	Wait Professor! Did I understand correctly that we are working in a normed Banach space?
Path61	3
Path62	4
Path65	11
Path65b	"Since the Alcaris has three paws, then their number system must be ternary!" - you guessed it.
*	
*	Your guess was brilliantly confirmed when the Alkaris gave you an "excellent" mark on the examination sheet.
Path66	What numbering system do you use?
Path66b	- Sometimes you can judge the mind better by questions than by answers,” the alkaris said, giving an excellent mark.
Path67	Go to the next exam
Path68	Consult "your" alcaris
Path68b	Asking for time to think, you went to the blackboard and, pretending to be busy with calculations, asked the chick you saved from hooligans: “Listen, do you remember how much 2 + 2 will be? We seem to have passed at school that 4, but I'm not sure..."
*	
*	In response, you heard the following: "We Alkaris have a ternary number system, so the correct answer is 11."
*	
*	It really was the right answer! Anyway, the Alkaris examiner liked him...
Path69	Enter the ring
Path69b	You cheerfully ran into the ring, bowed elegantly to the audience and even managed to get into a fighting stance. And then something hit you on the head - either a blow from a maloq, or just a sudden brain stroke ... It's not clear ...
*	
*	But you understood one thing for sure, waking up three days later in the hospital - you failed to pass the exam in physical education.
Path71	Make a bandage on the hand of a bandage and gauze, simulating a fracture of the hand, and demand that the boxing match be replaced with something else
Path72b	Maloq rushed at you with furious fury, but you managed to restrain his pressure and, having contrived, sent him to a knockdown.
*	
*	"That's what I understand - an athlete!" - respectfully said the trainer, grading you "excellent".
Path73	This is the end of your suffering! Hooray!
*	Go to the Student ID Ceremony
Path74	Go to the second exam
Path75	Fencing
Path75b	Maloq was not only an excellent boxer, but also a good swordsman. What can not be said about you, since for the first time in your life you held in your hands such an archaic weapon as a sword. And what did you think about when choosing this type of martial arts?
*	
*	Be that as it may, for physical education you received "failed".
Path76	Arm wrestling
Path76b	Your cunning has forced the Maloq to compete in a sport he is not familiar with. And yet, his colossal superiority in physical strength had its final say. You failed to beat the trainer and received a "failed" mark for the exam.
Path77b	Your cunning has forced the Maloq to compete in a sport he is not familiar with. This gave you some advantage, which you brilliantly translated into victory. Reluctantly, the trainer was forced to give you an "excellent" mark.
Path78	Take an exam for the professor
Path79	Take an exam for the assistant
Path80	Give the rector his notebook
Path80b	- You know, professor, - you began, - yesterday after your speech, I found this book in the university garden under the podium. Did you accidentally lose it?
*	
*	 -Why did you think it could be me? - inquired the rector.
*	
*	 - I just read the first poem out of curiosity, and then I could not tear myself away, I read and read everything until I read the whole book. And you know what I think? It's just ingeniously! Amazing, amazing lyrics! I haven't read anything better in a long time!
Path81	Go to the next exam
Path82	Your suffering is over! Hooray!!!
*	You can go for a student ID
Path83	Explain that only Maloq poetry was studied at your school
Path83b	"That's what you would have entered the Maloq university ," - said the assistant, with great pleasure putting you "failed".
Path84	Start a discussion on a literary topic
Path84b	Is it with your brains to participate in literary disputes? Peleng simply flooded you with quotes and with a feeling of deep satisfaction gave you "failed".
Path85b	You started a dispute on a literary topic and easily demonstrated the peleng that you know no less long words than he does.
Path86	Continue the literary dispute with the professor
Path86b	It didn't work with the professor. He easily found gaps in your preparation and you got "failed".
Path87b	Your erudition delighted the professor, and he gave you "excellent".
Path88	Accuse the professor's assistant of racism, unreasonable nit-picking and explicit sexual harassment, threaten to make a loud scandal
Path88b	Hearing this, the furious peleng grabbed a volume of Manamanama's poems and threw it right at your head...
*	
*	...When you woke up, the doctor had two pieces of news for you. The good news was that the peleng was expelled from the University in disgrace. And the bad thing is that you, after lying in the hospital with a concussion, did not enter this University.
Path89b	Hearing such accusations, the bearer gritted his teeth with rage, but, seeing your muscular figure and menacingly clenched fists, he did not dare to openly object.
*	
*	In order to avoid a scandal, the rector compromised and gave you an "excellent" mark for the exam.
Path90	Proceed
Path90b	"We don't need such students," the rector concluded.
*	From his firm look, you understood that the decision is final and not subject to appeal.
Path91b	"But I like agile people like you, so I'll probably give you a chance," the rector continued and, to your great amazement, gave you an "excellent" mark on the examination paper!!!
Path92b	"But I like strong people like you, so I'll probably give you a chance," the rector continued and, to your great amazement, gave you an "excellent" mark on the examination paper!!!
Path93b	"But I like smart people like you, so I'll probably give you a chance," the rector continued and, to your great amazement, gave you an "excellent" mark on the examination paper!!!
Path94	Is that all? Can not be! HURRAH!!!
*	Go to the Student ID Ceremony
Path95	Go to the second exam
Path96b	But in vain! You had every chance to enter the University ...
Path97b	But in vain! You had every chance to enter the University ...
Path98b	But in vain! You had every chance to enter the University ...
Path99	These are their problems! And I need to quickly get out of this planet!
Path100	These humanoids need my help!
Path101	No, I have to go to the spaceport
Path101b	But in vain! You had every chance to enter the University ...
Path102b	You have easily completed this task. However, you did not like the vengeful smile of the approaching faeyan at all.
*	
*	- Yesterday I saw you, young man, at the preparatory courses for labor, - he said, - but your name does not appear on the lists of those who paid for these courses. There are no deceivers in our University! I have already reported this incident to the rector, so there is absolutely no need for you to go to other exams...
Path104	Finally go to sleep!
Path105	Get out of here as soon as possible and try something else
Path106	Get out of here as soon as possible and try something else
Path107	Get out of here as soon as possible and try something else
Path108	Get out of here as soon as possible and try something else
Path109	Get out of here as soon as possible and try something else
Path110b	You guessed the correct answer, but were unable to convincingly explain to the alcaris how you got it. Accusing you of cheating, he put you "bad".
Path116	Follow this bureaucratic procedure
