QuestDescription	As you <Ranger> know, we Feyans are a peaceful race, so our warships usually employ mercenaries from other planets. The recruitment system was developed a long time ago. Only people are being recruited, since the Gaals themselves use mercenaries, and the Pelengs and maloks can turn our weapons against us at any second. We usually invite people from the <ToPlanet> planet of the <ToStar> system to our ships. But a nuisance happened - due to the heavy losses among the military in recent years, the prestige of the profession has fallen sharply, and now it is not so easy to recruit recruits. The chief commissioner of the planet <ToPlanet>, however, did an excellent job with this case, but recently he was awarded the Order of the Hunchback with a twist on his back, and he was paralyzed with joy! The call is in jeopardy!!! You must arrive on the <ToPlanet> planet of the <ToStar> system no later than <Date> and help fulfill the summoning plan. We are ready to pay you a premium in <Money> cr for this small service.
QuestSuccessGovMessage	We believed in you, <Ranger>, and you didn't let us down. The new recruits have already arrived to serve on our ships. By the way, by the decision of the Collegium of Commissars, you were awarded the honorary title of Chief Corporal of the planet <ToPlanet>. You can be proud and happy. And, of course, your travel expenses - as agreed, <Money> cr. Thank you so much for helping the galaxy!!!
Par1-1	Mechanics: called <> from [p6]
Par2-1	Signalmen: called up <> from [p7]
Par3-1	Pilots: Drafted <> from [p8]
Par4-1	Navigators: called up <> from [p9]
Par5-1	Gunners: called up <> from [p10]<br>
Par14-1	Left {[p14] mod 24} hours - prepare the report!
Par14-2	Has 1 day left and {[p14] mod 24} hours
Par14-3	Has 2 days left and {[p14] mod 24} hours
Par14-4	Has 3 days left and {[p14] mod 24} hours
Par14-5	Has 4 days left and {[p14] mod 24} hours
Par14-6	5 days left and {[p14] mod 24} hours
Par14-7	6 days left and {[p14] mod 24} hours
Par14-8	7 days left
Par14-crit	- Tell me, how many conscripts have you drafted? Eh?! What are you mumbling about? Are you saying that you have completed the plan? Why wasn't it reported in a timely manner?!! Why? - the old Malok general asked, and you just remained silent in response, realizing that the mission had failed miserably. Goodbye, <Money> cr...
Par23-crit	This pill turned out to be the last straw for your body. Taking a tranquilizer regularly has exhausted you. The toxins that were deposited with each tablet ingested filled your body, and you died without even noticing it.
Par24-1	Subpoenas: <> - order urgently!
Par24-2	Subpoenas: <> - there should be enough for today
Par24-3	Subpoenas: <> - enough for a couple of days
Par24-4	Subpoenas: <> - we will wrap the fat in them
Par25-1	Am I dreaming all this?
Par25-2	Your eyes stick together, you fall asleep
Par25-3	Would be nice to have a rest
Par25-4	Normal condition
Par25-5	Are you feeling cheerful
Par25-6	You are full of energy
Par25-crit	What a shame to fall asleep on the move, fall down and smash your head through the door, which, being torn off its hinges, broke the legs of two conscripts, broke the glass in the vacuum window and crushed the foot of the Private general himself - the head of all military enlistment offices in the galaxy!!!
*	"No, I no longer work in military enlistment offices"- You have firmly decided.
Par26-1	Human rights defenders trust you
Par26-2	Human rights activists suspect you
Par26-3	Human rights defenders don't like you
Par26-4	Human rights activists are rallying under your windows!
Par26-5	Human rights defenders are ready to tear you apart
Par26-crit	"Something is wrong here," you thought, looking at the door of your office, which was crumbling under the blows of the axes of human rights activists. And only when these axes got to your skull did you realize that there is nothing scarier than the wrath of fans of any kind and cut. They don't like grafters and lawbreakers here...
Par27-1	On the account of the military enlistment office <> cr
Par28-1	Your bank account <> cr
Loc1-1	You were greeted very solemnly at the spaceport of the planet - flowers, an orchestra, a carpet path to the very ramp. It immediately alerted you: if you are greeted like this, it means that the draft is most likely bad...
Loc2-1	At the military enlistment office, your fears were confirmed when your deputy for conscription briefly brought you up to date. 
*	
*	- The summoning plan this time is not very big. It is necessary to call {[p6]} mechanics, {[p7]} signalers, {[p8]} pilots, {[p9]} navigators and {[p10]} flight gunners. We have already done some work and drafted several people ({[p1]+[p2]+[p3]+[p4]+[p5]}, to be precise) of different specialties. There are 7 <clrEnd> days left until the end of the draft. There is representative money in the amount of [p17] cr on the account of the military enlistment office. There are still subpoenas - [p24] pcs., but it doesn't hurt to order them - suddenly they will end tomorrow, and then the whole working day will go down the drain. And yet, I have to disappoint you - if you are tired, then you will not have to rest. These 7 days we've all been on tranquilizers and working around the clock without sleeping, eating or watching TV shows! Just don't get carried away with taking medications - use them only in the most urgent cases, otherwise you'll ruin your health.
Loc3-1	The office is quiet, peaceful and, most importantly, cozy. A desk with papers, a laptop, visiphones, a poster "Have you signed up to volunteer?" There are stands all over the wall that say "They disgrace the honor of the Rangers" and, of course, "Our Pride." That's all the furniture in your office. A soft armchair hugs your body, you want to relax and take a break from everything...
*	
*	Okay, stop looking around - it's time to get things done!!!
Loc3-2	In your office, you plopped down in a comfortable chair and closed your eyes. Oh, I wish I had a couple of liters of beer and went to the sauna! However, there is no time to rest - work awaits. You just need to remember why you came here...
Loc3-3	You sat in your chair for a while, puffing out your cheeks and staring intently at the visitor's chair opposite you. It's nice to feel like a big boss after all! However, stop having fun, it's time to get to work.
Loc3-4	You've skimmed through the mail on your desk. It turned out that the usual spam was instructions for conducting parades, advertising a new boot polish cream, reminding the command to be vigilant during recruitment events in order to avoid information leakage through the channels of dominator spies, as well as {[5..20]} letters from human rights defenders demanding that they stop bullying conscripts, remove bureaucratic delays, and strictly adhere to the letter of the law.
*	
*	You irritably threw all the mail into the trash - you have more important things to do!
Loc4-1	The hallway is crowded and bustling as usual, the noise is terrible. All you can hear is: "... I got into Markab...", "... and when they give cigarettes to the gunners, are you tired of shooting strangers?..", "... wow, our navigators are storming..."
*	Doors open and close, letting in and letting out new crowds. 
*	The archive is on the left, the medical board is on the right, music and lively voices can be heard right along the corridor - there is a propaganda team there. Everyone comes up to you every now and then with stupid questions like, "Is it true that all the rangers are kept in cargo holds during the hyperloop?""Where did I end up?", "What time is it?" etc.
Loc4-2	The hallway is bustling as usual. Some new recruit is waving a summons and shouting indignantly that he has already served his time. "To the medical examination, we'll figure it out there!" - the sergeant at the desk speaks habitually. 
*	
*	"That's right, there's nothing to evade the draft! - You thought. "Since the summons has been brought, then I must serve!!!"
Loc4-3	The hallway was pretty sparsely populated this time. Only the sergeant on duty was dragging another unsuccessful deserter to the medical examination. He tried to escape and shouted that he had a white ticket. 
*	
*	"He shouldn't have done that," you thought of the conscript. "Anyway, the sergeant doesn't understand such complicated words..."
*	
*	In general, everything is fine here so far.
Loc4-4	You've just noticed how dreary your hallway looks. The gray-green color of the walls is completely depressing. It would be great to paint different paintings on military themes on the walls! A conscript arrives at the military enlistment office, and plasma tanks are coming at him from all sides, dominator ships and combat robots are flying!!! I would have known right away where he was...
*	
*	"I'll have to remember to pitch this idea to the general!" you thought.
Loc5-1	The medical examiner's office smells of medicines, doctors in white, but already heavily splattered with blood, are scurrying about. Somewhere outside the door, a creature is screaming hysterically on the operating table. Pressed against the wall, there are conscripts of different colors - pale as toadstools, white as chalk, green as Pelengs, blue as a board. Everyone tries to slip through without standing in a huge queue - time, time, time...
*	The doctors all froze when you appeared, as if on command.
*	
*	"Work, work," you said fatherly.
Loc5-2	The usual buzz reigns at the medical board. Snatches of conversation can be heard: "Is it possible to serve on a ship with flat feet?" "Doctor, I have a hernia, can I get a white ticket?" "You want to dodge, you bastard?! And who's going to fight the dominators, am I?!!" 
*	
*	You smiled with satisfaction - the work is in full swing!
Loc5-3	There were long queues for doctors at the medical examination. The doctors did their job slowly - after all, every conscript must be thoroughly examined before being sent to the meat grinder of the fight against dominators! You can't send just anyone to do this, although unspoken instructions and ancient traditions oblige doctors to recruit absolutely everyone. When you arrived, work stopped altogether, as all the doctors stood at attention.
*	
*	- At ease! - you ordered, and the doctors returned to work.
Loc5-4	At the medical examination, everything is as usual - conscripts stand in line and tell jokes, doctors examine patients, study their complexes and reflexes, take tests and make a diagnosis: "Fit!" 
*	
*	Actually, your presence here is not really necessary...
Loc7-1	The propaganda team greeted you as usual with songs and dances, posters like "The enemy will not pass", "Our cause is just, we will win" and "Remember, dominator, the Ice battle!"
*	
*	The head of the propaganda team, a Fei by race, a Peleng in life, greeted you joyfully and reported the situation, gesturing and waving a balalaika. From his words, you only understood that "... f major is in the order of the third octave ... ...what is the fourth position?.. ..plywood or plusovka ... ... watercolors on canvas..."
*	
*	- Everything is very clear, - you interrupted him.
Loc7-2	Everything is as usual in the propaganda team - someone is playing rock'n'roll on a balalaika, someone is drawing a wall newspaper. Everything seems to be working. Feiyanin, the head of the brigade, is waiting for your orders.
Loc7-3	You crept up to one of the rooms unnoticed and listened. From inside, there was a lively argument about how to make a ruff - first beer, then vodka, or vice versa, or at the same time. 
*	
*	- What a mess!!!  You shouted, yanking the door open.
*	
*	- We are discussing the technical details in case of a bar raid! - Feyanin, the head of the propaganda team, wriggled out. - By the way, maybe we should organize a raid, huh? The guys stayed too long...
Loc7-4	There was a working atmosphere in the propaganda team - the musicians were rehearsing a hyper-rock concert, several maloks were trying to march, a couple of Pelengs were composing a commercial, and the head of the brigade, Feyanin, was preparing a lecture on "How do we defeat the dominators".
Loc8-1	Deputy
Loc9-1	It was with great difficulty that you were able to reach the printing company. The head of the printing house V.V. Od, with a face that expressed absolutely nothing, said:
*	
*	- I can't give you many summonses, there are only {[p17]}, they haven't printed any more yet.
Loc10-1	- The called subscriber is in the zone and is temporarily unavailable," you heard in response.
*	- How is it not available? - You were indignant.
*	- Available, available! Always available for you, Commissioner! - the rector of the planetary university of the planet <ToPlanet>, one of the smartest people in the galaxy, Professor Dumbass, appeared. - How is your health, how are you doing at work?
*	- Everything is OK. 
*	- And what happened that you turned to my insignificant person?
Loc11-1-Dear	Commissioner," a middle-aged, imposing-looking man began. - While all progressive humanity is rushing to fight the dominators, some individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where the real aces, potential pilots, are hiding!
*	- Very interesting! - You answered. Of course - what a help to the plan!
*	- And I will gladly hand over these deserters, - the man continued, - but you will have to promise me that the medical board will find my son any health problems incompatible with military service. I don't want him to die in some senseless assault on a captured system!
*	" It's a tempting idea, you thought. - There are few violations, but they are even closer to fulfilling the plan! Should I agree or not?"
Loc11-2	- Dear Commissioner, - a short, middle-aged woman began. - While all progressive humanity is rushing to fight the dominators, some individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where the real aces, potential pilots, are hiding!
*	- Very interesting! - You answered. Of course, what a help to the plan!
*	"And I will gladly hand over these deserters," she continued, "but you will have to promise me that my son will serve on a military base, not on a ship. He usually gets seasick on ships...
*	"It's a tempting idea," you thought. - There are few violations, but they are even closer to fulfilling the plan! Should I agree or not?"
Loc12-1-Dear	Commissioner," began a middle-aged, personable-looking man. - While all progressive humanity is rushing to fight the dominators, some individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where smart and educated people are hiding. These potential <clr>signalmen<clrEnd> only know that they sit and tap all day!
*	- Very interesting! - You answered. Of course, what a help to the plan!
*	"And I will gladly hand over these deserters," the man continued, "but you will have to promise me to hire my son as a mechanic, not a flight gunner. I think he was unfairly disqualified during the test! Just think, I poured gasoline into the radiator...
*	"It's a tempting idea," you thought. - There are few violations, but they are even closer to fulfilling the plan! Should I agree or not?"
Loc12-2	- Dear Commissioner, - a short, middle-aged woman began. - While all progressive humanity is rushing to fight the dominators, some individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where smart and educated people are hiding. These potential <clr>signalmen<clrEnd> only know that they sit and tap all day!
*	- Very interesting! - You answered. Of course, what a help to the plan!
*	"And I will gladly hand over these deserters," she continued, "but you will have to promise me to send my son to the elite units of the construction battalion. It's better than dying in battles with dominators, and at the same time my son will learn a good profession.
*	"It's a tempting idea," you thought. - There are few violations, but they are even closer to fulfilling the plan! Should I agree or not?"
Loc13-1	- Dear Commissioner, - began a middle-aged, personable-looking man. - While all progressive humanity is rushing to fight the dominators, some individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where professional killers, potential <clr>gunmen <clrEnd> are hiding!
*	- Very interesting! - You answered. Of course - what a help to the plan!
*	- And I will gladly hand over these deserters, - the man continued, - but you will have to promise me to make my son a war journalist. Not everyone has to die in battles with dominators, someone has to work hard on the information front, right?!
*	"It's a tempting idea," you thought, "A few violations, but even closer to fulfilling the plan! Should I agree or not?"
Loc13-2	- Dear Commissioner, - a short, middle-aged woman began. - While all progressive humanity is rushing to fight the dominators, some individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where professional killers, potential <clr>gunmen <clrEnd> are hiding!
*	- Very interesting! - You answered. Of course - what a help to the plan!
*	- And I will gladly hand over these deserters, - she continued, - but you will have to promise me to get my son a job at a military factory so that he gets a reservation from the army.
*	"It's a tempting idea," you thought. - There are few violations, but they are even closer to fulfilling the plan! Should I agree or not?"
Loc14-1,	Dear Commissioner, began a middle-aged, imposing-looking man. - While all progressive humanity is rushing to fight the dominators, some individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where smart and educated people who understand maps and potential navigators are hiding!
*	- Very interesting! - You answered. Of course, what a help to the plan!
*	"And I will gladly hand over these deserters," the man continued, "but you will have to promise me not to send my son into space, but to put him as a secretary at headquarters.
*	"It's a tempting idea," you thought. - There are few violations, but they are even closer to fulfilling the plan! Should I agree or not?"
Loc14-2	- Dear Commissioner, - a short, middle-aged woman began. - While all progressive humanity is rushing to fight the dominators, some individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where smart and educated people who understand maps and potential navigators are hiding!
*	- Very interesting! - You answered. Of course, what a help to the plan!
*	And I will gladly hand over these deserters," she continued, "but you will have to promise me to place my son as an aide-de-camp to some general. It would be better to promote his career growth than dangerous service on a warship.
*	"It's a tempting idea," you thought. - There are few violations, but they are even closer to fulfilling the plan! Should I agree or not?"
Loc15-1	-Dear Commissioner," began a middle-aged, personable-looking man. - While all progressive humanity is rushing to fight the dominators, some individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where the real techies are hiding, potential <clr>mechanics <clrEnd>!
*	- Very interesting! - You answered. Of course, what a help to the plan!
*	"And I will gladly hand over these deserters," the man continued, "but you will have to promise me to send my son into space without undergoing a medical examination - he has minor health problems.
*	"It's a tempting idea," you thought. - There are few violations, but they are even closer to fulfilling the plan! Should I agree or not?"
Loc15-2	- Dear Commissioner, - a short, middle-aged woman began. - While all progressive humanity is rushing to fight the dominators, some individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where the real tech experts, potential <clr>mechanics <clrEnd>, are hiding!
*	- Very interesting! - You answered. Of course - what a help to the plan!
*	- And I will gladly hand over these deserters, - she continued, - but you will have to promise me to send my son to serve in the song and dance ensemble! The fact is that my son is an excellent singer and dancer, but for some reason no one but me believes in this...
*	"The idea is tempting," you thought. - There are few violations, but they are even closer to fulfilling the plan! Agree or disagree?"
Loc16-1	Bar Raid
Loc17-1	Advertising
Loc18-1	Concert
Loc19-1	Parade
Loc20-1	Lecture
Loc22-1	- You need to summon at least the planned number of conscripts from each of the five specialties: <clr>mechanics, signalmen, pilots, navigators, and flight gunners<clrEnd>. The plan is as follows: {[p6]} mechanics, {[p7]} signalmen, {[p8]} pilots, {[p9]} navigators and {[p10]} flight gunner. Summonses are needed for conscription, now they are available [p24] pcs., but you can order more. To attract potential recruits, use the <clr>campaign team<clrEnd>. There are also illegal ways to recruit conscripts, but they must be used with caution, because the Committee of Defenders and Midfielders of the Rights of Humans and Other Mammals will constantly monitor all your actions! Don't forget that walls can have ears, too...
Loc22-2	is a strange question! - the deputy was surprised. - The summons is the only document that allows you to turn a free young man into a conscript, summon him for a medical examination and send him further into the open spaces of outer space. Accordingly, one summons is needed for one recruit. The more conscripts are drafted, the fewer subpoenas are left. When the number of subpoenas does not exceed <clr>50<clrEnd> pieces, it is urgently necessary to order them from the printing house (these civilian bureaucrats flatly refuse to send us subpoenas if we have more than 50 pieces!). You can do this directly from your office via a visiphone. However, there is one small caveat: the subpoenas are not spent during some events. For example, during the mass expulsion of students, the university issues summonses to them, and when recruiting on a tip (parents are well-wishers and the services of informers), the police bring deserter recruits in handcuffs directly from shelters to the military enlistment office.
Loc22-3	- There are several ways to get additional recruits, but all of them are either not completely legal or require material costs. I know the following ways.
*	
*	1) It's no secret that the semi-legal "Seventh-day Pacifists" party operates on the planet <ToPlanet>. They carry out anti-war agitation, create shelters where deserters hide. We do our best to combat these manifestations of cowardice: for example, we introduce our <clr>informers <clrEnd> into groups of deserters, who (of course, not gratuitously) provide these shelters. The method is good, effective, and, in general, legal, but it requires certain material costs. 
*	
*	2) <clr> bar raids <clrEnd> work well, although this is not a completely legal way to conduct a draft. The essence of it is that our employees in civilian clothes go through bars, find potential recruits, get them drunk, and while their brains are drugged with some kind of swill, they are forced to sign all the papers. The method is, of course, very effective, but the Committee of Defenders and Midfielders does not approve of it at all. So if there are problems with them, it's better to forget about bar raids. 
*	
*	3) An even more effective method, as illegal as it is costly, is the <clr>recruitment of expelled students<clrEnd>. If you can come to an agreement with the rector of the planetary university of the planet <ToPlanet>, and he expels more of his students, then all of them will transfer to the ranks of our valiant Armed Forces.
Loc22-4	- The essence of the campaign team's work is that it regularly conducts various mass events on your instructions, thereby raising the prestige of military service and attracting new recruits. The system of these events was developed by a group of psychologists, and they are designed to attract people with certain psychophysical parameters. There are the following types of agitation activities.
*	
*	By holding a <clr>parade <clrEnd>, you can count on an increase in the number of <clr>pilots<clrEnd> and <clr>mechanics<clrEnd> (these types of people often come to see the equipment).
*	
*	<clr><clrEnd> advertising attracts <clr>signalmen<clrEnd> and <clr>navigators<clrEnd>, who constantly sit at the visors both before and during the service.
*	
*	By giving <clr>lectures<clrEnd>, you will attract <clr>navigators<clrEnd> and <clr>pilots<clrEnd> (they must be accurate, punctual and literate - in short, the intelligentsia).
*	
*	<clr>hyper-rock concerts<clrEnd> are mostly attended by <clr>mechanics<clrEnd> and <clr>gunmen<clrEnd> (these just like to have fun and scream a lot).
Loc23-1	This time there were no orchestras, no flowers, no carpet at the spaceport. But your ship was in its place, waiting for you to leave the planet <ToPlanet>. Which you immediately did.
*	
*	Your mission has failed.
Loc24-1	Questionnaire
Loc25-1	- Hello, dear <Ranger>, the great commissioner of the planet <ToPlanet>! We, ordinary mortals, always pronounce your name with joy and trepidation! ..
*	- Let's make it short, if possible, - you cut off these grandiose statements.
*	- Of course, of course!!! Sorry! My poor father can't do the housework himself at home, and calling his son into the ranks of the great and invincible warriors who bring light and liberation from the dominator yoke to all races will bring great suffering and pain to our entire family. Could you help me stay at home? And next time, I promise to go conquer space...
*	- And who is your long-suffering father? - You asked.
*	- My father, Mr. Bourgeois, is the owner of factories, newspapers, steamships, casinos, and a pirate gang. We will be very grateful for your assistance, and the amount of <clr>500 cr<clrEnd> will surely please you for such a small service. Well, how's that?
Loc25-2	- Hello, dear <Ranger>, the great commissioner of the planet <ToPlanet>! My poor father won't be able to handle the household if his son is drafted into the army. Could you help me stay at home? I'm not asking for greed, but for the will of the father who sent me...
*	- And who is your long-suffering father? - You asked.
*	- My father is Mr. Bill Gates the Eighteenth - I hope his name speaks for itself. We will be very grateful for your assistance, and the amount of <clr>500 cr<clrEnd> for such a small service will surely please you. Well, how's that?
Loc26-1	- Hello, I am a draftee of Xerox, I work in a printing company, and we value every hour of working time. If you could help me get through the medical examination without waiting in line, I would give you some summonses as a friendly help.
Loc26-2	- Hello, I am a conscript Scanner - I work in a printing company, and we value every hour of working time. If you could help me get through the medical examination without waiting in line, I would give you some summonses as a friendly help.
Loc26-3	- Hello, I am conscript M.S.Ward - I work in a printing company, and we value every hour of working time. If you could help me get through the medical examination without waiting in line, I would give you some summonses as a friendly help.
Loc27-1	Passed the {7th-([p14] div 24)}th day of conscription. Your deputy has put a report on your desk.
*	
*	Over the past day, {[p18]+[p19]+[p20]+[p21]+[p22]} people have been called up, here is the general information about the draft:
*	
*	<fix>
*	<format=left,16></format>The plan For The day Is Everything Left
*	<format=left,15>Mechanics -</format>   <format=left,3>[p6]</format>      <format=left,3>[p18]</format>          <format=left,3>[p1]</format>        <format=left,3>[p37]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Signalmen -</format>   <format=left,3>[p7]</format>      <format=left,3>[p22]</format>          <format=left,3>[p2]</format>        <format=left,3>[p38]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Pilots -</format>   <format=left,3>[p8]</format>      <format=left,3>[p19]</format>          <format=left,3>[p3]</format>        <format=left,3>[p39]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Navigators -</format>   <format=left,3>[p9]</format>      <format=left,3>[p20]</format>          <format=left,3>[p4]</format>        <format=left,3>[p40]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Side Shooters -</format>   <format=left,3>[p10]</format>      <format=left,3>[p21]</format>          <format=left,3>[p5]</format>        <format=left,3>[p41]</format>
*	</fix>
*	
*	Today is <clr> the last<clrEnd> day of conscription! Start preparing the report.
Loc27-2	Passed the {7-([p14] div 24)}th day of conscription. Your deputy has put a report on your desk.
*	
*	Over the past day, {[p18]+[p19]+[p20]+[p21]+[p22]} people have been called up, here is the general information about the draft:
*	
*	<fix>
*	<format=left,16></format>The plan For The day Is Everything Left
*	<format=left,15>Mechanics -</format>   <format=left,3>[p6]</format>      <format=left,3>[p18]</format>          <format=left,3>[p1]</format>        <format=left,3>[p37]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Signalmen -</format>   <format=left,3>[p7]</format>      <format=left,3>[p22]</format>          <format=left,3>[p2]</format>        <format=left,3>[p38]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Pilots -</format>   <format=left,3>[p8]</format>      <format=left,3>[p19]</format>          <format=left,3>[p3]</format>        <format=left,3>[p39]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Navigators -</format>   <format=left,3>[p9]</format>      <format=left,3>[p20]</format>          <format=left,3>[p4]</format>        <format=left,3>[p40]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Side Shooters -</format>   <format=left,3>[p10]</format>      <format=left,3>[p21]</format>          <format=left,3>[p5]</format>        <format=left,3>[p41]</format>
*	</fix>
*	
*	The draft is still {[p14] div 24} days away. With renewed vigor on a new day!
Loc27-3	Passed the {7-([p14] div 24)}th day of conscription. Your deputy has put a report on your desk.
*	
*	Over the past day, {[p18]+[p19]+[p20]+[p21]+[p22]} people have been called up, here is the general information about the draft:
*	
*	<fix>
*	<format=left,16></format>The plan For The day Is Everything Left
*	<format=left,15>Mechanics -</format>   <format=left,3>[p6]</format>      <format=left,3>[p18]</format>          <format=left,3>[p1]</format>        <format=left,3>[p37]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Signalmen -</format>   <format=left,3>[p7]</format>      <format=left,3>[p22]</format>          <format=left,3>[p2]</format>        <format=left,3>[p38]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Pilots -</format>   <format=left,3>[p8]</format>      <format=left,3>[p19]</format>          <format=left,3>[p3]</format>        <format=left,3>[p39]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Navigators -</format>   <format=left,3>[p9]</format>      <format=left,3>[p20]</format>          <format=left,3>[p4]</format>        <format=left,3>[p40]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Side Shooters -</format>   <format=left,3>[p10]</format>      <format=left,3>[p21]</format>          <format=left,3>[p5]</format>        <format=left,3>[p41]</format>
*	</fix>
*	
*	The draft is still {[p14] div 24} days away. There's still plenty of time!
Loc28-1	Tranquilizer intake
Loc29-1	The commander had a huge office with a long desk. The giant malok sat majestically in an armchair as huge as himself.
*	- General, draft... - You started timidly.
*	"There is no need to report the obvious," he interrupted you. - I know everything perfectly well. <clr>The call was conducted brilliantly<clrEnd>, this has not happened on the planet <ToPlanet> for many years. It was a real 7 days that shocked me, and therefore the whole world! Thank you so much from the government and from me personally. You've done a great job. Vivat! Your reward in the amount of <Money> cr is waiting for you on the planet <ToPlanet>, and for my part, I want to present you with {[p36]} cr - everything that remains in the account of the military enlistment office!
Loc31-1	Bribe to the committee
Loc32-1	intermediate
Loc33-1	- Interesting, interesting. And what kind of business is this? - said the Dumbass.
*	"Maybe we should offer him a bribe - let him expel more of his students, maybe we'll fulfill the plan," you thought.
Loc33-2	- Interesting, interesting. And what kind of business is this? Are you trying to sell me a bribe again? - said the Dumbass.
*	"Maybe we should really offer him a bribe - let him expel more of his students, maybe we'll fulfill the plan," you thought.
Loc34-1	Bribe
Loc35-1	- And why not. Our scientists' salaries are small, and your financial help may be very useful. So how much will you pay me for this small but gross violation of our laws? Keep in mind that the risk is not small, so the more you pay, the more students I will expel and send to you," the Dumbass switched to a whisper.
Loc36-1	- Okay, remember my kindness, - V.V. Od suddenly became kind, - just for you, out of old friendship, I will allocate a few subpoenas from my "NZ". I have some {[p17]} pieces somewhere. So here you go.
Loc37-1	Bribe
Loc38-1	- And how can we come to an agreement? - an expression of extreme interest in the events appeared on the face of V.V.Oda.
Loc39-1	25
Loc40-1	50
Loc41-1	100
Loc42-1	- And how much money can I expect? - V.V. Oda's interest has gone beyond all imaginable limits.
Loc44-1	- Money transfer using the West-Uni system is the most versatile and reliable way to receive money!!! - the voice of the advertising robot came from the visiophone. - Even if you just want to transfer money from one pocket to another, the safest way to do this is using the West-Uni system!!! The transfer rates are as follows:
*	
*	- <clr>up to 300<clrEnd> cr - deducted <clr>5%<clrEnd>;
*	- <clr>300-900<clrEnd> cr - removed <clr>3%<clrEnd>;
*	- <clr>over 900<clrEnd> cr - deducted <clr>2%<clrEnd>.
*	
*	How much should I transfer?
Loc46-1	You took out the money, called the head of the propaganda team and told him:
*	
*	- Work with informants.
*	
*	"No problem," he replied, "do you have any additional instructions?"
Loc47-1	The work of informers
Loc48-1	You called the head of the propaganda team and told him:
*	
*	- Work with informants.
*	
*	"I'm sorry," said the head of the campaign team, "this service is paid, it costs <clr>at least 200<clrEnd> cr, and you can't afford it. Try it some other time when you have more money.
Loc49-1	Is the {7th-([p14] div 24)}th day of conscription. Today {[p18]+[p19]+[p20]+[p21]+[p22]} people are called up, here is the general information:
*	
*	<fix>
*	<format=left,16></format>The plan For The day Is Everything Left
*	<format=left,15>Mechanics -</format>   <format=left,3>[p6]</format>      <format=left,3>[p18]</format>          <format=left,3>[p1]</format>        <format=left,3>[p37]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Signalmen -</format>   <format=left,3>[p7]</format>      <format=left,3>[p22]</format>          <format=left,3>[p2]</format>        <format=left,3>[p38]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Pilots -</format>   <format=left,3>[p8]</format>      <format=left,3>[p19]</format>          <format=left,3>[p3]</format>        <format=left,3>[p39]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Navigators -</format>   <format=left,3>[p9]</format>      <format=left,3>[p20]</format>          <format=left,3>[p4]</format>        <format=left,3>[p40]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Side Shooters -</format>   <format=left,3>[p10]</format>      <format=left,3>[p21]</format>          <format=left,3>[p5]</format>        <format=left,3>[p41]</format>
*	</fix>
*	
*	The <clr> penultimate<clrEnd> day of conscription is coming!
Loc49-2	Is the {7th-([p14] div 24)}th day of conscription. Today {[p18]+[p19]+[p20]+[p21]+[p22]} people are called up, here is the general information:
*	
*	<fix>
*	<format=left,16></format>The plan For The day Is Everything Left
*	<format=left,15>Mechanics -</format>   <format=left,3>[p6]</format>      <format=left,3>[p18]</format>          <format=left,3>[p1]</format>        <format=left,3>[p37]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Signalmen -</format>   <format=left,3>[p7]</format>      <format=left,3>[p22]</format>          <format=left,3>[p2]</format>        <format=left,3>[p38]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Pilots -</format>   <format=left,3>[p8]</format>      <format=left,3>[p19]</format>          <format=left,3>[p3]</format>        <format=left,3>[p39]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Navigators -</format>   <format=left,3>[p9]</format>      <format=left,3>[p20]</format>          <format=left,3>[p4]</format>        <format=left,3>[p40]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Side Shooters -</format>   <format=left,3>[p10]</format>      <format=left,3>[p21]</format>          <format=left,3>[p5]</format>        <format=left,3>[p41]</format>
*	</fix>
*	
*	The draft is still {[p14] div 24} days away.
Loc49-3	Is the {7th-([p14] div 24)}th day of conscription. Today {[p18]+[p19]+[p20]+[p21]+[p22]} people are called up, here is the general information:
*	
*	<fix>
*	<format=left,16></format>The plan For The day Is Everything Left
*	<format=left,15>Mechanics -</format>   <format=left,3>[p6]</format>      <format=left,3>[p18]</format>          <format=left,3>[p1]</format>        <format=left,3>[p37]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Signalmen -</format>   <format=left,3>[p7]</format>      <format=left,3>[p22]</format>          <format=left,3>[p2]</format>        <format=left,3>[p38]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Pilots -</format>   <format=left,3>[p8]</format>      <format=left,3>[p19]</format>          <format=left,3>[p3]</format>        <format=left,3>[p39]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Navigators -</format>   <format=left,3>[p9]</format>      <format=left,3>[p20]</format>          <format=left,3>[p4]</format>        <format=left,3>[p40]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Side Shooters -</format>   <format=left,3>[p10]</format>      <format=left,3>[p21]</format>          <format=left,3>[p5]</format>        <format=left,3>[p41]</format>
*	</fix>
*	
*	The draft is still {[p14] div 24} days away.
Loc49-4	Is the {7th-([p14] div 24)}th day of conscription. Today {[p18]+[p19]+[p20]+[p21]+[p22]} people are called up, here is the general information:
*	
*	<fix>
*	<format=left,16></format>The plan For The day Is Everything Left
*	<format=left,15>Mechanics -</format>   <format=left,3>[p6]</format>      <format=left,3>[p18]</format>          <format=left,3>[p1]</format>        <format=left,3>[p37]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Signalmen -</format>   <format=left,3>[p7]</format>      <format=left,3>[p22]</format>          <format=left,3>[p2]</format>        <format=left,3>[p38]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Pilots -</format>   <format=left,3>[p8]</format>      <format=left,3>[p19]</format>          <format=left,3>[p3]</format>        <format=left,3>[p39]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Navigators -</format>   <format=left,3>[p9]</format>      <format=left,3>[p20]</format>          <format=left,3>[p4]</format>        <format=left,3>[p40]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Side Shooters -</format>   <format=left,3>[p10]</format>      <format=left,3>[p21]</format>          <format=left,3>[p5]</format>        <format=left,3>[p41]</format>
*	</fix>
*	
*	Today is <clr> the last<clrEnd> day of conscription! It's time to prepare a report.
Path2	I can't work in such inhumane conditions!!! Home, home, home...
Path3	Go to the military enlistment office
Path4	Ask about the summoning in more detail
Path5	Get to work
Path6	To the corridor
Path7	To the campaign team
Path8	For a medical examination
Path9	To the Deputy
Path9b	- They were just looking for you from a medical examination. Or from the campaign team, I don't remember exactly...
Path11	To talk to the parents of the conscript
Path16	Bar Raid
Path17	Launch Ads
Path18	Arrange a hyper-rock concert
Path19	Hold a parade
Path20	Give a lecture
Path22	Talk to the recruit who came up
Path23	Talk to the incoming Recruit
Path24	Okay, I'm going to my office, and you keep working!
Path25	Remind me again of these summoning rules.
Path26	Okay, I'm going to my office, and you keep working!
Path30	No bribes, queue up, you sons of bitches
Path31	Give me a subpoena and I'll help you
Path32	will be happy to help you.
Path33	will be happy to help you.
Path34	Will be happy to help you.
Path35	will be happy to help you.
Path36	Will be happy to help you.
Path40	To the office
Path42	I don't take a bribe - I'm offended by the Power
Path43	Yes, for that kind of money, I'm ready to fly into space for you.
Path44	I do not intend to violate laws. We are able to carry out the plan ourselves.
Path45	I do not intend to violate laws. We are able to carry out the plan ourselves.
Path46	I do not intend to violate any laws. We are able to carry out the plan ourselves.
Path47	I do not intend to violate laws. We are able to carry out the plan ourselves.
Path48	I do not intend to violate laws. We are able to carry out the plan ourselves.
Path50	To the Deputy
Path50b	- Come on in, come on in. Sit down. Do you want coffee or tea? Or maybe 50 grams each?
Path51	Take a tranquilizer
Path51b	You have taken two tablets, one blue and one red, from the safe of special medicines. "If you take the blue pill, you will wake up in your bed and believe that it was a dream; if you take the red pill, you will enter reality, and I will show you if the rabbit hole is deep," you recalled the instructions of the senior doctor of the medical board, Dr. Morf, swallowing the red pill.
Path56	Order Subpoenas
Path57	Call the Rector of the Planetary University of the planet <ToPlanet>
Path58	To the office
Path61b	At the meeting, you delivered an impassioned speech:
*	
*	- At a time when spaceships are plowing... In short, the plan is in danger of being disrupted, we will have to take emergency measures - tonight we are conducting raids on bars!
*	
*	Holding such a grandiose event, of course, began to produce good results. Especially since the bars were full of customers that day. But human rights activists were unhappy with your actions, and there weren't enough subpoenas...
Path63b	- And who is the smartest and most well-read here? - you asked Feiyanin, the head of the propaganda team.
*	"I am," he replied.
*	- Then you will have the flag in your mighty Feiyan hands! It is urgently necessary to read a series of lectures!
*	
*	Said and done. The lectures on "Everything to fight the dominator invaders" gave a good result.
Path64b	- Participants of the parade, come to attention! Equality on the right! - you practiced in front of the mirror. - Managing troops is my element, and a parade is the best way to prove myself.
*	
*	A huge crowd of people gathered at the parade, all cheering the brave liberating soldiers. There were infantry and vehicles. The audience shouted "Hurrah!" and other militant slogans.
*	
*	Holding the parade would have brought positive results <clr>if there had been subpoenas<clrEnd>.
Path65b	- Come on, sing "The moon is shining, the moon is clear..." in the orange of the bass guitar or this one from the classics - "Nescafe..." - you stopped the first agitator. — great. To a concert with a solo program.
*	
*	"Stop," you stopped the second one, who was trying to slip through the door behind you. - Come on, dance a lezginka in the style of heavy metal... Great - for a backup dance.
*	
*	There is nothing easier than to organize a concert with the help of a propaganda team. And the results are instant, like in a lottery.
Path66b	- Launch ads!  You shouted in your commanding voice.
*	
*	And the car started to spin - the agitators immediately contacted all the media representatives, ordered commercials and brochures, and launched them on the air. The results were not long in coming, and the recruits poured into the military enlistment office.
Path67	Transfer 100 cr to the Committee of Defenders and Midfielders fund
Path67b	Representatives of the Committee of Defenders and Midfielders were very grateful and even shed tears.
Path70	What does the campaign team do?
Path72	What are additional ways to attract recruits?
Path73	Why do we need subpoenas?
Path74b	- Sorry, I have lunch. If it's not difficult, speak up quickly.
Path75b	- I think you visit me a lot. No, no, don't think anything wrong!!! I am always glad to see you!
Path76b	- I wish you good health, O great commissioner of the planet <ToPlanet>, Ranger <Ranger>. Our military enlistment office is thriving under your leadership. I'm extremely busy right now, but I'll take a break for you and provide all-round help and support.
Path77b	- How nice of you to come in. Such a pleasant companion does not visit these walls every day!!!
Path78b	- Have a seat, my dear! And all of you get out of the office! Commissioner Ranger himself wants to talk to me!
Path79b	- They were just looking for you from the medical examination. Or from the campaign team - I don't remember exactly...
Path80b	- I wish you good health, Commissioner <Ranger>. What can I do for you? - your deputy asked.
Path81b	- Are you on business or just to chat? I'm always glad! - The deputy was glad to see you, that's obvious.
Path82b	- I heard that human rights activists have filed a complaint against you for incorrect work in the Book of Fitness Chords," your deputy expressed surprise on his face. "What impudence on their part!
Path83b	- How's it going? Are you ready to submit the report? I see that a lot of work has been done! - the deputy smiled good-naturedly at you. - Is the plan almost completed? May I congratulate you?
Path84b	- Don't get so upset about the little things. Well, the plan didn't go well. It happens. I remember I was in '91..." your deputy was ranting, but you were listening to him with half an ear.
Path85b	- Come in quickly, the news is just starting, - the deputy invited you.
Path86	I didn't get it right, repeat from the beginning!
Path87	Response to the report
Path88	On the report
Path89	On the report
Path90	Response to the report
Path91	Response to the report
Path104	Okay, let's do at least that much
Path105	In the hallway
Path108b	At the meeting, you delivered an impassioned speech:
*	
*	- At a time when spaceships are plowing... In short, the plan is in danger of being disrupted, we will have to take emergency measures - tonight we are conducting raids on bars!
*	
*	The bars were crowded, but you wasted your time and came to the attention of human rights activists - what kind of conscripts can there be without subpoenas?
Path109	Into the hallway
Path112b	- Run ads!  You shouted in your commanding voice.
*	
*	And the car started to spin - the agitators immediately contacted all the media representatives, ordered commercials and brochures, and launched them on the air. Unfortunately, you did not achieve any result with this - the lack of subpoenas <clr> affected you.
Path113b	- Come on, sing "The moon is shining, the moon is clear..." in the orange of the bass guitar or this one from the classics - "Nescafe..." - you stopped the first agitator, - Great. To a concert with a solo program.
*	
*	"Wait," you stopped the second one, who was trying to slip through the door behind you, "Dance a heavy metal lezginka.".. Great - for a backup dance.
*	
*	There is nothing easier than to organize a concert with the help of a propaganda team. But there was no return from this - <clr>there are no subpoenas<clrEnd>, and there is no result!
Path114b	- Participants of the parade, come to attention! Equality on the right! - you practiced in front of the mirror. - Managing troops is my element, and a parade is the best way to prove myself.
*	
*	A huge crowd of people gathered at the parade, all cheering the brave liberating soldiers. There were infantry and vehicles. The audience shouted "Hurrah!" and other militant slogans.
*	
*	The parade brought positive results - conscripts began arriving at the military enlistment office again. But you practically didn't have any subpoenas to serve them...
Path115b	- And who's the smartest and most well-read here? - you asked Feiyanin, the head of the propaganda team.
*	"I am," he replied.
*	- Then you will have the flag in your mighty Feiyan hands! It is urgently necessary to read a series of lectures!
*	
*	Said and done. Unfortunately, the lectures on "Everything to fight the dominator invaders" brought absolutely no result due to the lack of agendas.
Path116	Just wanted to pay a courtesy call. Good luck
Path117	Has a case
Path118	Politely say goodbye and disconnect
Path119	Offer a bribe
Path121b	- What kind of bribe can there be with pennies in your account?!! While. Come back when you're rich! Ha ha ha!
Path122b	- How dare you?  Professor Dumbass shouted. - I have never accepted bribes and I am not going to be taken into account by our fair Committee of Defenders and Midfielders!!!
Path123	To my great regret, there are little difficulties with money right now. But I sincerely hope for our further mutually beneficial cooperation.
Path124	Offer 500 cr
Path124b	- For that kind of money, I'll try to come up with something unusual... - The rector muttered. - Oh, I've thought of it! It's time to fight for cleanliness and hygiene! Today, anyone who comes to the university without a change of shoes will be expelled!
*	
*	The rector's draconian measure produced stunning results - by evening, [p11] mechanics, [p12] signalmen, [p13] pilots, [p15] navigators and [p16] flight gunners were brought from the university!
*	
*	"I hope that you will be satisfied with such a large number of recruits," Professor Tupitsa told you that evening, counting the money.
Path125	Offer 250 cr
Path125b	- I'm going to hold a colloquium on medieval Gaelic philosophy today! - the rector decided. - I think this will send a lot of lazy and sloppy people to the army!
*	
*	It seems that the rector's colloquium turned out to be very difficult, as by the evening [p11] mechanics, [p12] signalmen, [p13] pilots, [p15] navigators and [p16] flight gunners were brought from the university. 
*	
*	"I hope that you will be satisfied with such a large number of recruits," Professor Tupitsa told you that evening, counting the money.
Path126	Offer 100 cr
Path126b	- I'm going to conduct an unscheduled control on the mechanics of protective fields! - The rector decided. - It's not the most difficult discipline, of course, but everyone who fails it will join the ranks of the armed forces!
*	
*	The professor kept his word - by evening, [p11] mechanics, [p12] signalmen, [p13] pilots, [p15] navigators and [p16] flight gunners were brought from the university. 
*	
*	"I hope that you will be satisfied with such a large number of recruits," Professor Tupitsa told you that evening, counting the money.
Path127	How not? Take a closer look at the warehouse!
Path127b	- What does "look at the warehouse" mean? I don't even have a warehouse," replied V.V. Od. "I told you in human language: THERE are NO MORE SUBPOENAS!!! And if you have hearing problems, contact the doctors of your medical board - they will clear your ears!
*	
*	Oh, these civilians - they only know how to swear and make a mess!
Path129	Thank you, you are a true friend
Path130	Okay, print it for now. I'll come back later
Path131	Can we somehow come to an agreement?
Path132	Maybe we can somehow come to an agreement and you can send more subpoenas?
Path133b	- I told you there are no more subpoenas!!! - V.V.Od was starting to rage. - Go mind your own business and don't bother me with mine!!!
Path134b	- What are you doing? You don't get it right once? How many times do I have to tell you that there are no subpoenas!!! Noooo!!! - V.V. Oda's unwillingness to have a further conversation with you was obvious.
Path135	Has already been agreed. Bye
Path141b	- Okay, I've persuaded you, - smiled V.V.Aude, - for <clr>25<clrEnd> cr, I'll give you a dozen or two subpoenas. Don't think that I'm taking bribes, let's assume that you just bought these subpoenas from me! 
*	
*	Pay <clr>25<clrEnd> cr for {[p17]} pcs. - a successful deal!
Path142b	V.V.Od literally flew into a rage after your suggestion.
*	"Are you trying to bribe me?!" I don't give a damn about your money!!! I can give you twice as much myself, just not to see your face here ever again!!!
Path143	I can offer you a small monetary reward for your contribution to the common cause, if you help with subpoenas
Path145	However, I've changed my mind. Bye
Path146	Offer <clr>25<clrEnd> cr
Path147	Offer <clr>100<clrEnd> cr
Path148	Offer <clr>50<clrEnd> cr
Path149b	V.V.Od literally flew into a rage after your suggestion.
*	"Are you trying to bribe me?!" I don't give a damn about your money!!! I can give you twice as much myself, just not to see your face here ever again!!!
Path150b	- Okay, I persuaded you, - smiled V.V.Aude, - for <clr>50<clrEnd> cr, I will give you some subpoenas from my secret stocks. I even hide this stash from my wife, but I have no secrets from you. Don't think that I'm taking bribes, let's assume that you just bought these subpoenas from me. 
*	
*	Pay <clr>50<clrEnd> cr for {[p17]} pcs. - a successful deal!
Path151b	V.V.Od literally flew into a rage after your suggestion.
*	"Are you trying to bribe me?!" I don't give a damn about your money!!! I can give you twice as much myself, just not to see your face here ever again!!!
Path152b	- Okay, I persuaded you, - smiled V.V.Aude, - for <clr>100<clrEnd> cr, I will give you a lot of subpoenas. I'll go over everything and provide you with subpoenas for a couple of days. Don't think that I'm taking bribes, let's assume that you just bought these subpoenas from me. 
*	
*	Pay <clr>100<clrEnd> cr for {[p17]} pcs. - a very good deal!
Path154	I think I've got the wrong door! (exit into the corridor)
Path162	Transfer money from your account to the account of the military enlistment office
Path164	Transfer 100 cr
Path164b	The transfer has been received. The percentage withdrawn by West-Uni is <clr>5<clrEnd> cr.
Path165	Transfer 250 cr
Path165b	The transfer has been received. The percentage withdrawn by West-Uni is <clr>13<clrEnd> cr.
Path166	Transfer 500 cr
Path166b	The transfer has been received. The percentage withdrawn by West-Uni is <clr>15<clrEnd> cr.
Path167	Transfer 1000 cr
Path167b	The transfer has been received. The percentage withdrawn by West-Uni is <clr>20<clrEnd> cr.
Path168	Transfer 2500 cr
Path168b	The transfer has been received. The percentage withdrawn by West-Uni is <clr>50<clrEnd> cr.
Path171	Use the services of informers
Path174	Search for everyone (200 cr)
Path175	Search hard for <clr>mechanics<clrEnd> (250 cr)
Path176	Search hard for <clr>signalmen<clrEnd> (250 cr)
Path177	Hard to search for <clr>pilots<clrEnd> (250 cr)
Path178	Search hard for <clr>navigators<clrEnd> (250 cr)
Path179	However, set aside the search for now
Path180	Hard to search for <clr>gunners<clrEnd> (250 cr)
Path181	Set aside Translation
Path183	Next
Path185b	- And who is the smartest and most well-read here? - you asked Feiyanin, the head of the propaganda team.
*	"I am," he replied.
*	- Then you will have the flag in your mighty Feiyan hands! It is urgently necessary to read a series of lectures!
*	
*	Said and done. The lectures on "Everything to fight the dominator invaders" gave a good result. But it would be even better if you didn't have a terrible shortage of subpoenas.
Path186b	- And who is the smartest and most well-read here? - you asked Feiyanin, the head of the propaganda team.
*	"I am," he replied.
*	- Then you will have the flag in your mighty Feiyan hands! It is urgently necessary to read a series of lectures!
*	
*	Said and done. The lectures on "Everything to fight the dominator invaders" gave a good result. But it would be even better if you didn't have a shortage of subpoenas.
Path187b	- Come on, sing "The moon is shining, the moon is clear..." in the orange of the bass guitar or this one from the classics - "Nescafe..." - you stopped the first agitator you came across. — great. To a concert with a solo program.
*	
*	"Stop," you stopped the second one, who was trying to slip through the door behind you. - Come on, dance a lezginka in the style of heavy metal... Great - for a backup dance.
*	
*	There is nothing easier than to organize a concert with the help of a propaganda team. And the results are instant, like in a lottery. It's just a pity that the subpoenas are running out, otherwise the results would have been even better...
Path188b	- Come on, sing "The moon is shining, the moon is clear..." in the orange of the bass guitar or this one from the classics - "Nescafe..." - you stopped the first agitator. — great. To a concert with a solo program.
*	
*	"Stop," you stopped the second one, who was trying to slip through the door behind you. - Come on, dance a lezginka in the style of heavy metal... Great - for a backup dance.
*	
*	There is nothing easier than to organize a concert with the help of a propaganda team. And the results are instant, like in a lottery. It's just a pity that there are almost no subpoenas left, otherwise the results would have been even better...
Path189b	- Participants of the parade, come to attention! Equality on the right! - you trained in front of a mirror, - Managing troops is my element, and a parade is the best way to prove yourself.
*	
*	A huge crowd of people gathered at the parade, all cheering the brave liberating soldiers. There were infantry and vehicles. The audience shouted "Hurrah!" and other militant slogans.
*	
*	The parade brought positive results - conscripts began arriving at the military enlistment office again.
Path190b	- Participants of the parade, come to attention! Equality on the right! - you trained in front of a mirror, - Managing troops is my element, and a parade is the best way to prove yourself.
*	
*	A huge crowd of people gathered at the parade, all cheering the brave liberating soldiers. There were infantry and vehicles. The audience shouted "Hurrah!" and other militant slogans.
*	
*	The parade brought positive results - conscripts began arriving at the military enlistment office again. But you didn't have a lot of subpoenas to serve them...
Path191b	At the meeting you made a fiery speech:
*	
*	- At a time when spaceships are sailing... In short, the plan is in danger of being disrupted, we will have to take emergency measures - tonight we are conducting raids on bars!
*	
*	Holding such a grandiose event, of course, began to produce good results. Especially since the bars were full of customers that day. But human rights activists were unhappy with your actions...
Path192b	At the meeting you made a fiery speech:
*	
*	- At a time when spaceships are plowing... In short, the plan is in danger of being disrupted, we will have to take emergency measures - tonight we are conducting raids on bars!
*	
*	Holding such a grandiose event, of course, began to produce good results. Especially since the bars were full of customers that day. But human rights activists were unhappy with your actions, and there were very few subpoenas...
Path193b	- Launch ads!  You shouted in your commanding voice.
*	
*	And the car started to spin - the agitators immediately contacted all the media representatives, ordered commercials and brochures, and launched them on the air. The results were not long in coming, and the recruits poured into the military enlistment office. There weren't even enough subpoenas to register everyone...
Path194b	- Launch ads!  You shouted in your commanding voice.
*	
*	And the car started to spin - the agitators immediately contacted all the media representatives, ordered commercials and brochures, and launched them on the air. The results were not long in coming, and the recruits poured into the military enlistment office. But there weren't enough subpoenas to register everyone...
Path195	Tell me about the progress of the draft!
Path196	To the office
Path197	In the hallway
Path198	In the hallway
