QuestDescription	Dear <Ranger>! As you probably know, Chief Lyakusha of the planet <FromPlanet> is also the owner of the largest casino in our system. He is rightly proud that his casino has the most varied selection of gambling games, slot machines and other entertainments in the Galaxy, which allow a customer to part with his money quickly.
*	
*	Recently a fellow named Glydl from the planet <ToPlanet> (<ToStar>) invented a new, unusual game. Need I say that Chief Lyakusha wants it to adorn the assortment of games in his casino? But there is one snag: this Glydl agrees to sell the rights to his game only to someone who can beat him at it. We have already sent several players to him, but all in vain - Glydl plays damn well. If you agree to try your luck, we will give you a copyright transfer contract drawn up by our lawyers. If you can beat Glydl, he will, as he promised, put his signature on it. Bring the signed contract here by <Date> (that day is the birthday of one of Chief Lyakusha's sons, so the presentation of a new game would come in very handy), and a bonus of <Money> cr will adorn your bank account.
*	
*	Oh, and one more thing: Glydl will not play with anyone who does not have <clr>1000<clrEnd> cr on them. So make sure you have it. What? No, we give no advances, but then all the money you win from Glydl will be yours.
QuestSuccessGovMessage	Magnificent, <Ranger>! To beat Glydl himself, the author of the game, at Klugg - that is something! Chief Lyakusha is pleased to hand you this check for <Money> cr, and hopes that you will never visit his casino, ha-ha-ha! Our Chief Lyakusha has an excellent sense of humor, doesn't he?
Par1-1	[p2] minutes have passed
Par1-2	<clr>1<clrEnd> hour [p2] minutes have passed
Par1-3	<clr>2<clrEnd> hours [p2] minutes have passed
Par1-4	<clr>3<clrEnd> hours [p2] minutes have passed
Par1-5	<clr>4<clrEnd> hours [p2] minutes have passed
Par1-6	<> hours [p2] minutes have passed
Par3-1	You have <> cr
Par4-1	Current balance: {[p3]-[p4]} cr
Par5-1	Glydl has <> cr
Par6-1	Pot: <> cr
Par7-1	You have "<clr>nothing<clrEnd>"
Par7-2	You have a "<clr>sucker<clrEnd>"
Par7-3	You have a "<clr>derquack<clrEnd>"
Par7-4	You have a "<clr>longnosed crester<clrEnd>"
Par7-5	You have a "<clr>human<clrEnd>"
Par8-1	Glydl has "<clr>nothing<clrEnd>"
Par8-2	Glydl has a "<clr>sucker<clrEnd>"
Par8-3	Glydl has a "<clr>derquack<clrEnd>"
Par8-4	Glydl has a "<clr>longnosed crester<clrEnd>"
Par8-5	Glydl has a "<clr>human<clrEnd>"
Par11-1	Bet: <>
Par12-1	Deleted
Loc1-1	At the embassy of the planet <FromPlanet> on <ToPlanet> you were quickly told where Glydl could be found. Chief Lyakusha of the planet <FromPlanet> must have specially instructed his employees about it. Soon you were sitting in one of the local night bars, waiting for Glydl, who was supposed to appear at exactly midnight. Your watch showed 23.58.
*	
*	- Allow me to introduce myself, - a voice came from somewhere below. - My name is Glydl.
*	
*	Lowering your eyes, you saw a short man with hair smeared with some kind of oil. He was showing you his teeth, which among humans meant friendly intentions.
*	
*	- Another copyright hunter wants to beat me at Klugg? - Glydl asked, looking up at you and continuing to display his teeth. - If you have at least <clr>1000<clrEnd> cr, I will be glad to play with you.
Loc2-1	- Let's place bets. To begin with, <clr>50<clrEnd> cr each, - Glydl said. - Then we'll raise them.
Loc2-2	- I must remind you, - Glydl said, - that we do not play on credit. So if you have no money, then all the best and goodbye.
Loc2-3	- So, let's place the starting bets, - Glydl said. - <clr>50<clrEnd> cr from each. If there isn't enough money, we'll have to end the game.
Loc2-4	- Would you like something to drink? Top-grade beer! - a pleasant voice came from over your ear. Turning your head, you saw one of the local wheeled servodroids. - Made from the best malt and top-quality hops. - The servodroid put two glasses of water on the table and tossed down beside them several multicolored packets with numbers.
*	- I'll take a number three, I think, the "Classic," - Glydl said, pouring into his glass the contents of a blue packet with white stripes. - And which do you prefer? My treat.
*	- I prefer to place bets, - you answered. - After all, are we playing Klugg here, or what?
*	- Of course, of course, - Glydl said. - Let's place bets. <clr>50<clrEnd> cr each. Please.
Loc2-5	- Shall we take a smoke break? - Glydl suggested.
*	
*	- No smoke breaks! - you objected sharply. - Time is money! Speaking of money - isn't it time to place bets?
*	
*	- As you wish, - Glydl smiled. - Just a moment, let me get out <clr>50<clrEnd> cr!
Loc2-6	- I remind you that the starting bet is <clr>50<clrEnd> cr, - Glydl said.
*	
*	- I remember, I remember! - you snapped, reaching into your pocket.
Loc2-7	- I remember playing Klugg once with a gaal, - Glydl plunged into reminiscence. - The scoundrel learned to tell the dice apart by the look of their backs. But I beat him anyway, because...
*	
*	- I came here to play, not to listen to any nonsense! - you roared. - Let's place bets!
Loc2-8	- Oh, these pelengs! - Glydl grumbled. - They can't invent anything themselves, so they try to steal other people's. Now they've set their eyes on my game. Aren't you ashamed to work for them?
*	
*	You merely clenched your teeth, trying not to give in to the provocation.
*	
*	- All right, - Glydl sighed. - Time to place bets.
Loc2-9	- Perhaps you would like to raise the starting bet? - Glydl asked in a mocking tone. - I remember playing once with a maloq, and he kept trying to raise the starting bet. Well, I didn't object, but in the end he lost 10,000 cr or so, I don't remember exactly...
*	
*	- Stop stalling! - you growled. - We bet <clr>50<clrEnd> cr each, as agreed!
Loc2-10	- Not tired of taking risks yet? - Glydl asked. - No? You're quite the gambler, <Ranger>! All right, then put down <clr>50<clrEnd> cr!
Loc3-1	You and Glydl have each put down <clr>50<clrEnd> cr. The dice are thoroughly shuffled. Now you need to choose one of them.
Loc3-2	You and Glydl have each put <clr>50<clrEnd> cr on the table. The bets are in, the dice are shuffled, the bag lies in the center of the table. Time to begin!
Loc3-3	The starting bets of <clr>50<clrEnd> cr have taken their place on the table. Time to draw a die from the bag!
Loc3-4	You put down <clr>50<clrEnd> cr. Glydl puts down the same amount. Now you need to draw a die from the bag.
Loc3-5	Glydl was the first to put <clr>50<clrEnd> cr on the table. You reluctantly added the same amount.
*	
*	- Well, shall we draw our dice? - you joked.
Loc3-6	The bets of <clr>50<clrEnd> cr are in. Now everything depends on Lady Luck alone.
Loc3-7	The bag with the dice lies in the center of the table, next to the pile of money. Just think, all of this will be played for in a single hand! And you need to choose your die right now.
Loc3-8	The dice are well shuffled. You discreetly touch your talisman under the table - it is very important now to draw a good die!
Loc3-9	The dice are thoroughly shuffled. Now everything depends on your luck alone.
Loc3-10	- So, a replay! - Glydl said solemnly. - It all depends on who draws which die now!
Loc29-1	Two black circles lay on the table. You and Glydl had both drawn blank dice. You would have to replay.
Loc30-1	You had "nothing," and Glydl didn't have much either: a "sucker." But still more than you. You lost.
Loc31-1	Glydl's die showed a "derquack," yours a blank. You lost.
Loc32-1	Glydl's die showed a longnosed crester. Far weightier than your blank.
Loc33-1	- I respect your fighting qualities, - Glydl remarked. - Only a true hero can play with a blank against a human. Allow me to help you put the dice into the bag.
Loc38-1	Glydl put a black circle on the table. A weight fell from your heart. With your sucker you had managed to win after all.
Loc39-1	You and Glydl laid the dice on the table. From the two black circles two nasty suckers looked up at you. You would have to replay.
Loc40-1	- Well, that's wonderful, - Glydl said, seeing your sucker beside his derquack. - I had already stopped believing I could win.
Loc41-1	Your die with the sucker looked quite pitiful beside Glydl's die, which sported a longnosed crester. You lost.
Loc42-1	- What bad luck! - Glydl shook his head. - You surprised me with your sucker!
*	Glydl's die showed a human. You won.
Loc47-1	Glydl silently laid a die with no picture on the table. Beside it you triumphantly placed yours - with a derquack. Glydl sighed and took the bag. You won.
Loc48-1	Two dice lay on the table. Yours, with a derquack, and Glydl's, with a sucker. You could not contain your joy:
*	- Gather up the dice, Glydl! - you declared. - And I'll take care of the money.
Loc49-1	You and Glydl each had a derquack. You would have to replay.
Loc50-1	Laying the die with the derquack on the table, you looked at Glydl hopefully. He shook his head: "Can't help you!" and laid beside yours a die with a crester. You lost.
Loc51-1	Glydl put a die showing a human on the table.
*	- I have a derquack, - you announced, tossing your die into the bag. - Take the money, I can't bear to look.
*	- As you say, - Glydl replied. - It will be an honor.
Loc56-1	You laid a die with a longnosed crester on the table. Glydl laid a blank die beside it. You won with ease.
Loc57-1	Your die with the handsome crester lay on the table. Beside it Glydl placed his: with a picture of a pitiful sucker. You won.
Loc58-1	Your longnosed crester or Glydl's derquack: who beats whom? What a silly question! You won.
Loc59-1	Two longnosed cresters as the result of a stubborn struggle. You would have to replay.
Loc60-1	Sure of victory, you laid a die with a longnosed crester on the table. To which Glydl replied with a die with a human. Oh, what a pity! You lost.
Loc65-1	Glydl put a black circle on the table.
*	
*	- And with that you wanted to play against me? - you asked contemptuously, placing beside it your die with the picture of a human. - Come on, shuffle the dice.
Loc66-1	Glydl, stone-faced, laid a die with a sucker on the table. Damn, you swore to yourself, laying down your die with a human. How galling to lose like this! But it couldn't be helped; maybe you'd have better luck next time.
Loc67-1	You had a die with a human, Glydl one with a derquack. You won. It couldn't have been otherwise.
Loc68-1	- I was one step from winning, - Glydl remarked, looking at his die with a longnosed crester beside yours, which showed a human. - A thrilling game.
Loc69-1	On both dice, Glydl's and yours, a human was drawn. "Ah, I wish I'd drawn a sucker," you thought. "As it is, we'll have to replay."
Loc75-1	You put the dice back into the bag and began to shuffle them, waiting for Glydl to collect his winnings.
Loc75-2	- I feel you'll ruin me with this kind of play, - Glydl complained, taking the money.
*	
*	You put the dice back into the bag and began to shuffle them, waiting for Glydl to collect his winnings.
Loc75-3	- The wise yield, - Glydl approved of your action, raking the money off the table.
*	
*	You put the dice back into the bag and began to shuffle them, waiting for Glydl to collect his winnings.
Loc75-4	- We sacrifice the small for the sake of the great, - Glydl commented. - Very good.
*	
*	You put the dice back into the bag and began to shuffle them, waiting for Glydl to collect his winnings.
Loc75-5	- If only it were always like this! - Glydl said dreamily, taking his winnings.
*	
*	You put the dice back into the bag and began to shuffle them, waiting for Glydl to collect his winnings.
Loc75-6	- What if I have a bad die too? - Glydl suggested with a mysterious air. - Though it's your business.
*	
*	You put the dice back into the bag and began to shuffle them, waiting for Glydl to collect his winnings.
Loc75-7	- Well, unlucky at Klugg, lucky with a hug! - Glydl cheered you up, taking his winnings.
*	
*	You put the dice back into the bag and began to shuffle them, waiting for Glydl to collect his winnings.
Loc75-8	- Klugg is not a "gluck," to play is not a spree, you can lose your pants, you'll see, - Glydl summed up, raking the money off the table.
*	
*	You put the dice back into the bag and began to shuffle them, waiting for Glydl to collect his winnings.
Loc75-9	- Actually, I bluff sometimes, - Glydl reported, taking the money.
*	
*	You put the dice back into the bag and began to shuffle them, waiting for Glydl to collect his winnings.
Loc75-10	- You fold, - Glydl stated.
*	
*	You put the dice back into the bag and began to shuffle them, waiting for Glydl to collect his winnings.
Loc76-1	You and Glydl each put your die into the bag and shook it in turn. On the table lay a pile of money that you were about to fight for.
Loc77-1	- Unfortunately, - Glydl said, - I have to fold.
*	
*	While he puts the dice back into the bag and shuffles them, you can take your winnings.
Loc77-2	Glydl folded. While he puts the dice back into the bag and shuffles them, you can take your winnings.
Loc77-3	After looking at his die, Glydl folded. While he puts the dice back into the bag and shuffles them, you can take your winnings.
Loc77-4	While Glydl puts the dice back into the bag and shuffles them, you can take your winnings.
Loc77-5	- A serious bid, - Glydl remarked, putting his die into the bag. - I fold.
*	
*	While Glydl puts the dice back into the bag and shuffles them, you can take your winnings.
Loc77-6	- Where would I get such strength, - Glydl joked. - I fold.
*	
*	While Glydl puts the dice back into the bag and shuffles them, you can take your winnings.
Loc77-7	- I fold, - Glydl said, putting his die into the bag.
*	
*	While he puts the dice back into the bag and shuffles them, you can take your winnings.
Loc77-8	- No, I don't play like this, - Glydl shook his head. - Fold.
*	
*	While he puts the dice back into the bag and shuffles them, you can take your winnings.
Loc78-1	- The bar is closing! - the bartender shouted to the room.
*	
*	- It's already morning, - Glydl announced, getting up from the table. - We played all night. I hope you enjoyed it no less than I did. You managed to beat me at Klugg, you're the first who has been able to do it. As I promised, I will sign your copyright transfer contract.
*	
*	Soon Glydl's signature was gleaming on the peleng document.
*	
*	- And now allow me to leave you, - your Klugg partner said. - I wish you every success in your fight against the dominators! All the best.
*	
*	And Glydl left the bar. You did not linger either - you still had to deliver the signed document to the planet <FromPlanet>, where a round sum of <Money> cr awaited you, no later than <Date>.
Loc79-1	Reaching into the bag, you fished out a black disk. There was <clr>nothing<clrEnd> of interest drawn on it. You tried to give your face a calm expression so that Glydl, who was rummaging in the bag, would notice nothing.
*	
*	- I await your bets, - Glydl said. - The additional bet must be no more than <clr>200<clrEnd> cr. If you've run out of money or got a bad die, fold.
Loc79-2	You drew a die from the bag. It showed a <clr>sucker<clrEnd>, easily recognizable by its pair of membranous wings and long proboscis. With such a die all you could do was hope that Glydl drew a human.
*	
*	- I await your bets, - Glydl said. - The additional bet must be no more than <clr>200<clrEnd> cr. If you've run out of money or got a bad die, fold.
Loc79-3	The die you drew from the bag showed a <clr>derquack<clrEnd>: an animal with smooth skin and large eyes. Not the best option.
*	
*	- I await your bets, - Glydl said. - The additional bet must be no more than <clr>200<clrEnd> cr. If you've run out of money or got a bad die, fold.
Loc79-4	Looking at the die drawn from the bag, you recognized a <clr>longnosed crester<clrEnd>, a winged animal with long webbed legs and an equally long toothy maw. Not bad. Unless Glydl drew a human from the bag.
*	
*	- I await your bets, - Glydl said. - The additional bet must be no more than <clr>200<clrEnd> cr. If you've run out of money or got a bad die, fold.
Loc79-5	The die you drew showed a <clr>human<clrEnd>. You couldn't have wished for better. If only Glydl didn't fish a sucker out of the bag.
*	
*	- I await your bets, - Glydl said. - The additional bet must be no more than <clr>200<clrEnd> cr. If you've run out of money or got a bad die, fold.
Loc80-1	- I think I'll add a little, - Glydl said and put <clr>50<clrEnd> cr on the table.
Loc81-1	- This bet is a bit small for me, - Glydl said. - I'll raise a little.
*	Glydl put <clr>100<clrEnd> cr on the table.
Loc82-1	Looking thoughtfully at his die, Glydl put <clr>150<clrEnd> cr on the table.
Loc83-1	- I'll try taking a risk, - Glydl said and laid out <clr>200<clrEnd> cr.
Loc85-1	You added [p9] cr to the pot. All bets were made, time to reveal the dice.
Loc85-2	- Let's see what you've got there, - Glydl said. - I'll <clr>call<clrEnd> your bet.
*	
*	The bets were made, time to reveal the dice.
Loc85-3	- Well, well, - Glydl said, putting <clr>150<clrEnd> cr on the table. - Let's see what we're playing with. All bets are made, time to open up!
Loc85-4	- I'll add a <clr>hundred<clrEnd> too, - Glydl said, taking out his money. - Well then, time to see whose die is stronger!
Loc85-5	- The zero option, - Glydl said thoughtfully. - Fine, let's reveal.
Loc85-6	- Well, we're not afraid of fifties, - Glydl declared and laid <clr>50<clrEnd> cr on the table. - Here you are. And now let's reveal the dice!
Loc86-1	With an inscrutable expression on his face, Glydl took a die from the bag. You followed his example. Unfortunately, you got the weakest option: <clr>nothing<clrEnd>.
Loc87-1	The <clr>sucker<clrEnd> looking at you from the die you had just drawn from the bag was the most hated creature on the planet <ToPlanet>. Weighing your chances in a game with such a die, you too began to feel dislike for this creature.
Loc88-1	You drew from the bag a die with a <clr>derquack<clrEnd>. The expression in the derquack's huge eyes was as uncertain as your chances in this game.
Loc89-1	Not a bad choice: a <clr>longnosed crester<clrEnd>. You could probably take a risk.
Loc90-1	You got a die with a picture of a <clr>human<clrEnd>. Judging by the expression on Glydl's face, his die was worse.
Loc91-1	You added [p9] cr to the pot.
*	
*	- Now let's look at our dice, - Glydl said.
Loc91-2	Glydl silently added [p9] cr to the pot.
*	
*	- Now it's time to look at our dice, - he said.
Loc91-3	- All right, I'll put in another [p9] cr, - Glydl said, taking out his money. - Now let's see whose die is stronger.
Loc91-4	- I wonder what die you have, - Glydl said, laying [p9] cr on the table, - let's reveal the dice.
Loc91-5	- I can't go along with that, - you declared, adding <clr>150<clrEnd> cr to the bets. - Of course, you can fold.
*	
*	- No, I think I'll play a bit longer, - Glydl replied and put <clr>150<clrEnd> cr on the table.
*	
*	- Then let's reveal the dice! - you said.
Loc91-6	- The game is getting big, - Glydl joked. - I call.
*	
*	And he put <clr>50<clrEnd> cr on the table.
*	
*	- Time to reveal, - you said.
Loc91-7	- Why not two hundred? - Glydl inquired.
*	
*	- Come on, put up a hundred or fold, - you replied.
*	
*	- Fine, here's <clr>100<clrEnd> cr, - Glydl took out the money. - Well, let's see who gets the pot!
Loc91-8	- Oh no, buddy, - you declared gloatingly, laying <clr>200<clrEnd> cr on the table. - Put up two hundred or fold!
*	
*	- All right, have it your way, - Glydl agreed and also laid <clr>200<clrEnd> cr on the table.
*	
*	- Well, shall we reveal? - he asked, looking greedily at the pile of money on the table.
Loc91-9	- <clr>100<clrEnd> cr isn't enough for you? - Glydl asked in surprise. - Oh well, here's another <clr>100<clrEnd> cr. Now let's look at our dice.
Loc91-10	- Then let's look at our dice, - Glydl said.
Loc92-1	Glydl silently put <clr>50<clrEnd> cr on the table.
Loc93-1	- <clr>100<clrEnd> cr to start, - Glydl said, putting <clr>100<clrEnd> cr on the table. - I await your offers.
Loc94-1	- My bet: <clr>150<clrEnd> cr, - Glydl announced. - Now it's your turn.
Loc95-1	Glydl added <clr>200<clrEnd> cr to the pot and looked closely at your face, gauging the impression he had made.
Loc96-1	- I'm not in the mood for betting. Let's just reveal the dice, - Glydl suggested.
Loc97-1	- With your permission, - Glydl answered readily, - the game is called "Klugg," not "gluck." Its rules are extremely simple. Let's go over to the table, and I'll show you everything.
*	Glydl led you to one of the tables, on which lay a small pouch of opaque material. Then he shook out of the bag ten identical disks with pictures on one side.
*	- We call them "dice," - Glydl continued. He laid the disks out on the table in two rows of five. - As you can see, there are five pairs of pictures here. Two disks have no pictures; we call them blank. Two show a sucker - a local two-winged parasite that feeds on blood. The next two show a derquack. That is an amphibian that feeds on suckers. The next two show a longnosed crester - derquacks are its favorite food, though it does not turn up its nose at suckers either. And two more show a human, who has long hunted cresters and eaten derquacks. At the same time, humans are the suckers' main prey. Klugg is played like this. Two players make a starting bet: each puts <clr>50<clrEnd> cr on the table. Then each takes one die from the bag and, after looking at it, either offers to reveal the dice or raises the bet. After both players have put the same amount of money on the table, the dice are laid out on the table. The one whose die turns out higher takes all the money from the table.
*	- And which dice are considered higher? - you asked.
*	- I thought you had guessed, - Glydl answered. - But if not, I'll explain in detail:
*	any die is higher than a blank,
*	a sucker is higher than a human,
*	a derquack is higher than a sucker,
*	a longnosed crester is higher than a derquack and a sucker,
*	a human is higher than all except a sucker.
*	So, I hope everything is clear to you now. If you can scrape together <clr>1000<clrEnd> cr, you can have a wonderful time at this marvelous game.
Loc98-1	You left the bar. Pondering the stupidity of those who waste precious time at a gambling table, you headed for your ship. You had failed your mission, but that did not bother you. Let Chief Lyakusha of the planet <FromPlanet> look for someone else to add to the game assortment of his stupid casinos!
*	
*	New feats awaited you ahead.
Loc99-1	You were just about to put down another <clr>50<clrEnd> cr when Glydl announced:
*	
*	- With the greatest regret I must report that I have run out of money. You've cleaned me out! I never thought this could happen... Now I will have to sign your copyright transfer contract, otherwise what will I live on until I come up with some new game?
*	
*	After signing the document, Glydl got up from the table and quickly left the bar. You allowed yourself one more drink, celebrating your stunning victory. Just think, you had won {[p3]-[p4]} cr from Glydl, and you'd be given <Money> cr more on the planet <FromPlanet>! If you managed to get there by <Date>, of course - you suddenly remembered, and, hurriedly leaving the bar, headed back to the spaceport.
Loc101-1	- The bar is closing! - the bartender shouted to the room.
*	
*	- It's already morning, - Glydl announced, getting up from the table. - We played all night. I hope you enjoyed it no less than I did. However, you did not manage to beat me at Klugg, as I had expected. So I will not sign your copyright transfer contract.
*	
*	With these words Glydl left the bar. You also went out into the street and headed for your ship. On the way you pondered the stupidity of those who waste precious time at a gambling table. Take yourself, for example: you hadn't slept all night, you had lost {[p4]-[p3]} cr, you had failed your mission... Damn this game! Let Chief Lyakusha of the planet <FromPlanet> look for someone else to add to the game assortment of his stupid casinos!
*	
*	New feats awaited you ahead.
Path2	All right, let's play
Path2b	- With the greatest pleasure, - Glydl replied, still showing his teeth. - But mind you: we play to the end, that is, until <clr>6<clrEnd> o'clock in the morning, unless, of course, somebody gets cleaned out earlier.
*	
*	You went up to the table on which lay the bag with the dice. Glydl put the dice into the bag and mixed them, turning the bag over several times.
*	
*	- We have a rule: the loser shuffles the dice, - Glydl told you. - That is so that everyone plays fair. As the host, I shuffle the dice the first time. I hope it brings you luck. Please, have a seat.
*	You and Glydl sat down at the table. Your opponent shook and turned over the bag of dice for quite a long time, showing with his whole manner how honestly he intended to play. At last he left the bag alone, and the game began.
Path3	Place the starting bets
Path62	Draw a die
Path119	Replay
Path120	Replay
Path121	Replay
Path122	Replay
Path123	Replay
Path124	Wait for Glydl to collect the money
Path125	Wait for Glydl to collect the money
Path126	Wait for Glydl to collect the money
Path127	Wait for Glydl to collect the money
Path128	Wait for Glydl to collect the money
Path129	Wait for Glydl to collect the money
Path131	Wait for Glydl to collect the money
Path132	Wait for Glydl to collect the money
Path133	Wait for Glydl to collect the money
Path134	Wait for Glydl to collect the money
Path135	Take the winnings
Path136	Take the winnings
Path137	Take the winnings
Path138	Take the winnings
Path139	Take the winnings
Path140	Take the winnings
Path141	Take the winnings
Path142	Take the winnings
Path143	Take the winnings
Path144	Take the winnings
Path151	Fold
Path153	Suggest revealing the dice
Path157	Add 50 cr to the pot
Path164	Add 100 cr to the pot
Path169	Reveal the dice
Path197	Add 150 cr to the pot
Path202	Add 200 cr to the pot
Path207	Fold
Path208	Fold
Path209	Fold
Path210	Fold
Path211	Call the bet
Path212	Call the bet
Path214	Call the bet
Path217	Call the bet
Path247	Reveal the dice
Path272	Place additional bets
Path277	Place additional bets
Path278	Place additional bets
Path279	Place additional bets
Path280	Place additional bets
Path333	Agree
Path334	Call the bet
Path335	Call the bet
Path336	Call the bet
Path337	Call the bet
Path338	Fold
Path339	Fold
Path340	Fold
Path341	Fold
Path342	Fold
Path343	Add 50 cr to the pot
Path345	Add 100 cr to the pot
Path347	Add 100 cr to the pot
Path349	Add 150 cr to the pot
Path351	Add 200 cr to the pot
Path353	Add 150 cr to the pot
Path354	Add 200 cr to the pot
Path355	Add 150 cr to the pot
Path356	Add 200 cr to the pot
Path357	Add 200 cr to the pot
Path413	All right, let's play
Path413b	- With the greatest pleasure, - Glydl replied, still showing his teeth. - But mind you: we play to the end, that is, until <clr>6<clrEnd> o'clock in the morning, unless, of course, somebody gets cleaned out earlier.
*	
*	He put the dice into the bag and mixed them, turning the bag over several times.
*	
*	- We have a rule: the loser shuffles the dice, - Glydl told you. - That is so that everyone plays fair. As the host, I shuffle the dice the first time. I hope it brings you luck. Please, have a seat.
*	You and Glydl sat down at the table. Your opponent shook and turned over the bag of dice for quite a long time, showing with his whole manner how honestly he intended to play. At last he left the bag alone, and the game began.
Path414	I'd like to know what this "gluck" is
Path415	No, gambling is not for me
Path416	No, gambling is not for me
Path417b	After all, you couldn't confess to this puny little man that a glorious ranger didn't have 1000 cr!
Path418b	After all, you couldn't confess to this puny little man that a glorious ranger didn't have 1000 cr!
Path422	Try to bet an item instead
Path422b	- Listen, pal, - you addressed Glydl. - I'm having some small money problems here. I could stake something else. For example, my ranger's badge. A great rarity in the galaxy. I can let you have it for <clr>500<clrEnd> cr. Well, how about it, deal?
*	
*	- Thank you very much for the honor, - Glydl answered. - But I already have a decent collection of such badges, as well as blasters, clothing and other ranger junk. And if you can't stake <clr>50<clrEnd> cr, then there is nothing I can do to help you. Farewell.
*	
*	Glydl rose from the table. Realizing that you would get nothing more out of Glydl, you headed for the exit.
Path445	Try to bet an item instead
Path445b	- Listen, pal, - you addressed Glydl. - I'm having some small money problems here. I could stake something else. For example, my ranger's badge. A great rarity in the galaxy. I can let you have it for <clr>500<clrEnd> cr. Well, how about it, deal?
*	
*	- Thank you very much for the honor, - Glydl answered. - But I already have a decent collection of such badges, as well as blasters, clothing and other ranger junk. And if you don't have <clr>1000<clrEnd> cr on you, then there is nothing I can do to help you. Farewell.
*	
*	Glydl rose from the table. Realizing that you would get nothing more out of Glydl, you headed for the exit.
Path446	Try to bet an item instead
Path446b	- Listen, pal, - you addressed Glydl. - I'm having some small money problems here. I could stake something else. For example, my ranger's badge. A great rarity in the galaxy. I can let you have it for <clr>500<clrEnd> cr. Well, how about it, deal?
*	
*	- Thank you very much for the honor, - Glydl answered. - But I already have a decent collection of such badges, as well as blasters, clothing and other ranger junk. And if you don't have <clr>1000<clrEnd> cr on you, then there is nothing I can do to help you. Farewell.
*	
*	Glydl rose from the table. Realizing that you would get nothing more out of Glydl, you headed for the exit.
