QuestDescription	The security service of planet <ToPlanet> in the <ToStar> system has a one-time job for a person like you, <Ranger>. The assignment is delicate and dangerous, but for carrying it out you will receive a round sum of <Money> cr.
*	
*	Arrive on <ToPlanet> no later than <Date> and report to the Supervision Office; Supreme Supervisor Kuakish will explain the matter to you.
QuestSuccessGovMessage	Supreme Supervisor Kuakish has informed us that you handled his assignment splendidly, <Ranger>! We congratulate you and are transferring a bonus of <Money> cr to your account.
*	
*	We remind you of the need to keep silent about your mission on planet <ToPlanet>. Otherwise we will consider it necessary to get rid of you.
Par1-1	Time: {<> div 60} hr. {<> mod 60} min.
Par1-crit	Morning has come, and the casino is closing. You had to leave along with everyone else. You never found Kuakish - he must have been deeply disappointed in you. Or perhaps he suspected something. In any case, you failed your mission.
Par3-1	You know nothing about cards
Par3-2	A feeble player
Par3-3	You play so-so
Par3-4	A good player
Par3-5	Don't sit down to cards with you!
Par4-1	Security does not suspect you
Par4-2	Security hardly suspects anything
Par4-3	Security is starting to eye you
Par4-4	Security has taken note of you
Par4-5	Security suspects you
Par4-6	Security is about to throw you out!
Par4-crit	Two guards approach you with a determined look.
*	
*	- Excuse me, sir, but we are obliged to ask you to leave the casino...
*	
*	You had barely moved away from the casino when figures of Pelengans emerged from the darkness on the left and on the right.
*	
*	- Well, did you manage to get what we're looking for? - you recognized Kuakish's voice.
*	
*	Your rumpled look answered that question best of all. Kuakish's politeness evaporated in an instant.
*	
*	- Stupid little human! I knew that getting involved with your monkey race would only bring me losses! Get off the planet while I'm still being kind! And don't you dare blab about anything, or you'll regret it!
*	
*	Glad that he had not drowned you in the nearest swamp, you hurried to the spaceport.
Par5-1	Drunk: <> g
Par5-crit	And then the floor suddenly bends and hits you on the head! You remember nothing after that.
*	
*	Having sobered up by afternoon, you understand that the mission is a failure. Hm... Mother did tell you: "Sobriety is the norm of life!"
Par6-1	Attentiveness: <>
Par7-1	The loser has returned
Par7-3	The loser needs money
Par7-4	The loser has left
Par7-5	The loser is unconscious
Par8-1	Money in the case: <> cr
Par9-2	The case holds a laptop
Par9-3	The case holds drugs
Par11-1	Bet: <>
Par12-2	You bet on the first dozen (1-12)
Par12-3	You bet on the second dozen (12-24)
Par12-4	You bet on the third dozen (25-36)
Par12-5	You bet on even
Par12-6	You bet on odd
Par13-1	Chances of winning: <>%
Par14-1	You bet on <>
Par15-1	The number is <>
Par17-1	Your belongings and achievements:
Par18-1	Case
Par19-1	You have nothing to pay with!!!
Par19-3	<> cr
Par19-crit	Because of your insolvency, you are driven out of the casino in disgrace.
*	
*	You had barely moved away from the casino when figures of Pelengans emerged from the darkness on the left and on the right.
*	
*	- Well, did you manage to get what we're looking for? - you recognized Kuakish's voice.
*	
*	Your rumpled look answered that question best of all. Kuakish's politeness evaporated in an instant.
*	
*	- Stupid little human! I knew that getting involved with your monkey race would only bring me losses! Get off the planet while I'm still being kind! And don't you dare blab about anything, or you'll regret it!
*	
*	Glad that he had not drowned you in the nearest swamp, you hurried to the spaceport.
Par20-1	Spray
Par21-1	Pistol
Par22-2	"Out of Order" sign
Par22-3	The sign is hung
Par23-2	You know card sharps' tricks
Loc1-1	Supreme Supervisor Kuakish clearly had a rich past. The scar across his whole warty mug, the glass lens of a camera in place of his left eye and, of course, the Order of the Golden Leech with Seaweed on his belly bore witness to that. Nevertheless, at the sight of you he smiled amiably, baring two hundred small teeth.
*	
*	- Ah, <Ranger>. I was told of your agreement to carry out a small delicate mission. As you evidently know, our planet is located not far from the borders of human space, and we actively cooperate with your civilization. Earth specialists and guests live in our settlement called Human Town. One of Human Town's attractions is the casino "Galaxy". It is a respectable establishment frequented not only by Earthlings from the diplomatic mission and the representative offices of private firms but also by high-ranking Pelengans. It is run by one Jack Butterbroad. Now, we have information that the casino is in fact only a cover for illegal drug trafficking. But so far we cannot prove it.
Loc2-1	- Our agents will not be able to get close to Butterbroad. A person is needed for that... We could, of course, turn to Earth's special services, but you know about the regrettable mistrust that has reigned until now between our civilizations... Besides, as I said, the casino is visited by very high-ranking persons. So we would like to avoid any hint of scandal - at least until we have one hundred percent proof. That is why we prefer to act unofficially. So, if anything happens, we don't know you.
Loc3-1	- And that's not all. We cannot supply you with either weapons or special equipment. Firstly, the entrance of "Galaxy" has a very sophisticated control system; secondly, for the reasons mentioned, we would not want Pelengan special-service gear to be found on you... All we can allot you is 100 galactic credits; you're going to a casino, after all, and the money will come in handy. Try not to lose it all or get too drunk, but, on the other hand, if you neither drink nor play at all, that will arouse suspicion. Examine all the rooms carefully - you may notice something useful. And bear in mind that you have only one night to obtain proof of Butterbroad's illegal activity. If you come there a second time, the guards will start watching you far more closely, and then you will hardly be able to dig up anything. At the same time, we don't know what may happen there and at what moment, so keep your eyes open and don't miss a suitable chance. The task is not an easy one, but that is what you are paid for, isn't it?
Loc4-1	You are standing in a corridor. Where shall we direct our steps?
Loc4-2	You are standing in a corridor. Where shall we direct our steps?
Loc5-1	The gaming hall is in full swing. The roulette wheel spins, cards fall on the green baize.
*	
*	- Place your bets, gentlemen... place your bets... - the croupiers' voices carry. - Minimum bet 10 cr, maximum 150 cr!
*	
*	Looking at these polite young men, you would never say that they are robots. Yes, it is not for nothing that this casino has such a high reputation - with croupiers like these, cheating is practically out of the question...
Loc6-1	You had barely moved away from the casino when figures of Pelengans emerged from the darkness on the left and on the right.
*	
*	- Well, did you manage to get what we're looking for? - you recognized Kuakish's voice.
Loc7-1	The bar is dimly lit, and muted music plays. Some of the tables are empty, at others sit patrons - representatives of both races. A tall, elegant bartender is carefully wiping glasses with a towel. Behind him are two batteries of bottles - for humans and for Pelengans. He looks at you questioningly, and, so as not to arouse suspicion, you order a drink. Savoring your cocktail, you unhurriedly look over the local crowd. With the Pelengans, of course, you won't be able to strike up contact, but some of the humans may be of interest...
Loc7-2	Having ordered another cocktail, you cast an attentive glance over the patrons.
Loc7-3	Having ordered another round, you cast an attentive glance over the patrons.
Loc7-4	Having sipped another cocktail, you cast an attentive glance over the patrons.
Loc7-5	Having taken another glass, you cast an attentive glance over the patrons.
Loc7-6	Having ordered another round, you cast an attentive glance over the patrons.
Loc7-7	Having sipped another portion of booze, you cast an attentive glance over the patrons.
Loc7-8	Having taken one more cocktail, you cast an attentive glance over the patrons.
Loc7-9	Having ordered another cocktail, you cast an attentive glance over the patrons.
Loc7-10	You take a drink again, and the bartender looks at you with undisguised respect!
Loc8-1	Kuakish took the case from you, looked inside and croaked with satisfaction.
*	
*	- Well, this is what we need. To complete the picture, your testimony is lacking... Let's go to the car.
*	
*	You had barely sat down in the seat when you felt the needle of a syringe pierce your neck.
*	
*	- So-called Revelin, the truth drug, - Kuakish explained kindly. - We need to know everything, even what you noticed only on a subconscious level...
Loc9-1	Kuakish's politeness evaporated in an instant.
*	
*	- Stupid little human! I knew that getting involved with your monkey race would only bring me losses! Get off the planet while I'm still being kind! And don't you dare blab about anything, or you'll regret it!
*	
*	Glad that he had not drowned you in the nearest swamp, you hurried to the spaceport.
Loc10-1	Half an hour later, when your tongue ached from the loquacity that had broken out in you, Kuakish nodded.
*	
*	- That's all we wanted to find out. You will get your money. And now I recommend that you leave the planet as soon as possible.
*	
*	Only before takeoff, after tuning in to the Pelengan station "Swamp Herald", did you learn the latest news:
*	
*	"Thanks to a brilliant operation by Dzukhallag, a human espionage network has been exposed on planet <ToPlanet>. Under the cover of the casino "Galaxy", Earthlings carried out recruitment and received information from the double agents they had recruited. The spies and traitors will now receive their well-deserved punishment. An official protest has been sent to the Embassy of the Earth Confederation. So far there has been no official comment from the Earthlings - of course, they have nothing to say! Taking this opportunity, we congratulate Supreme Supervisor Kuakish on the award of his next order degree - the Golden Leech with Seaweed and Larvae."
*	
*	Well, how about that... You could have suspected from the start that Kuakish was not telling the whole truth. Still, it is interesting what information the Earthlings were obtaining that way. The Pelengans don't have that many technologies that could interest humans... And then you pay attention to the words "double agents". Of course! The Earthlings do not dare to spy directly against the Gaalians and Faeyans, so they decided to make use of the information that Pelengan intelligence obtains! And the Pelengans, much more than the rational Faeyans or Gaalians, are prone to such a weakness as gambling fever - which is a good pretext for recruitment... Yes, it was all cleverly devised, until you interfered. It seems your mission turned out to be not very patriotic... You feel rotten, but the sum of <Money> cr will help compensate your moral damage.
Loc11-1	Though you had guessed that it was better to say nothing about the laptop and the Faeyan files, there was nothing you could do. Kuakish heard you out to the end and only then gave vent to his irritation.
*	
*	- Damned monkey, who asked you to stick your nose into the case?! Well, all right, you asked for it...
*	
*	- I demand an explanation! - you exclaimed, vainly trying to break free from the grip of the Pelengans holding you. Another injection deprived you of the ability to move.
*	
*	- Very well, - Kuakish agreed in a tone that boded nothing good. - You won't tell anyone anything anyway... We have long suspected that human intelligence was operating under the cover of the casino. Alas, even our high-ranking lyakushas and Dzukhallag officers are not immune to gambling fever. Sometimes they lose too much in the casino, and the Earthlings use this for recruitment - so as to get, practically for free, the information we steal from the Faeyans and Gaalians with such difficulty! But now this will be put an end to, and I will finally receive the Golden Leech with Seaweed and Larvae! Begin the capture operation, - he turned to his henchmen. - And take this one to the nearest swamp, as food for the leeches...
*	
*	Not ten minutes had passed before the cold bog closed over you with a juicy smack...
Loc12-1	You can play cards or roulette. In roulette everything depends on the whim of chance; in cards the role of chance is also great, but skill and attentiveness count for quite a bit too - and card sharps' tricks especially raise your chances of success but are fraught with trouble if you are exposed. The candelabra here are made of a titanium alloy, and they hurt especially badly when you get hit with them...
*	
*	Besides, playing cards takes much longer, and you can win (in an honest game) at most four times your bet.
Loc13-1	Your bet?
Loc14-1	After glancing over your partners, you decide that you are dealing with experienced, cool-headed players. You might not even notice them stripping you to the skin... Maybe you should try to improve your odds with card sharp's tricks?
Loc14-2	After glancing at your partners, you decide that they are suckers and are unlikely to notice if you use card sharp's tricks. Then again, who knows - the candelabra are just so titanium...
Loc15-1	If you don't want to risk much, bet on even or odd. The probability of winning is practically 1/2, but the win is only double your bet. You can bet on the first, second or third dozen. The probability of winning is almost 1/3 and the win is triple your bet. If you want to play big, bet on one of the 36 numbers; you can win 36 times your bet, but the probability is only 1/37. What's that you say? Why 1/37? Because if zero comes up, all bets go to the casino.
Loc16-1	- Which number would you like to bet on? - the robot croupier asks politely.
Loc16-2	Ah, which number to bet on?
Loc16-3	- Young man, place your bet already, will you! - exclaims impatiently the sales representative of an Earth company to your right.
Loc18-1	Your partners double their bets!
Loc23-1	- Excuse me, sir, but I see that you are neither playing nor ordering at the bar. Is something wrong?
Loc24-1	The guard's face reflected an agonizing thought process.
*	
*	- Goods? I'm afraid you have the wrong door. This is not a shop.
Loc26-1	Butterbroad is sitting at the desk and looking at you without much sympathy. Well, for that matter, without even a little.
*	
*	- How may I be of service? - he inquires coldly.
Loc26-2	- Do you have something else to report? - Butterbroad asks.
Loc26-3	Butterbroad looks at you expectantly.
Loc26-4	- I'm still listening to you, - Butterbroad reminds you.
Loc26-5	Butterbroad looks at you expectantly.
Loc27-1	Standing by one of the card tables, you suddenly notice one of the players, in front of whom a considerable pile of money has already accumulated, deftly palming a card.
Loc28-1	- Buddy, I saw you cheating, - you say bluntly, - so now, unless you want everyone to find out...
Loc30-1	- To hell with you, take 1,000, and you don't notice me anymore, - the swindler answered.
Loc32-1	- Fine, I'll add another 500, - the sharper winces. - But really - you should have some conscience!
*	
*	"{[p15]} cr - not a bad sum!" you think.
Loc35-1	You notice one of the human players who has just stepped away from the table. He is deathly pale, and his lips tremble. After a few steps he leans against the wall in exhaustion. In his hands is a small case. Looks like yet another loser... Still, what if he turns out to be useful? If he knows something about the casino's secrets, in that state the truth can easily be squeezed out of him. Trying not to attract the guards' attention, you head toward him.
Loc36-1	The stranger looks at you with an absent gaze.
*	
*	- I lost money that wasn't mine... - he mumbles. - If I don't return it by 5 o'clock, I'm done for...
Loc37-1	- A lot, - his voice trembles. - Three... three thousand...
Loc38-1	The stranger sighs hopelessly. Some time later you notice him heading for the exit of the gaming hall.
Loc39-1	After waiting a bit, displaying bored indifference with your whole demeanor, you follow him. Stepping out into the corridor, you manage to see a restroom door closing. Is it worth disturbing a person in such an intimate place?
Loc40-1	Before you are two restroom doors - one says "Gentlemen", the other "Ladies". It's strange that such a fashionable casino has no separate restrooms for humans and Pelengans...
Loc41-1	You are in the men's room. Marble and chrome everywhere, creeping plants twine along the walls. A luxurious establishment! And, interestingly, not a single inscription on the walls. You take out a pen to correct this shortcoming by immortalizing a favorite couplet from childhood:
*	
*	"May the walls of our latrine
*	 Be adorned with wit and satire clean!"
*	
*	However, as it turns out, the walls are treated with a special compound, thanks to which the pens of vandals like you leave no trace on them. Disappointed, you continue your inspection and notice that the partitions between the stalls do not reach the floor.
Loc42-1	Feeling worse than a scout behind enemy lines, you slip into the ladies' room. Phew, it seems you got away with it! No, not in that sense - it's just that nobody is here. The restroom looks luxurious, but you have no time to admire the marble and chrome. Someone might come in, heaven forbid... Just as you are about to leave, you notice an "Out of Order" sign on the door of one of the stalls. After tugging at this door for some reason, you make sure it is impossible to open - short of breaking it out entirely.
Loc43-1	Not understanding what you forgot here, you nevertheless slip into the ladies' room. Well, sure enough - you forgot nothing. Get out of here before somebody comes!
Loc44-1	You carefully open the door, and then... your ears are blasted by a wild scream.
*	
*	- AAA!!! Maniac! Pervert!! Security!!!
*	
*	Of the three, only a guard appears immediately, but even that is enough... You explain to him that you got the wrong door by accident. He seems to have accepted this explanation, but his suspicion appears to have grown.
*	
*	While dealing with the guard, you noticed out of the corner of your eye that an "Out of Order" sign hung on the door of one of the stalls.
Loc44-2	You carefully open the door, and then... your ears are blasted by a wild scream.
*	
*	- AAA!!! Maniac! Pervert!! Security!!!
*	
*	Of the three, only a guard appears immediately, but even that is enough... You explain to him that you got the wrong door by accident. He seems to have accepted this explanation, but his suspicion appears to have grown.
Loc44-3	You carefully open the door, and then... your ears are blasted by a wild scream.
*	- AAA!!! Maniac! Pervert!! Security!!!
*	
*	Of the three, only a guard appears immediately, but even that is enough... You explain to him that you got the wrong door by accident. He seems to have accepted this explanation, but his suspicion appears to have grown.
Loc46-1	Bursting into the restroom, you see the door of the second-to-last stall closing. Well, shall we grab our loser by the gills right away, or first let him finish his business?
Loc47-1	Covering the remaining distance in two bounds, you sharply yank the door toward you. The loser turns around in fright, a beam pistol in his hand.
*	
*	Since he got a weapon past the control system, something fishy is going on here, you manage to figure out while he pulls the trigger...
Loc50-1	Well, you have a chance to take the place of the luckless courier and wait for his partner to show up with the goods - probably those very drugs. But first it would be nice to get rid of the body, since it's cramped in one stall with it, and you could be noticed through the gap...
Loc51-1	What shall we do with the case? Put some more money in it, or will it do as is? Or maybe take the money and go play?
Loc52-1	You set the case on the floor and prepared to wait...
*	
*	At exactly 5:00 someone entered the restroom and took the stall next to yours. From the smell wafting over you realized it was a Pelengan, and you pushed the case toward the partition separating you. The Pelengan took it; you heard the latches click. He's no fool - he's checking the cash! You hear a muffled Pelengan curse, and then rapidly receding footsteps. And he took the case with him, by the way... Well, you shouldn't have been greedy!
Loc53-1	You set the case on the floor and prepared to wait...
*	
*	At exactly 5:00 someone entered the restroom and took the stall next to yours. From the smell wafting over you realized it was a Pelengan, and you pushed the case toward the partition separating you. The Pelengan took it; you heard the latches click. Aha, he's checking the cash... Then the case came back down under the partition, and the Pelengan left. "What, is that all?" you thought with disappointment, and only then realized that it was a different case, though it looked exactly like the first.
*	
*	What's inside, I wonder? Really drugs? Nothing easier than to look and check. But what if there's, say, a bomb in there? Better to hand it over to Kuakish quickly and let him sort it out...
Loc54-1	The stranger's face, brightened for a first moment, darkens again.
*	
*	- Information? What information? I don't know anything... - he mumbles, edging sideways from you toward the exit.
Loc55-1	- Friend, you saved me! - the loser exclaims joyfully. Counting the money, he puts it in his case. - This calls for a celebration, - he continues. - Let's go to the bar, my treat. Don't worry, I have unlimited credit at the bar... too bad they don't take bets in shots, ha-ha-ha!
*	
*	Putting his arm around your shoulders, he steers you toward the bar. Sitting at a table in the corner, you try to drink less and listen more. But your companion chatters about some trifles, and you can't manage to shed any light on the local backstage secrets. From chance slips, however, you understand that this man has some connection to the diplomatic department. Can Earth diplomats really have fallen so low as to get mixed up with the drug mafia?
*	
*	But you are already beginning to regret the three thousand spent on him and are thinking about other options. Suddenly the watch of your anonymous friend (who, by the way, never introduced himself to you) emits a melodious sound, and he rises from his seat.
*	
*	- Friend, I need to step out for a while. You wait here, I'll be right back.
*	
*	He leaves the bar. You follow him with your eyes.
Loc56-1	Soon your friend returned and continued his meaningless chatter. Meanwhile morning comes, and the casino is nearing closing time. The guests are asked to proceed to the exit. You realize that you have wasted your time ingloriously...
Loc57-1	At exactly 5:00 some Pelengan enters the restroom, gives you a malevolent look, washes his hands and leaves. And his little case is exactly the same as your acquaintance's... It seems you scared him off! Well, now you can't prove anything... All that's left is to return to the bar - maybe your new friend will crack after all.
Loc58-1	How interesting! The case holds no drugs at all, and in general it's not really a case but a laptop disguised as one. Of Pelengan make, not the best model... but evidently the value is not in it but in the information stored on it.
*	You turned on the computer, and, not disappointing your expectations, it asked for a password. But for some reason it did so in the Faeyan language! Curiouser and curiouser, as a certain Alice used to say... Fine, the password can't be guessed by hand anyway, let's get out of here.
Loc59-1	As in all top-class casinos, the bartender is not a robot but a human being. He is used to patrons pouring out their hearts to him after another loss or inviting him to celebrate a win with them. You understand that the look of interested sympathy on his face is merely a tribute to the profession, and yet he looks inviting. You exchange a couple of meaningless remarks about the weather and sports, and then decide to move on to topics that interest you more.
Loc59-2	Having served another customer, the bartender turns to you again.
Loc59-3	- Did you want to ask something else?
Loc59-4	The bartender looks at you expectantly.
Loc60-1	Judging by her clothes and bearing, this lady clearly did not study at a finishing school (you, though, have no idea what that is, but it sounds nice). Well, you are concerned not with her moral character but with the information she has. She may very well be an addict who shops here...
*	
*	You buy her a drink.
Loc61-1	The elderly man at the table in the center may at first glance seem to be no less than the embassy's first secretary. But looking at his thin artistic fingers, which, when he falls into thought, seem to shuffle an invisible deck, you guess that you are dealing with a professional gambler. He is hardly interested in the casino's shady dealings - he is here only for the cards... and yet, just in case, you could buy him a drink. Though he is clearly an aesthete, so you will have to order a more expensive beverage.
Loc61-2	The elderly gambler looks at you expectantly.
Loc61-3	- Did you want to ask something else?
Loc61-4	- Is there anything else you're interested in, young man?
Loc61-5	The elderly gambler looks at you expectantly.
Loc61-6	The elderly gambler looks at you expectantly.
Loc62-1	The pale, lanky fellow with tousled straw-colored hair does not inspire much trust. He looks quite like an addict, and even more like a drug dealer. Maybe he is just the one we need! We should question him thoroughly...
Loc62-2	You sit down at the table of the lanky fellow.
Loc62-3	You sit down at the table of the lanky fellow.
Loc62-4	You sit down at the table of the fellow with the tousled hair.
Loc62-5	You sit down at the table of the lanky fellow.
Loc62-6	You sit down at the table of the fellow with the tousled hair.
Loc62-7	You sit down at the table of the lanky fellow.
Loc63-1	Her car really is parked nearby - and looks, perhaps, too expensive for an addict. She presses a button, the car opens its door and turns on its antigravity suspension.
*	
*	- Get in, cowboy!
Loc68-1	The bartender's face frowns.
*	
*	- What do you mean, sir?
Loc69-1	- I can offer pills that neutralize the effect of alcohol. 30 credits apiece. Well, will you take them?
Loc70-1	- Why not? It will cost you 200 credits. A professional's time costs money, young man.
Loc73-1	Covering the remaining distance in two bounds, you sharply yank the door toward you. The loser turns around in fright, a beam pistol in his hand. You try to knock him out with the spray, but because of the heavy dose of alcohol your reaction is too slow, and he pulls the trigger first... Yes, it's not for nothing they say that alcohol shortens life!
Loc74-1	A guard of imposing size stands at the door of Butterbroad's office and looks at you suspiciously.
Loc75-1	- Do you have an appointment?
Loc76-1	You come to only by evening in the Human Town hospital. They tell you that a police patrol picked you up on the street unconscious and, what is worse, without money. The last twenty-four hours have been wiped clean from your memory. Not understanding why you even ended up on this planet, you make your way to the spaceport and fly away.
Loc77-1	- Oh? - Butterbroad raised an eyebrow ironically. - And what do you happen to know?
Loc82-1	Suddenly you understood why he had told you this so easily: he was simply stalling for time. At that very moment guards burst into the office with weapons at the ready...
Loc83-1	You are killed in a shootout with the guards.
Loc84-1	Half an hour later, when your imagination had almost run dry, Kuakish finally stopped the interrogation.
*	
*	- Fine, I see you are telling the truth... You will get your money. And get off the planet while I'm still being kind!
Path2	And you needed me for that? But I'm not a policeman... Why don't you use your own specialists?
Path3	Sounds encouraging
Path4	Well then, let's not waste time
Path4b	Above the casino roof, a hologram of the Galaxy slowly rotates, sparkling with millions of stars. But you are not here to admire special effects. After passing through the control system's scanners, you find yourself in a corridor. To the right is the gaming hall, to the left the bar, and at the end of the corridor two inconspicuous doors - probably a restroom - and behind them a staircase to the second floor.
Path5	To the gaming hall
Path6	Go into the corridor
Path7	To the exit
Path10	Go into the corridor
Path11	Go to the gaming hall
Path12	Go to the bar
Path13	To the bar
Path14	I wasn't able to sniff out anything concrete.
Path15	Yes, of course. I managed to get hold of this case...
Path18	Take part in the game
Path19	Play cards
Path21	Play honestly
Path22	Cheat
Path23	Play roulette
Path24	I bet on even! Come what may!
Path25	I bet on odd, definitely!
Path26	I bet on the second dozen (13-24)!
Path27	I bet on the third dozen (25-36)!
Path28	If we're playing, let's play! I bet on a number!
Path29	7 has always been considered a lucky number!
Path30	13, damn it!
Path31	I'm the coolest Ranger in the Galaxy! So my number is 1!
Path32	In kindergarten I studied programming, so my favorite number is 16!
Path33	Since school I've liked A's...
Path34	Though in school I got C's more often, I think it's a trend!
Path35	Let's play big - may the number be the biggest too! 36!
Path36	10
Path37	20
Path38	40
Path39	50
Path40	100
Path42	Double
Path43	Pass
Path43b	Well, better to lose less than more...
Path44b	Alas! Your money went to your lucky opponents...
Path45b	Zero! What a shame! The only consolation is that your opponents got nothing either...
Path46b	Hooray! You won, and big!
Path47b	Smiling sweetly at your opponents, you put a card sharp's trick into play - now victory is practically in your pocket!
Path48b	Hooray! The croupier pushes your winnings toward you with his paddle.
Path49b	It seems you managed to fool the vigilance of your opponents, but not the robot croupier. He calculated your chances and realized that you had no hope of an honest win.
*	
*	- This player is a cheat, - the robot calmly pronounces. Your opponents exchange glances and reach for the candelabra... Oh, anywhere but the head!!!
Path50b	Your card sharp's tricks have paid off... And, most importantly, nobody noticed a thing!
Path54b	Hooray! You won!
Path55	Observe what is happening in the hall
Path56b	For a while you walked among the tables, watching and listening to the patrons, but noticed nothing suspicious.
Path57b	You watched and listened to the patrons for quite a long time, but their behavior does not seem suspicious. Your own behavior, on the other hand, seems to be suspicious to security... The guy heading toward you, despite his impeccable suit, does not look like a subtle intellectual, but with his shoulder width that's no longer his problem. You make a belated attempt to get lost in the crowd, but he is beside you faster.
Path58	Right - I'll go try my luck at the game!
Path59	Good idea - I'll go have a drink at the bar!
Path60	I think that's none of your business, my dear fellow
Path61	Well, actually I'd like to... acquire... some goods, you know, you understand me?
Path62	Pay no attention, my jokes aren't coming out today, heh-heh...
Path63	I mean neurochemical euphorigens... well, that is, dope... narcotics, in short, got it?
Path63b	The guard called two of his colleagues. They were quite determined.
*	
*	- Excuse me, sir, but we are obliged to ask you to leave the casino...
*	
*	You had to leave this gambling establishment.
Path64	Yes, something really is wrong! And I need to see the manager
Path65b	The guard looks at you doubtfully for a while, then decides:
*	
*	- All right, I'll take you to Mr. Butterbroad.
*	
*	Following the guard, you go out into the corridor; here he lets you go ahead, and you climb to the second floor, feeling his heavy, boring stare on your back. At the doors of the manager's office another hulk stands frozen, but at his colleague's signal he lets you in. You enter the office, and one of the guards comes in after you, staying behind your back.
Path67	Expose the card sharp
Path67b	- Gentlemen, this man is a card sharp! - you exclaim, seizing the swindler by the hand.
*	
*	After a moment's confusion, one of the dishonest player's partners - a Pelengan in the dress uniform of a lyakusha, evidently one who has lost especially much - turns green with fury and, shouting "You vile Earth monkey!!!", throws himself at the sharper. "An Earthling is being beaten!" he cries desperately. Two men from the neighboring tables rush to his aid. A general brawl breaks out...
*	
*	With difficulty you manage to get out of the scrum, escaping with a couple of bruises, a tuft of hair missing and a torn trouser leg. At last the guards who have run up pull the brawlers apart. But it is too late - several high-ranking Pelengans have already been injured in the fight. They demand that the Supervision Service be called and threaten to cause a big diplomatic scandal. "Gentlemen," a voice comes from loudspeakers hidden under the ceiling, "in connection with the regrettable incident that has occurred, the casino is closing early today. We offer our apologies." Along with the other patrons you are forced to proceed to the exit...
Path68	Wait until the game is over and call the card sharp aside for a talk
Path69b	- All right, - the sharper agrees.
*	
*	After a half-hour lecture you are sure that you will always be able to win at cards... if, of course, your cheating is not exposed.
Path70	Teach me these tricks of yours!
Path71	You'll have to share your winnings with me!
Path72	Deal!
Path72b	Taking the money, you return to the gaming hall.
Path74	That's not enough!
Path75	That's not enough!
Path77b	- As you like, - the sharper shrugged. - Greed ruins suckers. Take care.
*	
*	And he calmly headed for the exit, and only then did you realize that you cannot even expose him in revenge - you have no proof. Left empty-handed, you return to the gaming hall.
Path79	Deal!
Path81	What, buddy, had an unlucky day?
Path82	Hello, I'm <Ranger>. May I know your name?
Path83	Is that so? And how much do you need?
Path84	Ha, not bad! Well, I'm afraid that's your problem, buddy.
Path85	Stay in the gaming hall
Path86	Follow him
Path87	Return to the gaming hall
Path88	After him, quick!
Path89	Enter the men's room
Path90	Enter the ladies' room
Path92	To the restroom
Path93	Back to the corridor
Path94	Return to the corridor
Path95	Back to the corridor
Path97	Back to the corridor
Path98	Take the sign
Path99b	After stuffing the sign inside your jacket with difficulty, you returned to the corridor.
Path101	Don't hesitate for a second
Path102b	Covering the remaining distance in two bounds, you sharply yank the door toward you. The loser turns around in fright, a beam pistol in his hand. But a space Ranger's reflexes do not fail you: before he manages to fire, you shoot a jet of spray straight into his nose. He drops to the floor unconscious.
*	First of all you pick up the pistol, and then you pay attention to the stranger's little case. Opening it, you see inside a lone five-credit bill - less than the casino's minimum bet... Apparently this case had held those 3,000 that the stranger squandered. It was not his money, so he was supposed to hand it over to someone... When? Examining the courier's watch, you see that the warning signal is set for 4:55. It remains to decide where the handover is supposed to take place. Here, in the restroom? Why not, actually? Setting the case on the floor again, you make sure that it can easily be pushed under the partition into the next stall.
Path103	Wait
Path103b	Folding your arms on your chest, you wait calmly. Suddenly a short zap of a beam pistol comes from the stall, followed by the sound of a falling body. You rush to the stall and yank the door with all your strength...
Path104b	The gleam of chrome and polished marble holds your attention only briefly, and then it focuses on the second-to-last stall. Through the gap under the door you can see that someone is in there... and it looks like he is neither standing nor sitting but lying on the floor! You sharply yank the stall door, making it swing open...
Path105b	On the stall floor lies the lifeless, curled-up body of the stranger who lost at the tables. Evidently, despairing of quickly finding the necessary sum, he killed himself... First of all you pick up his pistol (noting in passing that something really is fishy, since he got a weapon past the control system), and then you pay attention to his little case. Opening it, you see inside a lone five-credit bill - less than the casino's minimum bet... Apparently this case had held those 3,000 that the stranger squandered. It was not his money, so he was supposed to hand it over to someone, and soon at that. When? Examining the courier's watch, you see that the warning signal is set for 4:55. It remains to decide where the handover is supposed to take place. Right in the restroom? Why not, actually? Setting the case on the floor again, you make sure that it can easily be pushed under the partition into the next stall.
Path107	Hide the body in the ladies' room
Path107b	With your heart pounding with fear, you dragged the body out into the corridor and, after listening at the door, hauled it into the ladies' room. Phew, lucky - nobody there! After quickly seating the courier in one of the stalls, you were about to leave, but just then two girlfriends came into the restroom, chatting about something. The silent scene lasted two seconds. Realizing what was about to happen, you pushed the girlfriends aside and ran. A horrible shriek followed you... You managed to dash out of the casino before security blocked your way.
Path108	Hide the body in another stall
Path108b	Reasoning that the courier's partner would come to one of the neighboring stalls, you decided to drag the body farther away, into the very first stall. But you did not enjoy the wisdom of this decision for long. Only a few minutes had passed when someone entered the restroom. From your stall you heard him humming as he opened a stall door... then the singing broke off.
*	
*	- Your maternal great-grandmother! - the visitor swore in amazement and stomped away. Without waiting for him to bring security, you dashed out into the corridor. But, of course, within a couple of minutes the internal speakers announced that due to extraordinary circumstances the casino was closing and guests were asked to proceed to the exit. You had to comply...
Path109	Hide the body in another stall and hang the "Out of Order" sign on it
Path109b	Reasoning that the courier's partner would come to one of the neighboring stalls, you decided to drag the body farther away, into the very first stall, and hung the "Out of Order" sign on the door. Now you need not fear that a chance visitor will spoil everything.
Path110b	You enter the stall you already know and lock yourself in from the inside.
Path111b	Covering the remaining distance in two bounds, you sharply yank the door toward you. The loser turns around in fright, a beam pistol in his hand. But a space Ranger's reflexes do not fail you: before he manages to fire, you shoot a jet of spray straight into his nose. He drops to the floor unconscious.
*	First of all you pick up the pistol, and then you pay attention to the stranger's little case, where he had put the money... It was not his money, so he was supposed to hand it over to someone - and apparently very soon. Here, in the restroom? Why not, actually? Setting the case on the floor again, you make sure that it can easily be pushed under the partition into the next stall.
Path112	Just wait
Path113	Top up the case with money to 3,000
Path114	Take the money from the case and go to the gaming hall
Path116-par1-crit	You sat in the restroom until the casino closed, but found out nothing!
Path117-par1-crit	You sat in the restroom until the casino closed, but found out nothing!
Path118	Return to the corridor
Path119	Never mind, buddy! I'm in luck tonight, and, so be it, I'll win you that money. We'll settle up some other time!
Path119b	Hope lights up in the stranger's eyes.
*	
*	- Sir, you will save me if you manage to do it before 5 o'clock!
Path120	Well, buddy, today is your lucky day! I'm ready to give you that money... but first I need some information about this casino. We both know it's not just a gambling establishment, don't we?
Path121	Follow him
Path122	Stay in the gaming hall
Path123	Well, consider yourself lucky. Today Fortune is smiling at me with her whole face, and I'll give you those lousy three grand.
Path124	To look for the loser
Path124b	Having found the man who lost someone else's money, you hand him the coveted three thousand.
Path125b	You look for the man who lost someone else's money but cannot find him anywhere. Then suddenly an announcement comes from the speakers: "Ladies and gentlemen, we apologize, but today we are forced to close the casino early. We ask all guests to proceed to the exit." On your way to the exit, from the patrons' remarks you learn that they have just found some guy who killed himself in the restroom...
Path126	Follow him
Path127	Wait
Path128	Go to the exit
Path130	Return to the bar
Path131	Return to the bar
Path132	Enough adventures for today! To the exit
Path133	Oh no, first let's open the case!
Path134	Well, I sniffed out what I could... and the rest is not my concern. To the exit
Path135	Talk to the bartender
Path136	Talk to the girl at the table by the entrance
Path137	Sit at an empty table
Path137b	Slowly sipping your cocktail, you sit alone at a table in the corner, pondering how to carry out your mission. Suddenly the girl who was sitting at the table by the entrance gets up, crosses the bar and sits down across from you, smiling coquettishly with her painted mouth.
Path138b	You sit at a table in the corner, unhurriedly sipping your cocktail and wondering how to bring the casino's owners to light. In the end, having come up with nothing, you decide that the music, which has a soporific effect on you, is to blame for everything. You get up irritated and leave the bar.
Path139	Talk to the man at the table in the center
Path140	Talk to the guy at the table in the corner
Path141	Hi, baby! Bored? How about having a little fun?
Path141b	- With you, is it, handsome? Well, why not. I've always liked space heroes. I hope you have money on you? Then let's go. My car is around the corner.
*	
*	Slightly stunned by this briskness, you follow her out of the bar and then out of the casino.
Path142	Hi, baby. You look great. Listen, I was told you can get dope here, is that true?
Path142b	- Shh! Not here. Do you have money on you? Then come with me.
*	
*	You follow her out of the bar and then out of the casino.
*	
*	- In my car, - she says quietly.
Path143	Get in the car, relax and enjoy it
Path143b	You settle into the soft, comfortable seat. Suddenly steel clamps lock your arms and legs, and the girl pushes something into your face. There is a hiss of aerosol shooting right into your nose. "What a fool I am!" you manage to think before passing out.
Path144	Bang her! Over the head with something heavy.
Path144b	You had nothing heavier than your own fist at hand, but back in college no girl could stand up to you - in the ring, of course. And now too - a knockout with one blow. You drag the unconscious body onto the seat so as not to loiter in the street, and at once steel clamps lock her arms and legs. Aha, so that is what she had prepared for you... After searching her thoroughly, you find neither weapons nor drugs - but you do discover 1,100 credits (surely left over from this lady's previous trusting client) and a small aerosol canister. You know this spray - it causes loss of consciousness for several hours with simultaneous erasure of short-term memory. The indicator on the canister shows that only one dose remains.
*	
*	Taking the money and the spray, you return to the casino.
Path145	You have a cozy bar... Have you worked here long?
Path145b	- Thank you, sir. I'll say without false modesty that our casino is known not only on <ToPlanet> but in neighboring star systems... I have worked here since the very opening. Getting this position is a great honor... and a great responsibility, of course. Among our clients there are quite a few Pelengans, some of them high-ranking... and besides, a casino is the kind of place where passions always run high... you understand how important it is to prevent interracial conflicts. We have, of course, a good security system - it usually works preemptively, nipping dangerous situations in the bud... but after a loss, guests go to pour out their hearts not to a guard but to the bartender... it is important to find words of encouragement for each one, to understand both humans and Pelengans...
Path147	Could you tell me about the patrons? You see, I wouldn't like to drink alone, but at the same time I don't like making acquaintances with just anyone...
Path149	All this is wonderful, of course... but do you have anything... stronger than liquor?
Path150	Thanks, it was nice talking. Pour me another round.
Path151	Pay no attention, my jokes aren't coming out today...
Path152	I mean a high... dope... well, in short, drugs
Path152b	- One minute, sir.
*	
*	The bartender steps back and says something quietly into an intercom. A minute has not yet passed when security enters the room...
Path153	Hi, buddy. I'm interested in certain preparations... um... for internal use.
Path153b	- Not here, - the fellow answered, glancing toward the bartender. - Let's step out into the corridor.
*	
*	You follow him.
Path154	Give me one
Path154b	After swallowing the pill, you feel your brain clear up somewhat.
*	
*	- Don't follow me right away, - the fellow warns. - No need to give the bartender extra grounds for suspicion. Selling these things is not allowed here. Later, if you need more, come back, but don't overdo it - my stock is not unlimited.
Path155	Give me two
Path155b	Nearly choking on two pills, you nevertheless feel a noticeable clearing in your brain.
*	
*	- Don't follow me right away, - the fellow warns. - No need to give the bartender extra grounds for suspicion. Selling these things is not allowed here. Later, if you need more, come back, but don't overdo it - my stock is not unlimited.
Path156	Actually I'm interested in stronger stuff... Dope, in short
Path156b	- Nah, man, I don't deal in that crap, and I don't advise you to! I do the opposite, I clear people's heads... without losing money myself, of course... My pills are completely legal, it's just that they don't allow selling them in the casino. A drunk client loses more money, you understand... But only a drunk one, all within the law. If anyone is spotted here high, he'll be thrown out in a flash. A classy joint, diplomats come in... You know what an eye the guards have here, even though their mugs look dumb... All right, don't follow me, or the bartender will latch on.
*	
*	The fellow returns to the bar.
Path157	Could you teach me the subtleties of card games?
Path158	Agreed
Path158b	After an hour-and-a-half lecture, your card-playing skills improved greatly. However, as a true gentleman, your instructor despises card sharp's tricks, and that area remained unknown to you.
*	
*	By the way, if your attention had not been dulled by alcohol, you would have absorbed the material better.
Path159	Hm... that seems to have been a bad idea
Path160	You know, I have a friend who claims that in Orion preference a black misère can't be caught in principle if at least one red suit has fallen in a half-and-half split...
Path160b	- Your friend is an ignorant blockhead, you can tell him so! In the first place, it depends on which side the sevens fell...
*	
*	By deftly steering your interlocutor with suggestions to laugh at your friend's foolishness, you got a full-scale hour-and-a-half lecture on the subtleties of card games. However, as a true gentleman, your instructor despises card sharp's tricks, and that area remained unknown to you.
*	
*	By the way, if your attention had not been dulled by alcohol, you would have absorbed the material better.
Path162	You must come to this casino often... Tell me, haven't you noticed any oddities here? Say, whether somebody here is peddling something... mm... not entirely legal?
Path162b	- Who told you such nonsense, young man? This is a respectable establishment, one of the best in this sector of space, and not some port dive. Besides, I am not here to track and sniff. I am here for the noble mystery of the Game!
Path164	It was nice talking. I think I'll go play some more!
Path164b	- Good luck, - the gambler nods. You get up and head for the gaming hall.
Path166	To the second floor
Path166b	Ignoring the "Staff Only" sign, you climb to the second floor.
Path167	Ask him to let you through
Path168	No, but...
Path168b	Then I ask you to leave the administrative floor. Make an appointment with the cybersecretary in the usual way.
Path169	Demand that he let you through
Path169b	- Hey you, gorilla, I need to see your boss on important business, and if you get in my way, you'll be very sorry!
Path171	Use the spray
Path171b	You directed a jet of aerosol straight into the guard's nose, but he did not even sneeze. Of course, nose filters, you should have thought of that right away! You get to finish that thought lying on the floor with your arms twisted behind your back. During the interrogation that followed in Butterbroad's office, with the use of Revelin - the truth drug - you spilled everything.
*	
*	- Well, well... - Butterbroad grimaced. - So Pelengan counterintelligence is digging under us after all... And this fool himself has no idea what he got into. All right, inject him with amnesin and throw him out through the back door!
Path172	Return to the first floor
Path173	Use the pistol
Path173b	You pretended to leave, and then suddenly leveled the pistol at the guard:
*	
*	- I don't want trouble, buddy, but you leave me no choice. Open the door, raise your hands and go inside!
*	
*	After a second's thought the guard complied.
Path174	Something tells me Kuakish is hiding something! Let's try to shake the truth out of Butterbroad!
Path174b	You go out into the corridor and, ignoring the "Staff Only" sign, climb to the second floor.
Path175	You'd better come clean right away, Butterbroad! I know everything anyway!
Path176	You're dealing drugs!
Path176b	- I have never heard greater nonsense, - Butterbroad answered, calling security. - Gentlemen, our guest has had too much to drink, please escort him to the exit.
Path177b	- I have never heard greater nonsense, - Butterbroad answered, keeping perfectly cool.
Path178	Ah... uh... so you're not John Butterbroad, my school friend? What a pity... Don't you happen to know John?
Path179b	- Unfortunately, no. And now, please excuse me, I am busy.
Path180b	- Unfortunately, no. Do you always visit friends with a pistol? Well, I hope the incident is closed?
Path181	Do you recognize this case? Yes, yes, the one that was to be handed to your courier in the restroom! I demand an explanation!
Path182	I know about your dealings with the Pelengans and the Faeyans!
Path183b	Perhaps you should not have forgotten about the guard standing behind your back! You get to finish that thought lying on the floor with your arms twisted behind your back. During the interrogation that followed in Butterbroad's office, with the use of the truth drug, you spilled everything.
*	
*	- Well, well... - Butterbroad grimaced. - So Pelengan counterintelligence is digging under us after all... And this fool himself has no idea what he got into. All right, inject him with amnesin and throw him out through the back door!
Path184	You have a corpse in the men's room! Or maybe the guy is just unconscious, I didn't figure it out...
Path185b	- I will deal with it, if, of course, you stop threatening me with a gun.
Path186b	- Really? - Butterbroad looks extremely worried. Even more than a mere casino manager in whose establishment a murder has occurred. He clicks some buttons...
*	
*	- Yes, it's true. Thank you for the information. The casino will have to be closed, and I will ask you not to leave the building until the police arrive.
*	
*	Recalling Kuakish's words that he would not cover for you, you decide that you had better not meet the police. In the commotion that begins, you manage to slip out of the casino.
Path187	Sorry for the trouble, I'm just leaving.
Path188b	It seems Butterbroad did not much like your visit...
Path189b	As soon as you lowered the pistol and left the office, the guards pounced on you... During the interrogation that followed in Butterbroad's office, with the use of the truth drug, you spilled everything.
*	
*	- Well, well... - Butterbroad grimaced. - So Pelengan counterintelligence is digging under us after all... And this fool himself has no idea what he got into. All right, inject him with amnesin and throw him out through the back door!
Path190b	- Very well, I'll tell you. You have no idea what you've stepped into... Of course, we have nothing to do with any drug mafia. The casino serves as a cover for an Earth intelligence operation... Unfortunately, our friends the Faeyans and the Gaalians do not always show sufficient will to cooperate, refusing to give humans access to a number of technologies whose possession would promote peace and parity between the galactic races. This is most regrettable, but we cannot spoil relations with them by stealing their secrets. The Pelengans do it anyway, however, and not without success... Why shouldn't we take advantage of it? We managed to recruit several high-ranking lyakushas and Dzukhallag officers, who now share with us the information obtained by Pelengan intelligence. A casino suits this kind of operation well: Pelengans are gamblers, and such a weakness is convenient to use in recruitment...
Path191	Shoot back
Path192	Use your brain
Path192b	- Wait, wait, guys! - you exclaim, pointing your gun upward. - We're both Earthlings, what good is it if we shoot each other for the Pelengans' delight... I figure that if Dzukhallag's counterintelligence department has sat on your tail, it won't just get off. And if I don't walk out of here, or walk out with a washed brain, that will only strengthen their suspicions. And even if I simply tell Kuakish that everything is clean here, he won't believe it and will send someone else...
*	
*	- He has a point, - Butterbroad agrees, signaling his men to lower their weapons. - So what do you suggest? - he turns to you.
*	
*	- Pay Kuakish back in his own coin. He sent me here, telling me that drugs were being sold in the casino. And if I bring him proof of exactly that version, he will realize he screwed up and that this is plain crime, not politics. Of course, you will still have to wriggle out of the scandal, but that's better than the complete exposure of the operation.
*	
*	- Well, that's an idea! We'll pin it all on that idiot courier who managed to lose government money in our own casino. We'll expose him ourselves and call the Supervision Service ourselves before Kuakish comes down with a search... It will turn out that the small fry were to blame, and the casino administration identified and stopped it in good time. A very, very good idea.
*	
*	- All that remains is to find drugs somewhere, and quickly... - you remark.
*	
*	- Well, that's not a problem!
*	
*	- H-how? You just said you don't deal in drugs?
*	
*	- Of course we don't. But we do have a small stock of dope. For technical purposes. You see, sometimes for recruitment it is enough merely to plant something illegal on the recruit... drugs are ideal for that...
*	
*	Thinking to yourself that the methods of Earth intelligence are not a bit nobler than Dzukhallag's, you wait until another case is brought - this time with dope.
*	
*	- Oh, and one more thing, - Butterbroad remembers. - Kuakish may want to inject you with Revelin - the truth serum... Here, take a neutralizer - one of our latest developments. It has strong side effects, you'll be feverish for a whole day afterward... but what can you do.
*	
*	Bravely enduring that too, you take the new case and head for the exit.
*	
*	- Thank you for your cooperation, - Butterbroad says after you, - and, of course, you understand that all this must be kept quiet... Oh, by the way - have you never wanted to serve in intelligence?
*	
*	- No, - you answer proudly, - I'm a free Ranger.
Path193b	Kuakish opened the case and hissed with disappointment.
*	
*	- Isn't this what you need? - you inquired innocently.
*	
*	- To complete the picture, your testimony is lacking... Let's go to the car.
*	
*	You had barely sat down in the seat when you felt the needle of a syringe pierce your neck.
*	
*	- So-called Revelin, the truth drug, - Kuakish explained kindly. - We need to know everything, even what you noticed only on a subconscious level...
Path194b	- Excuse me, sir, but we do not disclose information about our clients. We have many high-ranking guests, and they would very much dislike it if they learned that we collect, let alone divulge, information about them. I can only advise you unofficially not to try to sit down with the Pelengans... relations between our races are still far from ideal, you understand. When they lose, they blame everything on the Earthlings, and when they win, you don't know where to go to escape their sense of superiority. Oh, and one more thing... I can hint, completely off the record, that it is hardly worth making the acquaintance of that lady at the table by the entrance... No, no, don't turn around, look later. I have seen more than once how she leaves with a man and after a short time returns alone. True, there have never been any complaints, and anyway, whatever happens outside the casino is none of our business...
Path195b	- Excuse me, sir, but we do not disclose information about our clients. We have many high-ranking guests, and they would very much dislike it if they learned that we collect, let alone divulge, information about them. I can only advise you unofficially not to try to sit down with the Pelengans... relations between our races are still far from ideal, you understand. When they lose, they blame everything on the Earthlings, and when they win, you don't know where to go to escape their sense of superiority.
Path196b	The only thought that came into your alcohol-soaked brain was to declare Butterbroad a hostage and demand <Money> credits.
Path198	No, never mind
Path198b	- Well, as you wish. If you need it, you know where to find me. Just bear in mind that the stock of goods is not unlimited...
Path199	Take the sign
Path200	I bet on the first dozen (1-12)!
Path201b	Hooray! You won!
Path202b	Hooray! You won!
Path203b	Alas! Your money went to your lucky opponents...
Path204b	Hooray! You won!
Path205b	Hooray! You won!
Path206b	Holding your breath, you watch the roulette wheel spin, and at last the ball drops into one of the pockets...
Path207b	The game is on, the game is on...
Path208-par1-crit	Unfortunately, you did not manage to place a bet. Morning has come, and the casino is closing!
Path209-par1-crit	Unfortunately, you did not manage to place a bet. Morning has come, and the casino is closing!
Path210	150
Path211	I bet on... on... at random!!!
