QuestDescription	<Ranger>, we need your help. On the planet <ToPlanet> of the <ToStar> star system our scientists have discovered a sarcophagus. This is an extremely important find for archaeology, but for further research we need a specialist in the languages of the Goshi. As a representative of the Gaalian race, you are sufficiently familiar with the runes of this culture and can help us in our research. But hurry. The expedition is packing up in <Day> days.
QuestSuccessGovMessage	Congratulations, <Ranger>! You have successfully completed the task and contributed to the progress of scientific research. According to preliminary estimates, this discovery will make it possible to increase the amount of energy produced tenfold. In this connection, the chairman of the scientific society and our prime minister personally express their gratitude to you. In addition, a bonus of <Money> cr has already been transferred to your personal account.
Par1-1	Parameter No. 1: <>
Par2-1	Parameter No. 2: <>
Par3-1	Parameter No. 3: <>
Par4-1	Parameter No. 4: <>
Par5-1	Parameter No. 5: <>
Par6-1	Parameter No. 6: <>
Par7-1	Parameter No. 7: <>
Loc1-1	Strangely enough, no one was there to meet you outside. People were scurrying back and forth, hauling boxes and logs, studying printouts, calculating something on xenocalculators, making a racket - no one paid you the slightest attention.
*	Standing in the middle of all this bustle, you were considering your next steps. But fate decided everything for you: a short bald man with a notepad came up to you and asked gloomily:
*	- <Ranger>? You're rather late. Oh well. Allow me to introduce myself: Prezhevalski, director of this expedition. So then. We are short of time, so we must get to work immediately. Your top priority is to translate the printouts of the ancient runes we have copied from the sarcophagus. - The man handed you a thick stack of papers with photographs and text. - Settle down in that yellow tent over there and take your time with the translation. As soon as you finish, let me know. And now excuse me - I'm in a great hurry.
*	With these words the disheveled director vanished into the bustling crowd, leaving you alone with your thoughts.
Loc2-1	We discovered this sarcophagus several weeks ago: a group of archaeologists went on a short hike through the local jungle in the hope of finding something worthwhile on this planet, and unexpectedly stumbled upon an ancient Goshi tomb surrounded by a thick stone wall. Inside they found only a stone sarcophagus covered with runes. The archaeologists' joy knew no bounds. They immediately reported the find to the base, and two days later work around the tomb was in full swing...
*	We studied the tomb for a long time and came to the conclusion that this is not just the burial place of one of the chiefs. It is something special. The sarcophagus itself is a large stone coffin with six recesses. Next to it, in a small box, we found six spheres with runes. Perhaps they are somehow connected with the sarcophagus. I think it will be clearer to you on the spot what I am talking about.
Loc3-1	At the entrance stood two armed soldiers guarding the way into the tomb. The director gestured for them to step aside and was the first to start down the steps.
*	Down below it was cold and damp. The chamber was lit only by a special kioxile lamp, which gave the tomb an even more mysterious and menacing look. In the middle of the room stood a large stone sarcophagus covered with runes. To the left stood a small stone box with large spheres.
*	The director surveyed the tomb and grinned from ear to ear:
*	- You've never seen anything like it in your life, have you? A real find!
*	- Ye-es... - you said as significantly as you could.
*	- Well then. You work, study it for now. And I have things to do. If you figure out how to open the sarcophagus - call me. Or maybe you can open it yourself? Only don't damage anything. This is a very valuable archaeological find, - said the disheveled director and nimbly ran off upstairs.
Loc4-1	Which rune should you place first?
Loc5-1	Here is the second hollow. Which rune will fit here?
Loc8-1	Which rune should you place fifth?
Loc9-1	The last hollow and the last rune remain. Now everything will be decided.
Loc10-1	You carefully inserted the last rune and began to wait. Something inside the sarcophagus started to buzz and creak. The noise kept growing, turning into a steady hum.
Loc12-1	The fourth hollow. Which rune will be fourth?
Loc13-1	Hollow number three. Which rune should be here?
Loc14-1	The massive lid of the sarcophagus began to rise slowly, a bright light bursting from under it flooded the chamber, and everyone present involuntarily shielded their eyes.
*	Quickly getting used to the bright light, you went up to the sarcophagus and looked inside. There was no doubt - inside lay ancient scrolls. The excited Prezhevalski was already standing next to you.
*	- Go on, translate. Don't be afraid. You can see right away that the scrolls are in excellent condition, and you won't damage them.
*	Carefully picking up a golden scroll that stood out from all the rest, you unrolled it and began reading it attentively to yourself.
*	A few minutes later it became clear that these scrolls contained the entire scientific base and the entire history of the Goshi. For centuries the priests of the clan had gathered all their experience in this sarcophagus, protected by the mark of the clan - the key of the priests.
Loc15-1	- Quick, over here! Something is happening! - you shouted.
*	The soldiers shouted back to you, and a minute later the tousled director burst into the tomb. Two soldiers came in after him.
*	Meanwhile the hum kept growing, the walls began to shake slightly, small pebbles started falling from the ceiling. The hum turned into a loud din. Now even the floor was shaking. Stones were raining down, hurting badly.
*	- Quick. We're leaving, - one of the soldiers said harshly.
*	Without needing to be told twice, you all quickly ran upstairs. Outside, people were already rushing away from the tomb. The four of you ran away with all your might, leaving the camp behind. A real roar was already spreading through the jungle, your ears were ringing, your head was buzzing.
*	Suddenly a bright light flashed, a tremendous explosion rang out, and you lost consciousness.
*	
*	You came to in a white room. People in white coats were walking around, talking about something. One of them came up to you and said:
*	- This Gaalian was just incredibly lucky: to escape from such an inferno and get off with nothing but bruises. You can discharge him.
*	An hour later you were already outside. To the south you could see a large black crater - all that was left of the camp. To the east, preparations for the expedition's departure were in full swing. Well... You've really made a mess of things.
*	Fortunately, your ship was undamaged and stood quietly in a clearing next to the infirmary. Deciding not to draw attention to yourself and not to cause unnecessary problems, you quickly got into your ship and flew away.
Loc17-1	The ship landed carefully near the expedition's parking area. Unfastening your safety belts and getting up from your seat, you looked out of the porthole.
*	Outside you could see a large tent camp at the foot of a stone tomb. People in gray clothes were scurrying back and forth, studying and measuring something. Ah... Secrets of the past, archaeological expeditions - they had always intrigued you.
*	Suddenly childhood memories came flooding back: your school years, studying the basics of psychobalance and the Great Philosophy in the junior grades, cramming the runes of the ancient Goshi - the things Gaalian children had to study at school! And why on earth did you go on this expedition: with school knowledge you can't translate very much. But it was too late to back out now.
*	With a firm step you went to the exit and pressed the red button. The hydraulic door slowly swung open, and the hold filled with the fresh air of a wild planet.
Loc18-1	- Do you have any questions for me? - the director asked.
Loc19-1	On first examination it turned out that your school knowledge was not enough for a full translation of the runes. So the work progressed slowly and with great effort: you had to apply all your knowledge and wits and put in a mountain of diligence to extract even a grain of useful information from a single paragraph.
*	When you finally tore yourself away from the printouts, you discovered that it was well past midnight outside.
Loc20-1	Gathering your strength, you began writing down the translation of the parable - the only thing you had more or less understood:
*	- A father gathered all his sons, that they might tell him their thoughts on the mark of the clan.
*	Then came the words of the six brothers. You somehow laid them out in a table:
*	
*	First brother: Fire is the second element in importance. And wind shall be the third of the elements.
*	Second brother: Fire blazes only second in the row. And darkness looms black in fourth place.
*	Third brother: Light is the third of all the elements. Water flows steadily in fifth place.
*	Fourth brother: Water comes before all the elements. It must be only in front, in first place. And light is second - it shines and sparkles.
*	Fifth brother: No. Wind blows before all the others. It and no other is in first place. And darkness deserves only to be fourth.
*	Sixth brother: Light illuminates the way in third place. And earth is sixth - the foundation of all the elements.
*	
*	At the end came the father's line: "O my sons, you have spoken only half the truth. Each of you told me the truth only once and lied to me once. But gather your words together and pronounce the mark of our ancestors."
Loc21-1	Generally speaking, the culture of the local Goshi is not very different from the culture of ordinary natives. Shamans, chiefs, idols - all as usual. But once an expedition found some very strange Goshi devices: knives with glowing blades, jewelry blazing with yellow fire. But the astonishing thing was not that the knife blade glows. It was that it has been glowing for more than a thousand years! This put the Goshi among the fairly advanced civilizations of the past. In narrow scientific circles the Goshi even came to be called the civilization of "great energy".
Loc22-1	Brothers... I have worked here for several weeks now, and I don't think this is a family tomb or a place for folk art. The Goshi were not given to parables and fairy tales at all. Most likely the inscription about the brothers is some kind of metaphor or riddle.
Loc23-1	Don't you see! A plasma knife able to work without recharging for a whole millennium - there is no such technology even now. It's simply some kind of magic. Naturally, some influential companies could not ignore this fact. One of them agreed to finance an expensive expedition, and here we are.
*	At first things did not go very well, and they wanted to cut off funding, but then the tomb with this mysterious sarcophagus was found... This find excited everyone so much that rumors spread that the sarcophagus holds the key to all the secrets of the Goshi.
Loc24-1	The director hastily looked through your report, circled some places with a red pen and put the papers on the table.
*	- Well. Very muddled, very muddled... But something is becoming clear after all - there really is something important in this sarcophagus, and we simply must open it. But that may become a dangerous business: the translation speaks of a severe punishment... I think you should examine the tomb directly.
Loc25-1	You slowly walked around the sarcophagus, peering at every line, every rune. It seems you have already translated, or tried to translate, all of this. Here is the introduction, here is the text about the brothers - right above the box with the spheres. By the way - what are these spheres? You carefully took one stone sphere out of the box and examined it cautiously. On it, as on a billiard ball, the rune of earth was inscribed. You carefully put it down on the ground and took the next sphere. So - the rune of light. You took out the third, fourth, fifth, sixth. That's all. Now six spheres with runes lie in a row next to the box: earth, light, fire, darkness, water, wind. Six spheres, six holes in the sarcophagus - obviously, the spheres are the key. The rune spheres must be placed in the recesses in a certain way. But what exactly should the order be? Wait a minute. The text about the brothers: there are six elements, six runes in it too. How did it go?
Loc26-1	- Quick, over here! Something is happening! - you shouted.
*	The soldiers shouted back to you, and a minute later the tousled director burst into the tomb. Two soldiers came in after him.
*	Meanwhile the hum kept growing, the walls began to shake slightly, small pebbles started falling from the ceiling. The hum turned into a loud din. Now even the floor was shaking. Stones were raining down, hurting badly.
*	- Quick. We're leaving, - one of the soldiers said harshly.
*	Without needing to be told twice, you all quickly ran upstairs. Outside, people were already rushing away from the tomb. The four of you ran away with all your might, leaving the camp behind. A real roar was already spreading through the jungle, your ears were ringing, your head was buzzing.
*	Suddenly a bright light flashed, a tremendous explosion rang out, and you lost consciousness.
*	
*	You came to in a white room. People in white coats were walking around, talking about something. One of them came up to you and said:
*	- This Gaalian was just incredibly lucky: to escape from such an inferno and get off with nothing but bruises. You can discharge him.
*	An hour later you were already outside. To the south you could see a large black crater - all that was left of the camp. To the east, preparations for the expedition's departure were in full swing. Well... You've really made a mess of things.
*	Fortunately, your ship was undamaged and stood quietly in a clearing next to the infirmary. Deciding not to draw attention to yourself and not to cause unnecessary problems, you quickly got into your ship and flew away.
Loc27-1	Having finally become hopelessly confused in all these marks, you ended the report with the words: "Unfortunately, this is all that can be translated using current knowledge of Goshi runes." That's all. Printing out the report on paper and signing it, you went outside.
*	Suddenly the disheveled director appeared right in front of you.
*	- Well? Is everything ready? - he asked.
*	- Unfortunately, I managed to translate very little - the Goshi language has not been studied well enough yet, - you answered confusedly, handing the scientist the report.
*	- Well then. Let's go inside.
Loc28-1	"A father gathered all his sons, that they might tell him their thoughts on the mark of the clan."
*	Then came the words of the six brothers:
*	
*	First brother: Fire is the second element in importance. And wind shall be the third of the elements.
*	Second brother: Fire blazes only second in the row. And darkness looms black in fourth place.
*	Third brother: Light is the third of all the elements. Water flows steadily in fifth place.
*	Fourth brother: Water comes before all the elements. It must be only in front, in first place. And light is second - it shines and sparkles.
*	Fifth brother: No. Wind blows before all the others. It and no other is in first place. And darkness deserves only to be fourth.
*	Sixth brother: Light illuminates the way in third place. And earth is sixth - the foundation of all the elements.
*	
*	And then came the father's line: "O my sons, you have spoken only half the truth. Each of you told me the truth only once and lied to me once. But gather your words together and pronounce the mark of our ancestors."
*	
*	Now everything seems to be getting clearer. Obviously, the parable about the brothers is a hint. Now at least there is something to start from.
Loc29-1	"A father gathered all his sons, that they might tell him their thoughts on the mark of the clan."
*	
*	First brother: Fire is the second element in importance. And wind shall be the third of the elements.
*	Second brother: Fire blazes only second in the row. And darkness looms black in fourth place.
*	Third brother: Light is the third of all the elements. Water flows steadily in fifth place.
*	Fourth brother: Water comes before all the elements. It must be only in front, in first place. And light is second - it shines and sparkles.
*	Fifth brother: No. Wind blows before all the others. It and no other is in first place. And darkness deserves only to be fourth.
*	Sixth brother: Light illuminates the way in third place. And earth is sixth - the foundation of all the elements.
*	
*	"O my sons, you have spoken only half the truth. Each of you told me the truth only once and lied to me once. But gather your words together and pronounce the mark of our ancestors."
Loc30-1	"A father gathered all his sons, that they might tell him their thoughts on the mark of the clan."
*	
*	First brother: Fire is the second element in importance. And wind shall be the third of the elements.
*	Second brother: Fire blazes only second in the row. And darkness looms black in fourth place.
*	Third brother: Light is the third of all the elements. Water flows steadily in fifth place.
*	Fourth brother: Water comes before all the elements. It must be only in front, in first place. And light is second - it shines and sparkles.
*	Fifth brother: No. Wind blows before all the others. It and no other is in first place. And darkness deserves only to be fourth.
*	Sixth brother: Light illuminates the way in third place. And earth is sixth - the foundation of all the elements.
*	
*	"O my sons, you have spoken only half the truth. Each of you told me the truth only once and lied to me once. But gather your words together and pronounce the mark of our ancestors."
Loc31-1	"A father gathered all his sons, that they might tell him their thoughts on the mark of the clan."
*	
*	First brother: Fire is the second element in importance. And wind shall be the third of the elements.
*	Second brother: Fire blazes only second in the row. And darkness looms black in fourth place.
*	Third brother: Light is the third of all the elements. Water flows steadily in fifth place.
*	Fourth brother: Water comes before all the elements. It must be only in front, in first place. And light is second - it shines and sparkles.
*	Fifth brother: No. Wind blows before all the others. It and no other is in first place. And darkness deserves only to be fourth.
*	Sixth brother: Light illuminates the way in third place. And earth is sixth - the foundation of all the elements.
*	
*	"O my sons, you have spoken only half the truth. Each of you told me the truth only once and lied to me once. But gather your words together and pronounce the mark of our ancestors."
Loc32-1	"A father gathered all his sons, that they might tell him their thoughts on the mark of the clan."
*	
*	First brother: Fire is the second element in importance. And wind shall be the third of the elements.
*	Second brother: Fire blazes only second in the row. And darkness looms black in fourth place.
*	Third brother: Light is the third of all the elements. Water flows steadily in fifth place.
*	Fourth brother: Water comes before all the elements. It must be only in front, in first place. And light is second - it shines and sparkles.
*	Fifth brother: No. Wind blows before all the others. It and no other is in first place. And darkness deserves only to be fourth.
*	Sixth brother: Light illuminates the way in third place. And earth is sixth - the foundation of all the elements.
*	
*	"O my sons, you have spoken only half the truth. Each of you told me the truth only once and lied to me once. But gather your words together and pronounce the mark of our ancestors."
Loc33-1	"A father gathered all his sons, that they might tell him their thoughts on the mark of the clan."
*	
*	First brother: Fire is the second element in importance. And wind shall be the third of the elements.
*	Second brother: Fire blazes only second in the row. And darkness looms black in fourth place.
*	Third brother: Light is the third of all the elements. Water flows steadily in fifth place.
*	Fourth brother: Water comes before all the elements. It must be only in front, in first place. And light is second - it shines and sparkles.
*	Fifth brother: No. Wind blows before all the others. It and no other is in first place. And darkness deserves only to be fourth.
*	Sixth brother: Light illuminates the way in third place. And earth is sixth - the foundation of all the elements.
*	
*	"O my sons, you have spoken only half the truth. Each of you told me the truth only once and lied to me once. But gather your words together and pronounce the mark of our ancestors."
Loc34-1	"A father gathered all his sons, that they might tell him their thoughts on the mark of the clan."
*	
*	First brother: Fire is the second element in importance. And wind shall be the third of the elements.
*	Second brother: Fire blazes only second in the row. And darkness looms black in fourth place.
*	Third brother: Light is the third of all the elements. Water flows steadily in fifth place.
*	Fourth brother: Water comes before all the elements. It must be only in front, in first place. And light is second - it shines and sparkles.
*	Fifth brother: No. Wind blows before all the others. It and no other is in first place. And darkness deserves only to be fourth.
*	Sixth brother: Light illuminates the way in third place. And earth is sixth - the foundation of all the elements.
*	
*	"O my sons, you have spoken only half the truth. Each of you told me the truth only once and lied to me once. But gather your words together and pronounce the mark of our ancestors."
Loc35-1	You told the director the significance of the find, and he was overjoyed. No wonder - this is a great discovery not only for archaeology, but for the whole Galactic Commonwealth. Now your memory will live on for centuries!
Path2	Go to the tomb
Path2b	- Well then. I think it's time to deal with this sarcophagus up close, - you said.
*	The director nodded in agreement, and you went outside together. Outside, people were still scurrying about: calculating, hauling, measuring - it seemed this bustle would never end. Fortunately, as you approached the tomb, the crowd gradually thinned out.
Path3	Tell me more about the sarcophagus
Path4	Next
Path5	Examine the sarcophagus
Path6	Place the rune of wind
Path7	Place the rune of earth
Path8	Place the rune of water
Path9	Place the rune of light
Path10	Place the rune of fire
Path11	Place the rune of darkness
Path12	Place the rune of fire
Path13	Place the rune of water
Path14	Place the rune of wind
Path15	Place the rune of earth
Path16	Place the rune of light
Path17	Place the rune of darkness
Path18	Place the rune of darkness
Path19	Place the rune of earth
Path20	Place the rune of water
Path21	Place the rune of fire
Path22	Place the rune of wind
Path23	Place the rune of light
Path24	Place the rune of light
Path25	Place the rune of fire
Path26	Place the rune of earth
Path27	Place the rune of darkness
Path28	Place the rune of water
Path29	Place the rune of wind
Path30	Place the rune of wind
Path31	Place the rune of darkness
Path32	Place the rune of fire
Path33	Place the rune of light
Path34	Place the rune of earth
Path35	Place the rune of water
Path36	Place the rune of earth
Path37	Place the rune of fire
Path38	Place the rune of wind
Path39	Place the rune of darkness
Path40	Place the rune of light
Path41	Place the rune of water
Path42	Call the director
Path42b	- Quick, over here! Something is happening! - you shouted.
*	The soldiers shouted back to you, and a minute later the tousled director burst into the tomb. Two soldiers came in after him.
*	Meanwhile the hum kept growing, the walls began to shake slightly, small pebbles started falling from the ceiling. The soldiers fearfully backed away, urging the director and you to leave the tomb. But nothing could frighten Prezhevalski anymore. His eyes were burning.
*	- It has begun... - he whispered under his breath, shaking his fists in the air.
Path44	Go outside
Path45	Go to the yellow tent
Path45b	Pushing your way through the crowd, you finally reached the tent.
*	Inside there was only a sleep capsule, an iron table, a minicomputer and a chair - no luxury. Evidently the people here follow the principle that nothing must distract a scientist. Perhaps that is right.
*	Putting the printouts on the gleaming tabletop and making yourself comfortable, you set to work.
Path46	Go to sleep
Path46b	Waking up in the morning, you sat down at the computer to write a full report on the work done. Your fingers obediently tapped out the beginning of the report: "I have carried out an enormous amount of work translating the Goshi runic inscriptions..."
*	At first the work went briskly, but after a few sentences you realized that you had translated disastrously little. The only thing that was clear: a shaman had hidden the secrets of his knowledge in a certain "giru" box and protected them with the "mark" of the clan. It was also said that anyone who dared to encroach on the great knowledge would be punished. Then came an abyss of completely incomprehensible text, and at the end some parable was written.
Path47	Go inside
Path48	Tell me more about the culture of the local Goshi
Path49	Everything is clear
Path50	What do you think of the parable about the brothers?
Path51	Next
Path52	And you need a whole army of scientists just for some knives?
Path53	Next
Path54	Next
Path55	Recall the text about the brothers
Path56	Open the sarcophagus by brute force
Path56b	You strode up to the sarcophagus and tried to lift the lid with your hands - it didn't work. You gathered all your strength and tried again - it didn't even budge. Looking around, you noticed an iron bar someone had left behind. Taking the tool in your hands, you tried to pry the sarcophagus open with it, but nothing came of it. Finally you began methodically pounding the sarcophagus in one spot, hoping to break through the lid. Now you had chipped through two centimeters, now five. Suddenly the sarcophagus began to hum quietly.
Path57	Next
Path58	Start placing the runes
Path59	Look over the words of the parable
Path60	Next
Path61	Look over the words of the parable
Path62	Next
Path63	Look over the words of the parable
Path64	Next
Path65	Look over the words of the parable
Path66	Next
Path67	Look over the words of the parable
Path68	Next
Path69	Look over the words of the parable
Path70	Next
Path71	Tell the director everything
Path72	All right. I remember the text. Time to start placing the runes
