QuestDescription	Yes, <Ranger>, we do have an interesting proposal for you. A ranger that we know told us that you were an excellent cook. So, there will be a pizza cooking tournament on the planet of <ToPlanet> of the <ToStar> system. The "Pizza-hack" restaurant chain sponsors the tournament. We would very much like this chain to include our planet as well. In order to facilitate that a representative of our planet won one of the three first places in this tournament. All participants must report to the tournament committee on the planet of <ToPlanet> not later than <Date>. If you agree to represent us at the competition and take one of the three first prizes we will pay you a fee of <Money> cr.
QuestSuccessGovMessage	This was truly a brilliant mission performance, <Ranger>! It's not too easy to get into the hall of fame when some of the best cooks in this Galaxy are competing against you! The Pizza-Hack network is already opening several restaurants on our planet. Oh, talking of which, how would you like becoming a chef in one of them? No? Well, too bad! Okay here is your prize fee of <Money> cr.
Par1-1	1st judge: <clr>Maloq<clrEnd>
Par1-2	1st judge: <clr>Peleng<clrEnd>
Par1-3	1st judge: <clr>Human<clrEnd>
Par1-4	1st judge: <clr>Faeyan<clrEnd>
Par1-5	1st judge: <clr>Gaalian<clrEnd>
Par1-6	1st judge: <clr>Maloq<clrEnd>, rate [p2]
Par1-7	1st judge: <clr>Peleng<clrEnd>, rate [p2]
Par1-8	1st judge: <clr>Human<clrEnd>, rate [p2]
Par1-9	1st judge: <clr>Faeyan<clrEnd>, rate [p2]
Par1-10	1st judge: <clr>Gaalian<clrEnd>, rate [p2]
Par3-1	2nd judge: <clr>Maloq<clrEnd>
Par3-2	2nd judge: <clr>Peleng<clrEnd>
Par3-3	2nd judge: <clr>Human<clrEnd>
Par3-4	2nd judge: <clr>Faeyan<clrEnd>
Par3-5	2nd judge: <clr>Gaalian<clrEnd>
Par3-6	2nd judge: <clr>Maloq<clrEnd>, rate [p4]
Par3-7	2nd judge : <clr>Peleng<clrEnd>, rate [p4]
Par3-8	2nd judge : <clr>Human<clrEnd>, rate [p4]
Par3-9	2nd judge : <clr>Faeyan<clrEnd>, rate [p4]
Par3-10	2nd judge : <clr>Gaalian<clrEnd>, rate [p4]
Par5-1	3rd judge: <clr>Maloq<clrEnd>
Par5-2	3rd judge: <clr>Peleng<clrEnd>
Par5-3	3rd judge: <clr>Human<clrEnd>
Par5-4	3rd judge: <clr>Faeyan<clrEnd>
Par5-5	3rd judge: <clr>Gaalian<clrEnd>
Par5-6	3rd judge: <clr>Maloq<clrEnd>, rate [p6]
Par5-7	3rd judge: <clr>Peleng<clrEnd>, rate [p6]
Par5-8	3rd judge: <clr>Human<clrEnd>, rate [p6]
Par5-9	3rd judge: <clr>Faeyan<clrEnd>, rate [p6]
Par5-10	3rd judge: <clr>Gaalian<clrEnd>, rate [p6]
Par7-1	4th judge: <clr>Maloq<clrEnd>
Par7-2	4th judge: <clr>Peleng<clrEnd>
Par7-3	4th judge: <clr>Human<clrEnd>
Par7-4	4th judge: <clr>Faeyan<clrEnd>
Par7-5	4th judge: <clr>Gaalian<clrEnd>
Par7-6	4th judge: <clr>Maloq<clrEnd>, rate [p8]
Par7-7	4th judge: <clr>Peleng<clrEnd>, rate [p8]
Par7-8	4th judge: <clr>Human<clrEnd>, rate [p8]
Par7-9	4th judge: <clr>Faeyan<clrEnd>, rate [p8]
Par7-10	4th judge: <clr>Gaalian<clrEnd>, rate [p8]
Par9-1	5th judge: <clr>Maloq<clrEnd>
Par9-2	5th judge: <clr>Peleng<clrEnd>
Par9-3	5th judge: <clr>Human<clrEnd>
Par9-4	5th judge: <clr>Faeyan<clrEnd>
Par9-5	5th judge: <clr>Gaalian<clrEnd>
Par9-6	5th judge: <clr>Maloq<clrEnd>, rate [p10]
Par9-7	5th judge: <clr>Peleng<clrEnd>, rate [p10]
Par9-8	5th judge: <clr>Human<clrEnd>, rate [p10]
Par9-9	5th judge: <clr>Faeyan<clrEnd>, rate [p10]
Par9-10	5th judge: <clr>Gaalian<clrEnd>, rate [p10]
Par11-1	Parameter # 14: <>
Par12-1	Parameter # 15: <>
Par13-1	Parameter # 16: <>
Par14-1	Parameter # 17: <>
Par15-1	Pizza thickness: <>
Par15-crit	After you added the last component your pizza started to look like the Pisa Tower. One careless movement and the tower crumbled down. While you were trying to rebuild your pizza back together the tournament was over. You left the planet of <ToPlanet> failing the mission.
Par16-1	Pizza calories: <>
Par17-1	Pizza meatness: <>
Par18-1	Pizza fishness: <>
Par19-1	Pizza vegginess: <>
Par20-1	Pizza exoticness: <>
Par21-1	Pizza estheticness: <>
Par22-1	Audience support: <>%
Par23-1	Your money: <> cr
Par25-1	Could eat an elephant
Par25-2	You are not very hungry
Par25-3	You refreshed the inner man
Par25-4	You've had your fill
Par25-5	You almost fed up
Par25-6	You are about to burst
Par25-crit	After you sent the last bit in down to your stomach you felt you were full. The stomach became heavy as a stone. You grew quite pale and froze still. The waiter noticed something was wrong and jumped up to you: 
*	
*	- Can I help you, sir? 
*	
*	Seeing no response on your side, the waiter figured you choked on a pip, and tapped you helpfully on the back. That was when you poor stomach could not take it anymore. Several seconds later everything that you'd just ate was on the table - a truly ugly sight. 
*	
*	This smelled like an international scandal. Puking out an eaten pizza was considered a very impolite gesture on the planet of <ToPlanet>. You were facing the danger of incarceration for an uncertain term. 
*	
*	You quickly jumped from behind the table, paid your check and rushed out of the restaurant. Running away, you heard the approaching sound of police car sirens.
Par26-1	Credit: <> cr
Par27-1	Judge № <> is corrupted
Par28-1	Your sum: <>
Par29-1	MAIN COMPETITORS:
Par30-1	Viro Nulph: <>
Par31-1	Gluck O'Naate: <>
Par32-1	Bit Bitey: <>
Loc1-1	Anyone who'd arrive to the planet of <ToPlanet> at this time, couldn't but notice the general excitement. Right at the spaceport you were met by a funny Maloq who was dressed like a kitchen-boy, a shit-eating grin on his face. He walked up to you and put a huge bagel and a sign around your neck which read <clr>"Chef<clrEnd> <Ranger><clr>"<clrEnd>. The next second a loud advertisement shot you right through the ear:
*	
*	- The <clr> "Pizza-Hack" <clrEnd> restaurant chain sponsors the tournament! Each tournament participant is given a <clr>100<clrEnd> cr coupon valid in all "Pizza-Hack" restaurants.
*	
*	You covered your ears although you still liked the coupon bit. Even more so since the <clr>"Pizza-Hack" Restaurant<clrEnd> ultra-neon sign was flashing just nearby. Might as well go and have something to eat since you won't be able to cash your coupon anyway.
Loc3-1	The entrance of the <clr>"Grand Cocktail"<clrEnd> palace was crowded. The poster on the facade read in capitals: <clr>"WELCOME THE BEST CHEFS OF THE GALAXY!!!"<clrEnd> The sign below it read <clr>"Freedom and pizzas for all!!! Tournament Sponsor: "Pizza-Hack"<clrEnd>. 
*	
*	A crowd whose attention was attracted by a performance of a famous Peleng show-ballet "Zhvirklatz" and their inimitable erotic dance "Seducing the Virgin" surrounded the extravagant podium. This was truly a breathtaking sight.
*	
*	Gravihover-limousines kept pulling up at the palace in numbers, with all kinds of cinema and stereo-vision celebrities famous all over the Galaxy. A young reporter of a local stereovision channel - Chill Doughnut'puke - ran up to you and started asking questions:
*	
*	- I see you are going to participate in this year's Pizza Tournament! Who do you represent at the competition?
Loc4-1	You opened the menu on the page that read <clr>"Regular Meals"<clrEnd>.
Loc4-2	The waiter brought in a monster of a mug filled to the brim with punch with a thin straw in it. Throwing away the unnecessary item, you started gulping up the punch straight from the mug. At that you had to stop for breath.
*	
*	Once you killed the punch, to your greatest surprise, you noticed you were hungry again.
Loc4-3	You remembered hearing something about this planet called Earth, where they had these farms where they bred this special monkey breed - the fluffy baboon. These monkeys were said to be extremely talented. They know how to read, write, paint and play up to ten musical instruments. This is why it is considered, that the brain of these poor creatures could increase the intellectual abilities of those who eat it. 
*	
*	This belief comes from the ancient times of the Voodoo Sect that was spreading on the Earth back in the 20th century. Nonetheless the tests that were held on Maloq-volunteers, indeed proved that the group of Maloqs who was regularly fed the baboon brains, had an intellectual coefficient one point above those only ate beans. As a result of this experiment the Maloqs of the advanced group learned to count to five, whilst the rest could only count to four. You also decided to try this famous delicacy and ordered it.
*	
*	The still steaming monkey brain was served immediately. It even seemed to you that you'd heard a monkey-like scream somewhere outside the restaurant. Having tried a couple of spoons you suddenly started remembering why was it that you were here on planet <ToPlanet>.
Loc4-4	The waiter smiled helpfully and rushed to place your order. 
*	
*	The beef stake was soaked in blood and covered with ashes. It's been a long time since you last saw a sight so bloody. You tried to take a bite but did not manage. You took the knife. You sawed the beef stake with the knife until, the waiter brought in an axe. Having finally chopped the stake into pieces you felt quite tired. 
*	
*	Everything around you was splattered with blood and stake pieces. You sunk your teeth into these delicious bits and started chewing. After half an hour of intense jaw-work, you figured those were easier to swallow in whole bits.
Loc4-5	- Sire, - the waiter disappeared somewhere in the depths of the restaurant.
*	
*	Five minutes later he brought in a tray, with some nice-looking dish on it. The dish was made in the shape of a large sea-shell, with eyes of some sea crab-like creature. All of this was neatly decorated with swamp algae and graciously scattered with white worms, who were still alive. The worms, apparently, served as a spice to this delicacy.
*	
*	You picked the biggest escargot and started eating. "I hope these worms do not gnaw a hole in my stomach" - you thought to yourself taking another bite.
Loc4-6	After this long flight you felt you were lacking vitamins. The salad of fresh vegetables and fruit was just what you needed. In fact the Faeyan largely feed off neon and minerals, but lately, due to the general exhaustion of resources on the majority of asteroids they taught themselves to eat regular food as well. You placed your order and leaned back in your chair. Some time later you heard somebody stabbing the cabbage. You wouldn't have mistaken that sound for anything. Back in the times when you were a little boy, running barefoot about your native village, you'd often see peasants stabbing the cabbage in their backyards. What a wonderful reminiscence!
Loc10-1	Nice quiet music played inside the "Pizza-Hack" restaurant. The ultra-photon lamps, built into the walls and ceiling, produced a soft light, creating a coy home-like atmosphere. It was not too crowded. The diners were in the absolute majority idle representatives of the local elite, plus you noticed several girls - apparently of a very frivolous character - in the far corner of the hall. The prostates were having some wild conversation accompanied with a lot of gestures. 
*	
*	You picked a free table and sat back. A quick waiter popped up from somewhere under the table and served you the menu. Choices-choices... Finally you stopped at the page that read <clr>"Pizzas"<clrEnd>.
Loc10-2	You opened the menu at the page that read <clr>"Pizzas"<clrEnd>.
Loc10-3	They did not serve Gaalian pizzas on all planets. The trouble with them was that these pizzas contained some <clr>rare exotic components<clrEnd>, that in some cases would cause narcotic intoxication. This effect was also partly due to the <clr>low calorie containing<clrEnd> of Gaalian pizzas. Well, this way or other, you felt like you wanted to try this exotic dish under a glass cap. 
*	
*	Once you opened the cap you were stunned with the beauty and <clr>estheticness<clrEnd> of this pizza: the components <clr>of different colours<clrEnd> contrasted with each other, forming rainbow-like patterns. Looks like the ancient school of Gaalian iike-baanas found its reflection in cooking as well!
*	
*	After the first bite of pizza landed in your stomach you went into a trance. You couldn't tell how long you stayed there. When you came back to normal you truly appreciated the skill of the local chefs who tried to please the Gaalians.
Loc10-4	In fact pizza was something that the Human race initially came up. That is why Human-made pizzas usually had a very <clr>well balanced<clrEnd> taste quality, with some <clr>exoticness<clrEnd> and excellent <clr>aesthetic qualities<clrEnd> (although as far as the aesthetics were concerned the Humans were still a long way from the Gaalians). The <clr>colors<clrEnd> of the components used <clr>contrasted<clrEnd> with each other. You tasted <clr>all kinds of components<clrEnd> - fish, meat, vegetables, and all kinds of exotics too - this was truly one tasty dish. 
*	
*	Indeed, the Humans do know how to cook a pizza! Licking your fingers you call for the water once again.
Loc10-5	The Maloq pizza was fat and thick. <clr>Calories<clrEnd> were literally pouring out of it like a cornucopia. Cutting a slice you felt the taste of <clr>meat<clrEnd> in your mouth. At that <clr> this particular pizza obviously had very little aesthetic or exotic qualities about it<clrEnd>. The main thing for the large Maloqs was obviously providing their systems with the required amount of energy. 
*	
*	Filling yourself to the brim with this meat-and-pastry creation, you once again called the waiter.
Loc10-6	Some time later that waiter brought in something on a tray that looked slightly like pizza. Earlier on the Pelengs used to eat only neon and minerals, and only taught themselves to eat regular food rather a short time ago. However the Faeyans liked their food to be rich with mineral salts, and absolutely <clr>could not stand any meat products<clrEnd>. The Faeyans tastes were fully reflected in their pizza: leaves of salad with some fruit and berries. This <clr>vegetarian<clrEnd> creation looked more like a salad, than pizza. Having tried it, you understood it tasted like that too.
Loc10-7	The Peleng pizza, rather expectedly, was rich with <clr>seafood<clrEnd>. This pizza was multi-layered, with fins and branchiae of all kinds of <clr>sea-dwelling creatures<clrEnd> protruding from all sides. There was also a great deal of <clr>vegetarian<clrEnd> and <clr>exotic<clrEnd> addends, traditional for Peleng cuisine. The top was decorated with baked escargots and colourful worms. <clr>No aesthetics<clrEnd> whatsoever. Cutting a slice that had less worms, you treated yourself to this masterpiece of Peleng cooking art.
Loc21-1	The hall, where the competition for the Galaxy's best pizza cook was to be held, was overcrowded. The spectators cheered and made constant "waves". Because of that noise you could hardly make out the names of the jury, that was to assess the pizzas. 
*	
*	Then they read out the rules of the competition. These were mainly concerned about the principles of fair play, but there was also one important technical rule: <clr>the thickness of the pizza was to be 10-20 units<clrEnd>. 
*	
*	The musicians played the anthems of races and organisations - participants of the competition. Instantly the hall went silent and everyone stood up. When they got to  "Glory-glory to the fearless rangers of the Galaxy", you shed a tear. Chary masculine tears ran down your unshaven cheek. Most naturally you didn't know the words of the anthem so you just opened your mouth to the music. Following that, the veterans of previous Pizza tournaments who came with all kinds of nonsense about traditions and succession assailed the scene. 
*	
*	At this moment you spotted a Peleng standing behind a column, who was giving you signals of some sort.
Loc22-1	You ignored the signs of the Peleng and stoically waited to the end of the official part. Finally you along with a couple of dozens of other participants - representatives of different races - were invited to the scene. 
*	
*	You stood at your table, whereupon lay the basis for your pizza - a <clr>yellow<clrEnd> flat cake of puff pastry. A fat Maloq clad in a chef-cap hit the gong and announced the start of the tournament.
*	
*	In front of you there are all kinds of potential pizza components laid out on carts and in boxes. The components are divided by categories. Your choice?
Loc22-2	Giving the Peleng <clr>1000<clrEnd> cr, you went back to the hall. Just at that moment you along with a couple of dozens of other participants - representatives of different races - were invited to the scene. 
*	
*	You stood at your table, whereupon lay the basis for your pizza - a <clr>yellow<clrEnd> flat cake of puff pastry. A fat Maloq clad in a chef-cap hit the gong and announced the start of the tournament.
*	
*	In front of you there are all kinds of potential pizza components laid out on carts and in boxes. The components are divided by categories. Your choice?
Loc23-1	You decided to add some protein-rich components to the pizza, thus increasing its calories. Meat and fish from famous manufacturers would be just the right thing.
Loc24-1	Some carbohydrates would increase the calories and at the same time would make animal rights activists happy. The choice of the noble!
Loc25-1	The fruits and vegetables were to soften and brighten up the taste of your pizza, and please the vegetarians. The organisers offered a wide selection of those. Although the larger part of the vegetables was water-sprinkled so that they looked nicer.
Loc26-1	Spices usually added little to the actual taste of the pizza, but for some reason or other all the cooks were making a very extensive use of them. Main thing was not to overdo it. Remembering this, you reached out for the colourful boxes and cans that stood on a separate cart.
Loc27-1	The exotic components were separated into a special product category. The use of those made any dish taste original and exotic. All of these components have been delivered by starships from all corners of the Galaxy especially for the tournament. The organisers have surely paid quite a round sum for the lot of them.
Loc28-1	Finally your pizza was ready. It was your sound opinion that your masterpiece had all the necessary components in required quantities. 
*	
*	You raised a white flag which meant that your pizza was ready to be put in the oven. Many other participants had already similar flags raised over their tables. You dragged your masterpiece to the oven. The anti-gravitation megawave with active absorption system was awaiting your chef-d'oeuvre. Shoving the pizza into the chamber you closed the door and pushed the big red button. Now it was time to wait. 
*	
*	As soon as all the other participants were done with their pizzas, the jury started the degustation. This was the most important part of the tournament. You studied the faces of the judges intensely, trying to make out even the smallest traces of assessment of your masterpiece. Unfortunately it was still hard to tell which of pizzas each member of the jury was tasting at this particular moment of time, so you had to wait for the results at the end of the degustation process. The audience cheered for the participants, blowing the horns, beating the drums, and blowing up the petards. It was very noisy. 
*	
*	You saw a judge fall into a trance after trying one of the pizzas. The audience roared in approval. Another judge all of a sudden went quite pale in the face and started spitting the just eaten pizza onto his colleague, who sat calmly at his side. The spit upon judge punched his unfortunate counterpart right in the eye. A fight broke out. The security tried to pull the raging judges apart. After they'd been taken to the toilet and washed, the degustation continued. 
*	
*	Finally, when the last slice of pizza presented for the trial by the unprejudiced jury was eaten, the judges announced the results. The highest possible mark was <clr>10<clrEnd> points. The winner was determined by the sum of all marks given by the jury.
Loc29-1	Finally the summed results appeared on the table. And sure enough you <clr>won <clrEnd> the first prize!!! The judge announced the results:
*	
*	1st place - ranger <Ranger> who struck [p28] points. Prize - <clr>750<clrEnd> cr.
*	2nd place - Viro Nulph who struck [p30] points. Prize - 500 cr.
*	3rd place - Gluck O'Naate who struck [p31] points. Prize - 250 cr.
*	
*	Thus, quite unexpectedly for yourself you became the best chef in the Galaxy!
*	
*	When all the congratulations and signing sessions were over, you went back to your ship. Now you could go the planet of <FromPlanet> to pickup the promised reward.
Loc29-2	Finally the summed results appeared on the table. And sure enough you <clr>won <clrEnd> the second prize!!! The judge announced the results:
*	
*	1st place - Viro Nulph who struck [p30] points. Prize - 750 cr.
*	2nd place - ranger <Ranger> who struck [p28] points. Prize - <clr>500<clrEnd> cr.
*	3rd place - Gluck O'Naate who struck [p31] points. Prize - 250 cr.
*	
*	Thus, quite unexpectedly for yourself you became the second best chef in the Galaxy!
*	
*	When all the congratulations and signing sessions were over, you went back to your ship. Now you could go the planet of <FromPlanet> to pickup the promised reward.
Loc29-3	Finally the summed results appeared on the table. And sure enough you <clr>won <clrEnd> the third prize!!! The judge announced the results:
*	
*	1st place - Viro Nulph who struck [p30] points. Prize - 750 cr.
*	2nd place - Gluck O'Naate who struck [p31] points. Prize - 500 cr.
*	3rd place - ranger <Ranger> who struck [p28] points. Prize - <clr>250<clrEnd> cr.
*	
*	Thus, quite unexpectedly for yourself you became the third best chef in the Galaxy!
*	
*	When all the congratulations and signing sessions were over, you went back to your ship. Now you could go the planet of <FromPlanet> to pickup the promised reward.
Loc30-1	Finally the summed results appeared on the table. And sure enough you <clr>lost <clrEnd>!!! The judge announced the results:
*	
*	1st place - Viro Nulph who struck [p30] points. Prize - 750 cr.
*	2nd place - Gluck O'Naate who struck [p31] points. Prize - 500 cr.
*	3rd place - Bit Bitey who struck [p32]. Prize - 250 cr.
*	
*	And you only came [p38]th with your pathetic [p28] points. 
*	
*	Stomping your chef-cap into the ground in desperation, you headed back to your ship.
Loc31-1	As it turned out two of the contenders including yourself struck the same amount of points! So how are they going to determine the winner? According to the rules of the tournament, in that case the winner was to be named by the audience. The master of ceremony announces the name of each contender and the winner is determined by the audience's reaction.
*	
*	Your contender started giving you fingers and badmouth you loudly, a common practice among famous fighters before a fair battle. What you reaction will be?
Loc33-1	Finally the master of ceremony took the mike and announced:
*	
*	- Ladies and gentlemen... The first contender... The magnificent and the wonderful... The charming and amazing... Mr....
*	
*	And then the hall exploded!!! The name of your competitor drowned in the roar of the crowd. It was simply unbelievable! The audience screamed and whistled, moaned and groaned, laughed and cried... They lifted the stage off the ground and started shaking it together with the participants. You were scared. You prepared for the worst, when the MC once again took the mike:
*	
*	- And now... The fearless and undefeated... the brave and valorous... the incorruptible and just... Ranger <Ranger>!!!
*	
*	The spectators went silent. There was only a couple of claps. Sure enough you <clr>lost<clrEnd> the fight for the {[p38]-1}th place.  Next time you shouldn't be brushing away the attention of the local reporters.
Loc34-1	Finally the master of ceremony took the mike and announced:
*	
*	- Ladies and gentlemen... The first contender... The magnificent and the wonderful... The charming and amazing... Mr....
*	
*	And then the hall exploded!!! The name of your competitor drowned in the roar of the crowd. The spectators cheered and clapped throwing things on the stage. You were scared. You prepared for the worst, when the MC once again took the mike:
*	
*	- And now... The fearless and undefeated... the brave and valorous... the incorruptible and just... Ranger...
*	
*	And then the hall exploded!!! The master of ceremony could not pronounce your name either. It was simply unbelievable! The audience screamed and whistled, moaned and groaned, laughed and cried... They lifted the stage off the ground and started shaking it together with the participants. Sure enough - <clr>you won<clrEnd>!!!
Loc36-1	- You are a new guy here, aren't you? - the Peleng asked you. - I could help you. I could buy the favour of any judge for you for a laughably small price of  <clr>1000<clrEnd> cr. He will give you the highest possible mark, even if your pizza makes him puke. Unfortunately I can only buy one judge.
*	
*	Your decision?
Loc38-1	You remembered your sum: [p28]. The results of other main contenders started appearing on the table: Viro Nulph (Human) - [p30], Gluck O'Naate (Gaalian) - [p31], Bit Bitey (Peleng) - [p32]. The results of other participants were much lower.
Path2	Go to the tournament
Path3	Visit "Pizza-Hack"
Path4	Beefsteak Maloq-style (10 cr)
Path5	Marinade escargots in pastry (25 cr)
Path6	Eggs with brains and sour cream (20 cr)
Path7	"Home Sweet Home" Faeyan salad (10 cr)
Path8	"Jolly Gaalian" punch (5 cr)
Path9	Open the menu at "Pizzas"
Path10	"King-size" (Maloqs) (25 cr)
Path11	"Seafood" (Pelengs) (20 cr)
Path12	"Stunning" (Humans) (20 cr)
Path13	"Vegetarian" (Faeyans) (15 cr)
Path14	"Heavenly" (Gaalians) (20 cr)
Path16	Open the menus at "Standard Meals"
Path28	Hey dude, get lost. I am not really into interviews today
Path30	I am representing the planet of <FromPlanet>!
Path30b	- Where is this planet? - looks like this Doughnut'puke only made it through prep school. It took you a while to explain to this extravagant reporter where the <FromPlanet> planet exactly was. Sure enough a lengthy monologue like that could irritate the impatient audience, although your own tolerance was nothing but admirable.  
*	
*	- Is it your first time at a competition like that? - next question followed.
Path32	In fact it's going to be the first time I am making a pizza!
Path32b	Doughnut'puke's face formed into a surprised grimace:
*	
*	- Well, in that case we can only wish you the best of luck, ranger <Ranger>! 
*	
*	It is common knowledge that brave newbies often receive approval from the audience, but approval is yet far from being popular... 
*	
*	From the corner of your eye you spotted a large screen right at the entrance to the hotel and yourself in it. Looks like you interview has just been aired! The crowd of spectators that watched you on the large stereovision exploded after your last remark. Cheers and applause mixed with booing and laughter went on a while. Apparently you were becoming popular after all! 
*	
*	Congratulating yourself on a good start you stepped inside the palace.
Path35	This will not be the first time when I show whose the master around here!
Path35b	The response was as provoking, as it could get. But at that point of time emotion won over self-control, so you only had to hope that the audience would get you right. Chill was still there in your face:
*	
*	- Anther question, if I may, of course. How do you feel before the fight?
Path37	Refuse the Peleng services
Path38	Meat, fish
Path39	Carbohydrates
Path40	Veggies, fruit
Path41	Spices
Path42	Exotic components
Path43	Send the pizza into the oven
Path44	Parm ham, sliced
Path44b	The Parm ham has been known around the Galaxy since penchekryak knows when. Everyone save for Faeyans, who were ardent environmentalists, liked this ancient food from the planet of Earth. The local ham, produced by <clr>"Eat-me-not"<clrEnd>
*	 was  of <clr>red<clrEnd> colour, with a touch of rot. You put a couple of rashers on your pizza, looked critically at it form all sides, and remained content with the results.
Path45	Dry cod
Path45b	The cod was most-positively over-dried. That was the downside of the ultra-modern processing technologies. The undervacuum smoke-ovens definitely spoiled the initial properties of fish. 
*	
*	You tore the plastic apart and produced the dry <clr>yellow<clrEnd> pieces of what used to bear the proud name of fish not so long ago.
Path46	Mutton blade
Path46b	They only had real rams left in the famous zoo of <clr>"MicroWorld"<clrEnd> back on Earth, which was still headed by the famous uncle Bill. All other rams in the Galaxy were clones of famous breeds. After trying this bright-<clr>red<clrEnd> meat, all you could do was hope that you will not suffer from some irreversible mutations, although it did contain lots of calories.
Path47	Fresh deepwater squids
Path47b	You felt like your creation could really use a touch of fish. Your attention was caught by a transparent package from which the bulging eyes of some sea creature stared at you. While you tried to extract the <clr>white<clrEnd> slick bodies out of the packet, they started deteriorating right in your hands. Their tentacles fell off, eyes fell out and rolled under the table. You spent some time putting them back together and into the pizza.
Path48	Sowbelly
Path48b	Nothing increases the calories of a pizza like sowbelly! This is the basic truth. Without giving it much thought you reached out for the <clr>white<clrEnd> appetising slices, which looked quite yummy.
Path49	Gutted herring
Path49b	The barrel with herrings stood nearby. You rolled up your sleeves and started fishing out the right erm... fish. Despite your expectations the herring was not gutted. The point was that the local manufacturers stood firm on their belief that a herring must only be gutted just before eating. So now you had to take care of it. This took some time, besides a very characteristic smell started spreading across the room. The audience was delighted.
*	
*	Finally the neat <clr>brown<clrEnd> pieces landed on top of your pizza.
Path50	Jerbooster tenderloin from Arnarique Goudad
Path50b	The Maloq planet of Arnarique Goudad has always been known for its jerboosters. About half of the planet's population picked poor jerbooster hunting as their day-job. As a result the jerbooster meat export makes about 50 percent of the planet's bulk sales. This meat of exotic <clr>green<clrEnd> colour is well known to all of the inhabitants of the Galaxy.
Path52	Potatoes, chopped
Path52b	Potatoes as vegetables under different names and of different varieties are grown pretty much everywhere in the Galaxy. This is one of the main agricultural products there is there. 
*	
*	Unfortunately the organisers did not give themselves the trouble of peeling the tubers before the tournament. A bucket full of dirty potatoes stood at the side. You picked a couple of those, took a pan of water and started peeling the tubers supported by loud cheering. Soon the yum-looking <clr>yellow<clrEnd> circles decorated your pizza.
Path53	Mashed peas
Path53b	The lack of vegetarian and excess of high-calorie products can be easily compensated with <clr>green<clrEnd> peas. For several past centuries mashed peas have been produced in tubes and would often be used by astronauts in long flights. The warning on the tube reads: <clr>"Do not eat prior to important meetings"<clrEnd>.
Path54	Parmesan cheese
Path54b	Cheeses have always been an indispensable component of any pizza, and Parmesan was definitely one of the best sorts. But it just happened so that on this very planet the <clr>yellow<clrEnd> product was never too popular. Apparently that was the reason for a slight touch of rot and a weird crooked shape. 
*	
*	But when you tried a bite, you understood, that despite all the cheese was still as good as fresh.
Path55	Ground rusks
Path55b	All dwellers of the Galaxy remembered the famine of 3017. Back then in the times of desperate fighting against the Klissans the Galaxy was going through the 2nd meteorite belt of the Universe, and meteors of all shapes and sizes destroyed crops on all planets of this branch. These were hard times indeed. Since then every planet had enormous store of ground rusks - in case of any unexpected calamity. But the time of unpredictable cataclysms has long passed, and now they needed to somehow spend the unending reserves of dry breadcrumbs. Hence they were listed on the menus of all restaurants on each and every planet.
*	
*	Generously your covered you pizza with <clr>brown<clrEnd> bread powder.
Path56	Corn cakes
Path56b	Corn is a high-calorie and a very important agricultural product. Semi-readies with a proud brand <clr>"Corn Forever"<clrEnd> were stacked in a neat stash and looked like a <clr>yellow<clrEnd> tower of Pisa. The bottom-most cake looked just right to you. You pulled it out and several dozens of cakes rolled all over the scene. The next 30 minutes were spent in futile attempts to collect the cakes back in a tower accompanied by the enthusiastic laughter of the audience.
Path57	"Macaroni" noodles
Path57b	You knit an intricate noodle pattern on top of the pizza. The <clr>white<clrEnd> knotwork looked a lot like the most sophisticated Celtic patterns ever to appear in the Galaxy.
Path58	Margarine with preservatives
Path58b	Your attention was caught by a small glass can of <clr>yellow<clrEnd> colour. Lots of calories and little thickness - just what you needed! Prior to applying the margarine onto the pizza you decided to read the contents: processed oil waste succus - 50%, hydrolizers - 20%, stabilisers - 10%, rest - dairy and meat industry waste treatment products. Beautiful! This definitely was the most ecologically clean margarine in the entire Galaxy!
Path60	Mango (pulp)
Path60b	The mango pulp smelled of fresh paint. Bright sun, tender sea, tanned birds - these were the thoughts provoked by the sight of these ripe and juicy fruits of <clr>red<clrEnd> colour, even those who'd never seen mango, sea, or tanned birds would still think all these things after one look at these fruits... Lost in daydreaming you didn't notice how you stepped into your neighbour's pizza. Mumbling a humble apology you carefully reassembled the creation of your brother-in-forks and patted it back together.
Path61	Crated coconut
Path61b	The coconuts in the basket were fresh from the palm-tree and not grated at all. Right by the bucket there stood a short round-headed poor-looking Maloq. As they've explained to you before the start of the competition, this very round head was to be used to crash the coconuts. This was called to give the tournament a touch of zest. You picked a nut, aimed carefully, but instead of hitting the Maloq's forehead you hit him right into the eye. The public roared in approval. On second attempt you did crack the nut open revealing the longed-for <clr>white<clrEnd> pulp. Indeed the organisers were right there - that was one heck of a show!
Path62	Bamboo sprouts
Path62b	The <clr>green<clrEnd> sprout of bamboo were marinated in three-litre cans.  The can opener lay nearby. The organisers did their best to provide the tournament with the most elite products available on the market. Only the riches and the most biased gourmets would use such an ancient way of food storage.
Path63	Fresh cucumber
Path63b	These vegetables were very popular with the folks all over the Galaxy. For the most part they were served as a marinated appetiser to all kinds of liquor and were generally known as <clr>"pickled cucumbers"<clrEnd>. But a fresh cucumber was also a welcome addition in any sort of elite dish. 
*	
*	The cucumbers were piled in a basket and you noticed that pretty much all of the participants had already taken at least one cucumber for their pizzas. The contents of the basket was diminishing swiftly. You also snatched a yum-looking <clr>green<clrEnd> vegetable and planted it down onto your pizza.
Path64	Dried tomatoes
Path64b	What kind of pizza would it be without <clr>red<clrEnd> tomatoes? The modern method of production of dried tomatoes reserved from the use latest technologies. In fact the vegetables were dried out under natural conditions in basements through extended periods of storage. Constant temperature and humidity levels were kept in the basements. They say this technology was originally taken from an ancient Egyptian race of planet Earth - the Egyptians used to make mummies of their Pharaohs using a similar method.
Path65	Beans
Path65b	This kind of food was extremely popular in the densely populated worlds of the Galaxy. Beans were the cheapest kind of food available, and could easily feed a fast-growing population of many planets. The latest achievements in agriculture allowed to grow beans even on asteroids. Of all the vegetables only the <clr>brown<clrEnd> beans had a decent calorie-rate.
Path66	Local zucchini
Path66b	The zucchinis were spread all over the Galaxy by some terrorists. They started procreating rapidly and soon were occupying all the uninhabited territories. On some of the planets the plant has even been announced a weed, and had a national war waged on it. Each citizen, destroying a zucchini and providing a trophy, was awarded a certain sum of money. However the smartest thing to do was not to battle, but rather make friends with this excellent plant and its <clr>yellow<clrEnd> fruit. This was why zucchini became appearing on the menus of different restaurants more and more often, although they were not really useful or nutritious.
Path68	Estragon mustard
Path68b	Estragon was used to rub the private parts of Taron stallions before long-distance runs. Estragon was also used to make excellent mustard. The <clr>yellow<clrEnd> can was made in the shape of a horse.
Path69	Aromatic greens
Path69b	Your attention was caught by a bright green box, that stood right in the centre of the cart with spices. The box read - <clr>"The freshest and the most aromatic greens in the Galaxy"<clrEnd>. You opened the box. To your great surprise the contents revealed some dark-<clr>green<clrEnd> powder. Oh well - modern technologies!
Path70	Pumpkin seeds
Path70b	A friend from Earth told you once that back on this planet they eat pumpkin seeds on every corner, and the husks of the seeds literally pave the streets. "Well, these <clr>green<clrEnd> seeds might as well improve the taste of the pizza ", - you figured.
*	
*	Only that, how do you use them, husked or not? Contemplating the new problem you started eating the seeds and, without really noticing it, spat a whole pile of husks into your neighbour's pizza. The neighbour was a huge Maloq so you could only hope that he would not notice anything.
Path71	Rusk sauce
Path71b	In order to get rid of the endless reserves of rusks stored in case of famine, a certain Peleng craftsman named Lyakusha Steeveenzon came up with an original sauce recipe. The fulminating <clr>brown<clrEnd> mixture of rusks, sawdust, and food product waste was packed in nice-looking cans and was passed off as spices.
Path72	Ground fish bones
Path72b	The research in the field of new nutrients resulted in grinding and crumbling everything that could possibly be ground and crumbled. The <clr>white<clrEnd> powder which looked slightly like lime, was none other than the favourite spice of one of the Galaxy races.
Path73	Vinegar (100%)
Path73b	When you poured some vinegar onto your pizza, it produced an odd hissing sound and started foaming. After the foam settled in, you noticed that all of the components on top of your creation have become <clr>red<clrEnd>. That's some serious spicing, this one!
Path74	Smoke-smell essence
Path74b	This <clr>brown<clrEnd> spice made of processed meat waste was packed in flasks that looked a bit like a famous deodorant for men. Thanks to its unusual and rather nice smell a lot of folks would actually use it as deodorant.
Path76	Portobello mushrooms
Path76b	The poisonous <clr>green<clrEnd> Portobello mushrooms could be made eatable if processed in the right way. However, one or two could still remain lethally toxic. This made dishes with these mushrooms especially piquant. Anyone who ate them was risking their very lives and would not know whether they'd live to take the next bite. This produced a burst of adrenaline and much excitement. Some folks would even start hallucinating after eating these mushrooms, which is why they were also considered a controlled substance.
Path77	Royal crab claws
Path77b	In order for a crab to be considered royal its claws must have been longer than 2 meters. These monsters were bred at special farms in the open ocean. Due to the poor ecological situation very few crabs would grow to such gargantuan size.
*	
*	With much difficulty did you break off a relatively small piece of the huge <clr>red<clrEnd> claw that lay in the middle of the scene.
Path78	Fresh brain, packed
Path78b	The <clr>white<clrEnd> brains of a special macaque breed were truly a gourmet dish. Only the real judges of ancient cuisine could truly appreciate their unusual taste. Although eating the macaques was prohibited, the brains could still be ordered in many of the Galaxy's restaurants.
Path79	Bourbon
Path79b	The favourite swill of the Rangers. It has become so popular, that the rangers managed to devastate almost all of the reserves of this liquor on Earth. The consumption grew especially high during active combat. As a result <clr>Bourbon<clrEnd> has become a very exotic product. Opening the all too familiar bottle you started pouring its <clr>brown<clrEnd> contents onto the pizza.
Path80	Pearl onion
Path80b	This unique product was lying under a cap in a special glass unit. Right next to it there was a detailed instruction on correct extraction and use of the unusual plant. You started reading. After 30 minutes of reading, it dawned on you that it was heaps easier to simply break the glass and snatch the onion, which you did to the greatest delight of the audience. Taking the <clr>white<clrEnd> onion, you chopped it into the pizza.
Path81	Yong boar saddle
Path81b	The saddle of a young boar was only presented at the tournament in one copy. It was put onto a separate cart and occupied more place scene than anything else. Giving it some thought, you decided to be the first one to use this extremely exotic component. Grabbing the saddle with both hands you somehow managed to lift it off the cart. Accompanied by the roar of the audience, you dragged the saddle to your table. The crowd roared in awe. After you planted the <clr>red<clrEnd> saddle on top of the pizza, it has become much thicker. Now it was looking a little like a rider-less horse.
Path82	Monstrodile liver oil
Path82b	A monstrodile was a very rare beast that could only be found very deep in the ocean. According to the latest scientific researches its liver could even digest metallic items, such as say the hull of a bathyscaph. The unique <clr>brown<clrEnd> oil, which it produced, had rich sapping properties. Some even considered that this oil had a rejuvenating effect - one year per one gram of oil approx. You grabbed the bottle and generously sprinkled the pizza with this precious product.
Path83	Other type of products
Path87	Show him a tongue
Path87b	You showed your huge tongue, as a response to the verbal attack of your opponent. He pulled on a face and called you some rude word, which you could not even make out at first. Continuing to grimace and calling each other names, you waited for the master of ceremony to begin the announcements
Path88	Wait for the audience's judgement
Path89	Do nothing
Path89b	You gave him your best ear-to-ear grin, showing the opponent that his tongue-lashing meant little to you, and that you indeed were above that. What you did forget was that you just recently went to a dentist who'd pulled out two of your front teeth. Once you remembered it, you quickly closed your mouth and stood there, nose up in the air.
Path91	Pull down your pants and give the opponent a "full-moon".
Path91b	This exotic move had different meanings among different races. Apparently, back in the home-system of your opponent it was used to demonstrate maximum possible respect, since the guy quickly stopped his verbal attacks and stood still. Then he turned around, full-mooned you back, and thus settling the quarrel, you two started waiting for the master of ceremony to deliver the announcements.
Path92	Call him names too
Path92b	In response your opponent grabbed the nearest pizza component left over from the competition and threw it right at you. Judging by the smell that struck you in the nostrils, it were the packed brains of the poor macaques. Not giving it much thought you shot back with a herring. Mutual fire ensued.
*	
*	The components, that were initially supposed to be used in the cooking process, were now flying all over the scene, hitting everyone who stood there. The other participants did not make wait for them too long and joined right in. The spectators applauded in a wild frenzy. 
*	
*	After you ran out of food-projectiles, everyone went calm and waited patiently for the master of ceremony to deliver the announcements. Who will be the winner?
Path98	I am here by myself!
Path98b	- Hmm... - Doughnut'puke seemed disappointed. What will the audience think of you after an answer like that, you wondered? But the reporter proceeded with his questions:
*	
*	- Is this your first time at a tournament like that one?
Path99	I represent the rangers of the Galaxy!
Path99b	You felt proud. You cheeks were slowly turning pink. The larger part of the population liked the rangers. Suddenly you remembered about the badge on your chest that read "<Ranger>, planet <FromPlanet> (<FromStar>)", which totally blew your cover, but since Doughnut'puke did not notice it, maybe the audience will not notice it either? Meanwhile the boring reporter continued:
*	
*	- Is this your first time at a tournament like that one?
Path100	It's a hard question. I feel a bit shy.
Path100b	- Not to worry, you are positively going to make it, we do believe in you, - the reporter decided to cheer you up. Lack of self-confidence would seldom find any support, but modesty was still considered the mother of all virtues. 
*	
*	From the corner of your eye you spotted a large screen right at the entrance to the hotel and yourself in it. Looks like your interview has just been aired! The crowd of spectators that watched you on the large stereovision exploded after your last remark. Cheers and applause mixed with booing and laughter went on a while. Apparently you were becoming popular after all! 
*	
*	Congratulating yourself on a good start you stepped inside the palace.
Path101	Excellent! I'll kick their asses!!!
Path101b	- That was one tough statement! - the reporter was overjoyed. Looks like it was his first interview, and it certainly appeared a success. Although, what will the audience think of your boldness?
*	
*	From the corner of your eye you spotted a large screen right at the entrance to the hotel and yourself in it. Looks like your interview has just been aired! The crowd of spectators that watched you on the large stereovision exploded after your last remark. Cheers and applause mixed with booing and laughter went on a while. Apparently you were becoming popular after all! 
*	
*	Congratulating yourself on a good start you stepped inside the palace.
Path102	Yessir. This is my debut!
Path102b	You decided to be honest. That was your golden rule.
*	
*	- And finally, the last question, - the boring reporter was getting on your nerves, - How does it feel before the battle?
Path103	Competitions of that kind were an alternative to the existing practice of Galaxy-wide global conferences aimed at finding interracial compromises and improving the relations between the nations of all planets.
Path103b	Gracefully you slipped away from a direct answer. Now you had to hope that the government of the planet of  <ToPlanet> did invest into education. The confused reporter continued with his next question:
*	
*	- How does it feel before the battle?
Path106	Leave the restaurant and head for the competition
Path107	Leave the restaurant and head for the competition
Path108	Not pay attention to the Peleng
Path109	Walk up to the Peleng
Path110	Corrupt judge #2
Path111	Corrupt judge #3
Path112	Corrupt judge #4
Path113	Corrupt judge #5
Path114	Corrupt judge #1
Path115	Other type of products
Path116	Other type of products
Path117	Other type of products
Path118	Other type of products
Path120	View the results of other participants
