QuestDescription	Dear ranger <Ranger>, our planet's government was invited to send a representative to take part in the Intergalactic combat robot battle tournament which will take place on the <ToPlanet> planet in the <ToStar> system. We would hate refusing this offer due to diplomatic reasons. But these competitions are very dangerous. The fact that the participants can get killed is an absolutely common thing there but we can't afford risking our people's lives. On the other hand, the victory in this tournament is rather honorific. This is why we need a hireling - a professional fighter. We will pay you an adequate amount, <Money> cr. The last day of the participants' registration is <Date>.
QuestSuccessGovMessage	Our congratulations! All the <FromPlanet>'s population kept their breath listening to the sportscasts from the tournament. Your victory aroused a record patriotic enthusiasm! It was our first victory in such a competition. They have already erected a full-length monument on one of the main capital squares to pay a tribute to you. We hope that popularisation of this sport will help us to bring along talented sportsmen of our own. However, I would recommend you to abridge your visit to our planet and leave immediately: if the fans find out that you are here, you will not be leaving for the next several next years. So if you don't want to welter in endless shows, presentations and horrible advertising shooting, go to the spaceport until the press find out about your arrival.
*	
*	Pardon? Oh, yes, of course, the promised award... Your <Money> cr have already been transferred to your account.
Par1-1	Player's life: <>
Par1-crit	The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Par2-1	Enemy's life: <>
Par3-1	Parameter No 22: <>
Par4-1	Average blaster
Par4-2	Reinforced blaster
Par5-1	Parameter No 5: <>
Par6-1	Average torpedo tube
Par6-2	Reinforced torpedo tube
Par7-1	Your cash: <>
Par9-1	Enemies and their weapons <>
Par10-1	Fights given: <>
Par11-1	Blaster charges: <> pcs.
Par12-1	Rocket sets: <> pcs.
Par13-1	Torpedoes: <> pcs.
Par14-1	Enemy's blasters: <> items
Par15-1	Enemy's rockets: <> items
Par16-1	Enemy's torpedoes: <> items
Par17-1	All the rockets missed their target
Par17-2	<> rockets
Par17-3	<> rockets
Par17-4	<> rockets
Par19-1	Parameter No 19: <>
Par20-1	Parameter No 20: <>
Par21-1	Parameter No 21: <>
Par22-1	Your cash: <>
Par23-1	Parameter No 23: <>
Par24-1	Parameter No 24: <>
Loc1-1	After arrival to <ToPlanet>, you had no problems finding the Tournament Committee.
*	
*	- Welcome to the combat robot battle tournament - BattleMech, - they told you in the Committee. - We have already lost all hope to see a <FromPlanet>'s representative at the competition but as long as you come, please acquaint yourself with the tournament order. To get the main tournament prize, you must defeat the three opponents defined after the draw. 
*	
*	Your opponents are:
*	<clr>John "God" O' Damned<clrEnd> - a Gaalian
*	<clr>Zen Cha-Cha<clrEnd> - a Faeyan
*	<clr>Steel Silvester <clrEnd> - a Human
*	
*	You must define the order you fight them in yourself. Every battle takes one day. It's too late to start today, so relax until tomorrow. You can acquaint yourself with the battle rules.
*	
*	Note, you will receive an average BattleMech. However, you may have additional equipment installed for a small fee in our boxes.
*	
*	You can go now. See you tomorrow.
Loc2-1	<clr>Battle rules.<clrEnd>
*	
*	You have tree types of weapons.
*	<clr>Blaster<clrEnd> - the weakest weapon but its sighting system is perfect. It is impossible to escape it. <clr> A power shield <clrEnd> is used against it.
*	<clr>Rocket launcher<clrEnd> volleys 3 rockets per one shot. The rockets are uncontrollable but they can cause much damage if all of them go home. However, their navigator leaves much to be desired - the cases when all rockets go home are rare. Moreover, it's easy to escape them with the help of <clr>antirocket manoeuvre <clrEnd>.
*	<clr>Torpedo tube <clrEnd> shoots with homing torpedoes. A couple of direct hits of such torpedoes will cause death easily. Unfortunately, their homing system can be jammed by <clr>the noise generator <clrEnd>. However, even if it bursts not far from the enemy, it can cause some damage.
*	
*	During each round the opponents attack each other once. Before the battle they ballot for the attack turn and choose the attacking weapon (the blaster, the torpedo tube, or the rocket launcher) and the defending weapon (the power shield, the noise generator, or the antirocket manoeuvre). Naturally, none of the opponents know what weapon their enemies have chosen.
*	
*	They fight until one of the combat robots is destroyed.
*	
*	A robot can carry <clr>10 ammunition sets <clrEnd>. 2 blaster charges, 2 rocket sets and 2 torpedoes make a standard set provided from the beginning. 4 remaining sets are added on the participant's discretion.
Loc3-1	Two sets for each type of weapon are inside already. You need to choose <clr>4<clrEnd> remaining sets.
*	
*	Choose <clr>the first<clrEnd> set.
Loc4-1	Cowardice has been considered disgraceful at all times and by all nations. On the other hand, sometimes they would call reasonable caution and indisposition for deadly adventures cowardice. Eventually, your fighting with dominators is much more important than this stupid tournament!
*	
*	Your mission failed.
Loc5-1	Choose <clr>the second<clrEnd> set.
Loc6-1	Choose <clr>the third<clrEnd> set.
Loc7-1	Choose <clr>the fourth<clrEnd> set.
Loc8-1	Prepare for the fight.
Loc12-1	Phew! This bloody nightmare is over at last. You left the playground with your legs shaking hardly believing that you managed to stay alive in this slaughter. Well, the waiting award will help to overcome this stress.
Loc19-1	So, the great and dreadful <clr>John "God" O'Damned <clrEnd> versus you! Stands kept their breath waiting for the fight. Huge monitors over them displayed a close-up of your enemy's stern and firm face. After recollecting your courage and wishing good luck to yourself, you put your hands on the joysticks.
Loc19-2	So, the great and dreadful <clr>John "God" O'Damned <clrEnd> versus you! Stands kept their breath waiting for the fight. Huge monitors over them displayed a close-up of your enemy's stern and firm face. After recollecting your courage and wishing good luck to yourself, you put your hands on the joysticks.
Loc19-3	While you were preparing to go out to the playground, the crowd-puller <clr>Zen  Cha-Cha<clrEnd> was demonstrating the art of manipulating a BattleMech in front of the spectators. Well, we'll see how these dancing steps will help him in the real fight!
Loc19-4	While you were preparing to go out to the playground, the crowd-puller <clr>Zen  Cha-Cha<clrEnd> was demonstrating the art of manipulating a BattleMech in front of the spectators. Well, we'll see how these dancing steps will help him in the real fight!
Loc19-5	<clr>Steel Silvester<clrEnd>'s BattleMech was worked as a gobzaurus and looked awesome if not to say shocking. The spectators acclaimed him while your appearance was followed by almost deadly silence. It looked like nobody believed in your victory there. However, when Silvester's face was shown on the huge monitor, there appeared to be some uncertainty hiding in his eyes...
Loc19-6	<clr>Steel Silvester<clrEnd>'s BattleMech was worked as a gobzaurus and looked awesome if not to say shocking. The spectators acclaimed him while your appearance was followed by almost deadly silence. It looked like nobody believed in your victory there. However, when Silvester's face was shown on the huge monitor, there appeared to be some uncertainty hiding in his eyes...
Loc20-1	While you were preparing to go out to the playground, the crowd-puller <clr>Zen  Cha-Cha<clrEnd> was demonstrating the art of manipulating a BattleMech in front of the spectators. Well, we'll see how these dancing steps will help him in the real fight!
Loc20-2	<clr>Steel Silvester<clrEnd>'s BattleMech was worked as a gobzaurus and looked awesome if not to say shocking. The spectators acclaimed him while your appearance was followed by almost deadly silence. It looked like nobody believed in your victory there. However, when Silvester's face was shown on the huge monitor, there appeared to be some uncertainty hiding in his eyes...
Loc20-3	So, the great and dreadful <clr>John "God" O'Damned <clrEnd> versus you! Stands kept their breath waiting for the fight. Huge monitors over them displayed a close-up of your enemy's stern and firm face. After recollecting your courage and wishing good luck to yourself, you put your hands on the joysticks.
Loc20-4	<clr>Steel Silvester<clrEnd>'s BattleMech was worked as a gobzaurus and looked awesome if not to say shocking. The spectators acclaimed him while your appearance was followed by almost deadly silence. It looked like nobody believed in your victory there. However, when Silvester's face was shown on the huge monitor, there appeared to be some uncertainty hiding in his eyes...
Loc20-5	While you were preparing to go out to the playground, the crowd-puller <clr>Zen  Cha-Cha<clrEnd> was demonstrating the art of manipulating a BattleMech in front of the spectators. Well, we'll see how these dancing steps will help him in the real fight!
Loc20-6	So, the great and dreadful <clr>John "God" O'Damned <clrEnd> versus you! Stands kept their breath waiting for the fight. Huge monitors over them displayed a close-up of your enemy's stern and firm face. After recollecting your courage and wishing good luck to yourself, you put your hands on the joysticks.
Loc21-1	<clr>Steel Silvester<clrEnd>'s BattleMech was worked as a gobzaurus and looked awesome if not to say shocking. The spectators acclaimed him while your appearance was followed by almost deadly silence. It looked like nobody believed in your victory there. However, when Silvester's face was shown on the huge monitor, there appeared to be some uncertainty hiding in his eyes...
Loc21-2	While you were preparing to go out to the playground, the crowd-puller <clr>Zen  Cha-Cha<clrEnd> was demonstrating the art of manipulating a BattleMech in front of the spectators. Well, we'll see how these dancing steps will help him in the real fight!
Loc21-3	<clr>Steel Silvester<clrEnd>'s BattleMech was worked as a gobzaurus and looked awesome if not to say shocking. The spectators acclaimed him while your appearance was followed by almost deadly silence. It looked like nobody believed in your victory there. However, when Silvester's face was shown on the huge monitor, there appeared to be some uncertainty hiding in his eyes...
Loc21-4	So, the great and dreadful <clr>John "God" O'Damned <clrEnd> versus you! Stands kept their breath waiting for the fight. Huge monitors over them displayed a close-up of your enemy's stern and firm face. After recollecting your courage and wishing good luck to yourself, you put your hands on the joysticks.
Loc21-5	So, the great and dreadful <clr>John "God" O'Damned <clrEnd> versus you! Stands kept their breath waiting for the fight. Huge monitors over them displayed a close-up of your enemy's stern and firm face. After recollecting your courage and wishing good luck to yourself, you put your hands on the joysticks.
Loc21-6	While you were preparing to go out to the playground, the crowd-puller <clr>Zen  Cha-Cha<clrEnd> was demonstrating the art of manipulating a BattleMech in front of the spectators. Well, we'll see how these dancing steps will help him in the real fight!
Loc38-1	The next fight will be only tomorrow, so now you can relax and have a rest. However, it is desirable that you visit <clr>the boxes<clrEnd> in the first place. May be, they will be able to upgrade the rubbish you are going to fight on tomorrow. And then it's worthwhile going to <clr>the bar<clrEnd> and try to get some info about your future opponents.
Loc38-2	So, the upgrade will be complete by tomorrow. You left the boxes with a contented smile.
*	
*	May be, it's worthwhile going to <clr>the bar<clrEnd> now and try to get some info about your future opponents, isn't it?
Loc39-1	There was nothing special about the bar. You must have seen thousands of such bars. And only several individuals attracted your attention. For example, a noisy <clr>fan<clrEnd> group in the middle of the bar. Or a huge <clr>Maloq<clrEnd> sitting at the table in the far corner. He is deadly drunk but it looks like he's till able to talk. And everybody knows that sober thinks, drunken speaks, he might say something interesting. There is a lonely <clr>Peleng<clrEnd> at the bar counter. Judging by his cunning snoot, he earns his living as a gambler and surely has some private information about the tournament participants.
*	
*	All you need to do is to decide who'll be the first.
Loc39-2	The bar is still as dull as ditch-water. The Maloq seems to be out of the drinking bout and is recollecting his feelings in his room. But there is <clr>the Peleng<clrEnd> you saw last night. And <clr>the fans<clrEnd> are still talking some of their business.
*	
*	"So, who else have I missed?"
Loc39-3	The bar was nicely gloomy and silent. There is no noisy fan group here today but the other regulars, in particular, <clr>the Maloq<clrEnd> and <clr>the Peleng<clrEnd> are still here.
*	
*	Well, who will you talk to?
Loc39-4	The bar is namely empty today. Neither the merry fan group, nor the wild Maloq drunkard can be seen anywhere. There is just <clr>the Peleng<clrEnd> who's never off the stand.
Loc39-5	So here you are again in the bar.
*	<clr>The Maloq<clrEnd> you saw last night, is hanging himself on again like he was doing yesterday. No Peleng today but there is an animated group of <clr>fans<clrEnd>, Faeyans mostly, discussing something. May be, you will be able to have them tell you something about their idol.
*	
*	Well, who will you talk to?
Loc39-6	There is neither the unblessed Maloq, nor the Peleng dodger in the bar today. But <clr>the fans<clrEnd> are still making a racket for all absent once.
Loc39-7	What a bore it is in the bar today! There is nobody here but for the ever drunken <clr>Maloq<clrEnd> at the table in the corner so you have practically nobody to talk to.
Loc40-1	When you approached the Maloq, he could hardly raise his head, gave you a cloudy look and murmured:
*	- So, what the hell do you want? Sit down. Tap it!
Loc41-1	You decided that boozing together is the best way to get acquainted, so you ordered a glass of your favourite belly-wash, approached the fans and toasted:
Loc42-1	The Peleng noticed you as well so when you approached him, he gave you a nasty grin and asked:
*	- As far as I know, you are famous <Ranger>, a ranger, aren't you? Sit down, I've got something to tell you.
*	
*	- I'm just a gambler, - the Peleng said smoothly when you sat opposite him, - my fortunes are at low ebb now but I know a lot. If you pay me something like <clr>100 cr<clrEnd>, I'm ready to provide you with some private information about one of your future opponents.
Loc43-1	Judging from the fan's unutterable fury and their desire to clean your clock, it was obvious that you dished out something wrong. After you could hardly get out of their clutches, you chose to leave and go to bed.
*	
*	You went to the armoury first thing next morning.
Loc43-2	Gleeful hubbub of approving exclamations was the reaction to your speech. After the third glass you managed to turn the conversation to the necessary topic and found out that <clr>O'Damned<clrEnd> chose a tough <clr>upgraded blaster <clrEnd> to be his main weapon during the fight. And he is especially <clr>afraid of torpedoes <clrEnd> and often activates the noise generator. 
*	
*	After you found out everything you needed, you buzzed away from the bar and went to bed. In the morning after freshening up you went to the armoury.
Loc43-3	The fans noised approvingly, raised their glasses and had nothing against having a drink and paling with you. During the conversation, you found out that <clr>John "God" O'Damned is thought to be the greatest master of antirocket manoeuvre <clrEnd> able to escape even torpedoes sometimes. Moreover, he personally <clr>upgraded the rocket navigator <clrEnd> and substantially improved the impact grouping. 
*	
*	The party finished after midnight, and you could hardly make it to your hole. You went to the armoury first thing in the morning.
Loc43-4	After your toast the fans emptied their glasses and you became one of them. Booze unlocked your new friends' tongues and you had no problems to get the low-down on John "God" O'Damned. As it turned out, <clr>O'Damned uses unique torpedoes <clrEnd> with the improved homing system, which causes more noise. So you should make a fight with him short. The most valuable information you managed to fish out was the fact that O'Damned had serious <clr>problems with the protection field <clrEnd>, so he avoids activating it with no special reason.
*	
*	After giving your competitors a warm clasp, you went to bed. You went to the armoury first thing in the morning was.
Loc44-1	Judging from the fan's unutterable fury and their desire to clean your clock, it was obvious that you dished out something wrong. After you could hardly get out of their clutches, you chose to leave and go to bed.
*	
*	You went to the armoury first thing next morning.
Loc44-2	The fans noised approvingly, raised their glasses and had nothing against having a drink and paling with you. During the conversation, you found out that <clr>Zen Cha-Cha<clrEnd> is thought to be the greatest master of <clr>antirocket manoeuvre <clrEnd> able to escape even torpedoes sometimes. Moreover, he personally <clr>upgraded the rocket navigator <clrEnd> and substantially improved the impact grouping.
*	
*	The party finished after midnight, and you could hardly make it to your hole. You went to the armoury first thing in the morning.
Loc44-3	Gleeful hubbub of approving exclamations was the reaction to your speech. After the third glass you managed to turn the conversation to the necessary topic and found out that <clr>Zen Cha-Cha<clrEnd> chose a tough <clr>upgraded blaster <clrEnd> to be his main weapon during the fight. And he is especially afraid of torpedoes and often activates <clr> the noise generator<clrEnd>.
*	
*	After you found out everything you needed, you buzzed away from the bar and went to bed. In the morning after freshening up you went to the armoury.
Loc44-4	After your toast the fans emptied their glasses and you became one of them. Booze unlocked your new friends' tongues and you had no problems to get the low-down on Zen Cha-Cha. As it turned out, <clr>Zen Cha-Cha<clrEnd> uses <clr>unique torpedoes <clrEnd> with the improved homing system, which causes more noise. So you should make a fight with him short. The most valuable thing you managed to fish out was the fact that Zen Cha-Cha has serious <clr>problems with the protection field <clrEnd>, so he avoids activating it with no special reason.
*	
*	After giving your competitors a warm clasp, you went to bed. You went to the armoury first thing in the morning.
Loc45-1	Judging from the fan's unutterable fury and their desire to clean your clock, it was obvious that you dished out something wrong. After you could hardly get out of their clutches, you chose to leave and go to bed.
*	
*	You went to the armoury first thing next morning.
Loc45-2	After your toast the fans emptied their glasses and you became one of them. Booze unlocked your new friends' tongues and you had no problems to get the low-down on Steel Silvester. As it turned out, <clr>Steel Silvester<clrEnd> uses <clr>unique torpedoes <clrEnd> with the improved homing system, which causes more  noise sometimes. So you should make a fight with him short. The most valuable thing you managed to fish out was the fact that Steel Silvester has serious <clr>problems with the protection field <clrEnd>, so he avoids activating it with no special reason.
*	
*	After giving your competitors a warm clasp, you went to bed. You went to the armoury first thing in the morning.
Loc45-3	Gleeful hubbub of approving exclamations was the reaction to your speech. After the third glass you managed to turn the conversation to the necessary topic and found out that <clr>Steel Silvester<clrEnd> chose a tough <clr>upgraded blaster <clrEnd> to be his main weapon during the fight. And he is especially afraid of torpedoes and often activates <clr> the noise generator<clrEnd>.
*	
*	After you found out everything you needed, you buzzed away from the bar and went to bed. In the morning after freshening up you went to the armoury.
Loc45-4	The fans noised approvingly, raised their glasses and had nothing against having a drink and paling with you. During the conversation, you found out that <clr>Steel Silvester<clrEnd> is thought to be the greatest master of <clr>antirocket manoeuvre <clrEnd> able to escape even torpedoes sometimes. Moreover, he personally <clr>upgraded the rocket navigator <clrEnd> and substantially improved the impact grouping. 
*	
*	The party finished after midnight, and you could hardly make it to your hole. You went to the armoury first thing in the morning.
Loc46-1	You stroke the fans dumb by your cheek and they didn't know what to answer. After the silence became somewhat evil, you considered it wise to whistle off from the bar and to go to bed.
*	
*	You went to the armoury first thing in the morning.
Loc47-1	The Peleng ordered himself a drink, waited until they brought it and said:
*	- We-e-ll. As far as I can judge, you are not very generous. Perhaps, the information about <clr>John "God" O'Damned<clrEnd> is of no interest to you. However, he has his advantages and drawback as any other individual does. So whoever knows the details, gets much more chances to win, - the Peleng fell silent and made a sip from his glass looking at you with some expectation.
*	- Go on! - you hurried him.
*	- I'm not radio, - the Peeling's answer was unexpectedly abrupt. - Give me <clr>50 more cr<clrEnd>, and I'll tell you everything you want.
Loc47-2	The Peleng ordered himself a drink, waited until they brought it and said:
*	- We-e-ll. As far as I can judge, you are not very generous. Perhaps, the information about <clr>Zen  Cha-Cha<clrEnd> of no interest to you. However, he has his advantages and drawback as any other individual does. So whoever knows the details, gets much more chances to win, - the Peleng fell silent and made a sip from his glass looking at you with some expectation.
*	- Go on! - you hurried him.
*	- I'm not radio, - the Peeling's answer was unexpectedly abrupt. - Give me <clr>50 more cr<clrEnd>, and I'll tell you everything you want.
Loc47-4	The Peleng ordered himself a drink, waited until they brought it and said:
*	- We-e-ll. As far as I can judge, you are not very generous. Perhaps, the information about <clr>Steel Silvester<clrEnd> is of no interest to you. However, he has his advantages and drawback as any other individual does. So whoever knows the details, gets much more chances to win, - the Peleng fell silent and made a sip from his glass looking at you with some expectation.
*	- Go on! - you hurried him.
*	- I'm not radio, - the Peleng's answer was unexpectedly abrupt. - Give me <clr>50 more cr<clrEnd>, and I'll tell you everything you want.
Loc50-1	- You seem to be an adequate lad in contrast to the Gaalian bugger, <clr>John "God" O'Damned<clrEnd>. This bastard managed to beat me! Can you imagine that? ME! THE GALAXY CHAMP among Maloqs! And chose the vilest and trickiest means at that!
Loc50-2	- Hey, dude. So you don't think that an EX-champ is too miserable to drink with, do you? This skipjack <clr>Zen Cha-Cha<clrEnd> did it to me! It's still a secret for me how he contrived to beat me, THE WORLD CHAMP AMONG MALOQS... Only this foul wish-wash helps me to outlive such a disgrace somehow. Charge my glass again, man!
Loc50-4	- You're a tough lad, aren't you?. But <clr>Steel Silvester <clrEnd> will beat you anyway! He pulverised even me, THE WORLD CHAMP AMONG MALOQS! Pulverised completely! There is nothing left for me to do now but to sit in this crappy bar and soak.
Loc53-1	The first thing you did in the boxes was to acquaint yourself with the possible upgrade list. There were only three upgrading items for your model in the list.
*	1) <clr>Laser intensifier <clrEnd> - increases damage of the enemy's BattleMech caused by a blaster - <clr>150 cr<clrEnd>
*	2) <clr>Improved rocket navigator <clrEnd> - improves grouping, that is the case when 2 or 3 rockets volley your enemy, it will happen more often - <clr>200 cr<clrEnd>
*	3) <clr>Heading for the torpedo tube <clrEnd> - allows you to shoot with upgraded torpedoes with wider range of explosion that cause big damage even of the torpedo misses but bursts out not far from the target - <clr>100 cr<clrEnd>
*	
*	While you were studying the pricelist, the shift supervisor came to you. You asked how long one upgrade would take. He said they were too busy to manage more than one upgrade per day and asked what you wanted to have upgraded in the first place.
Loc53-2	The first thing you did in the boxes was refreshing your memory about the possible upgrade list. There were only three upgrading items for your model in the list.
*	Neither the prices, nor the terms have changed.
*	1) <clr>Laser intensifier <clrEnd> - increases damage of the enemy's BattleMech caused by a blaster - <clr>150 cr<clrEnd>
*	2) <clr>Improved rocket navigator <clrEnd> - improves grouping, that is the case when 2 will volley your enemy or 3 rockets will happen more often - <clr>200 cr<clrEnd>
*	3) <clr>Heading for the torpedo tube <clrEnd> - allows you to shoot with upgraded torpedoes with wider range of explosion that cause big damage even if the torpedo misses but bursts out not far from the target - <clr>100 cr<clrEnd>
Loc53-3	The first thing you did in the boxes was refreshing your memory about the possible upgrade list. There were only three upgrading items for your model in the list.
*	Neither the prices, nor the terms have changed.
*	1) <clr>Laser intensifier <clrEnd> - increases damage of the enemy's BattleMech caused by a blaster - <clr>150 cr<clrEnd>
*	2) <clr>Improved rocket navigator <clrEnd> - improves grouping, that is the case when 2 will volley your enemy or 3 rockets will happen more often - <clr>200 cr<clrEnd>
*	3) <clr>Heading for the torpedo tube <clrEnd> - allows you to shoot with upgraded torpedoes with wider range of explosion that cause big damage even if the torpedo misses but bursts out not far from the target - <clr>100 cr<clrEnd>
Loc62-1	The enemy is biting the dust at last! After the honour round in front of the elated stands, you went to the boxes.
*	
*	So, what do you feel like? Shall we go on and fight? Or is it enough?
Loc62-2	The enemy blew off all his ammunition so they announced your victory due to ammunition superiority. After the honour round in front of the elated stands, you can go to the boxes.
*	
*	So, what do you feel like? Shall we go on and fight? Or is it enough?
Loc63-1	You took a separate room in the bar, the Peleng ordered dinner for two of you and continued.
*	
*	- Backstreet fights are a little bit different from official ones. You get a much better upgraded BattleMech with the most up-to-date equipment. All types of weapons have five charge sets and you have no options here. Your award increases in geometric progression - every next victory costs twice more than the previous one. That is, you'll get <clr>250<clrEnd> cr for the first victory, <clr>500<clrEnd> cr for the second one, <clr>1000<clrEnd> cr for the third one, and so on... However, every next enemy will be die-harder and will have a more powerful type of weapons so it will take more effort to beat him. You have perfect freedom to opt out of the next fight before it starts and quit keeping all the earned money. Moreover, you can give up at any moment during the fight to stay alive. In this case you keep only one half of the previously earned money. Oh, yes, there is something I forgot to mention - the fights are non-stop, that is, the time given to you between the fights is enough to change your robot only. If you accept my offer, the fights start in an hour and you won't waste your precious time. Well, are you interested?
Loc64-1	The enemy activated the shield and the blaster did no harm to him.
Loc64-2	What a reaction! How did he manage to activate the shield?
Loc64-3	Humph... Bad luck! The enemy nicked your intentions and activated the shield.
Loc64-4	Noises can protect from torpedoes, of course, but the blaster is dreadful too and your enemy should keep it in mind.
Loc64-5	As skilful as you might be in zigzagging, nobody has escaped the blaster yet with the help of an antirocket manoeuvre!
Loc64-6	The blaster's powerful hit didn't allow the enemy to finish his antirocket manoeuvre.
Loc64-7	The enemy tried the antirocket manoeuvre but your blaster was faster.
Loc64-8	The enemy activated the noise generator but it didn't help him to escape the blaster.
Loc64-9	What a mercy! Despite the active noise generator your blaster caused serious damage to the enemy.
Loc70-1	The enemy activated the power field but it didn't help much to absorb the shock. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc70-2	The enemy's nerves snapped at last and he decided to activate the power shield. And all for nothing! The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc70-3	The protection field flashed in front of the enemy's robot. The enemy saw his mistake and tried to make a hairpin curve but it was too late. The rockets went home. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc70-4	The enemy's antirocket manoeuvre was well-done. Alas, all your rockets missed.
Loc70-5	The stands applauded to the echo cheering the enemy's next well-done antirocket manoeuvre.
Loc70-6	As usual, the enemy ducked all the rockets in a breeze.
Loc70-7	The noise generator has never protected anybody from a rocket volley. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc70-8	Just one second before the explosion, you saw the distorted features of your opponent on the monitor - this was the last video signal that came from his robot. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc70-9	Your enemy's intuition failed this time. He activated the noise generator instead of manoeuvring, and the rockets hit the target, which was almost stationary. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc71-1	The power shield turned out to be vulnerable to the torpedo.
Loc71-2	The torpedo ignored the enemy's poor attempts to activate the power shield.
Loc71-3	A power shield against a torpedo? It's nonsense!
Loc71-4	Even an antirocket manoeuvre didn't make the torpedo wander from the target.
Loc71-5	It's hard to duck a torpedo. Almost impossible. Your enemy didn't manage it either.
Loc71-6	Though the enemy's antirocket manoeuvre was perfect, the torpedo hit him any way.
Loc71-7	The noise generator made the torpedo wander from the target but several fragments still shaved the enemy's robot.
Loc71-8	Damn it! The enemy was quick enough to activate the noise generator. The torpedo exploded within several meters from the target. But the explosion shook up the enemy any way.
Loc71-9	The torpedo almost hit the enemy but the noise generator did its black deed. Well, at least the shock wave warped the enemy's machine though not too much.
Loc71-10	The antirocket manoeuvre was so well-done that the torpedo missed. There were just several fragments that reached the enemy.
Loc72-1	The power shield made a good defence against the blaster.
Loc72-2	The flash of the blaster's beam reached the power field and made you squint. But on the other hand, the field swallowed all its power and the machine was not damaged at all.
Loc72-3	You managed to be one jump ahead of the enemy's blaster shot. The attack is repelled successfully!
Loc72-4	The power shield provides poor protection from rockets. The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc72-5	Your mom told you to avoid activating the power shield when the rockets are approaching, didn't she? So, she was absolutely right! The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc72-6	The enemy's rockets rushed to your machine leaving a smoky trace behind them. Why the hell did you activate the power shield?! The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc72-7	The power shield is no obstacle for torpedoes.
Loc72-8	The torpedo went through the power shield as if there was nothing at all on its way. High-powered explosion shook your combat machine.
Loc72-9	The machine vibrated at the torpedo's terrible hit. Activating the power shield seemed to be a bad idea.
Loc73-1	Such a manoeuvre won't help you to escape the blaster.
Loc73-2	While giving your joystick a wrench and trying to veer, you felt how quickly your robot's jacketing became hot. It looked like the blaster got you.
Loc73-3	The blaster shot outran your ill-timed manoeuvre.
Loc73-4	That was a perfect manoeuvre. All the enemy's rockets missed.
Loc73-5	You ducked all the rockets manoeuvring elegantly and got a great tornado of applause on the stands.
Loc73-6	Rockets are dreadful, of course but it won't be a big problem to duck them for an experienced ranger.
Loc73-7	Your manoeuvre didn't misguide the torpedo's homing system.
Loc73-8	Alas, the configuration of the torpedo's homing system won't let you escape it just manoeuvring.
Loc73-9	Your machine that had just finished manoeuvring was nearly knocked over by the torpedo's high-powered hit.
Loc74-1	The generator didn't protect you from the blaster.
Loc74-2	Damn it, the enemy managed to outplay you. After you activated the noise generator, he remained cool and hit you with a blaster.
Loc74-3	Trying to misguide the enemy blaster beam with the help of the noise generator is rather insane!
Loc74-4	The generator is no protection against rockets.  The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc74-5	Don't trust the noise generator if enemy rockets are flying in your direction. The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc74-6	You saw the approaching rockets but it was too late to duck them. The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc74-7	The torpedo exploded nearby, so only several fragments reached the machine.
Loc74-8	The noise generator did its work perfectly and the torpedo turned up the soil of the playground aside of you. However, the explosion still shook you up a little.
Loc74-9	Though the torpedo passed by due to the generator, the charge was powerful enough to damage your machine a little.
Loc75-1	The enemy activated the shield and the blaster did no harm to him.
Loc75-2	What a reaction! How did he manage to activate the shield?
Loc75-3	Humph... Bad luck! The enemy nicked your intentions and activated the shield.
Loc75-4	The enemy activated the noise generator but it didn't help him to escape the blaster.
Loc75-5	As skilful as you might be in zigzagging, nobody has escaped the blaster yet with the help of an antirocket manoeuvre!
Loc75-6	The blaster's powerful hit didn't allow the enemy to finish his antirocket manoeuvre.
Loc75-7	The enemy activated the noise generator but it didn't help him to escape the blaster.
Loc75-8	Noises can protect from torpedoes, of course, but the blaster is dreadful too and your enemy should keep it in mind.
Loc75-9	What a mercy! Despite the active noise generator your blaster caused serious damage to the enemy.
Loc76-1	The enemy activated the power field but it didn't help much to absorb the shock. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc76-2	The enemy's nerves snapped at last and he decided to activate the power shield. And all for nothing! The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc76-3	The protection field flashed in front of the enemy's robot. The enemy saw his mistake and tried to make a hairpin curve but it was too late. The rockets went home. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc76-4	The enemy's antirocket manoeuvre was well-done. Alas, all your rockets missed.
Loc76-5	Though the torpedo passed by due to the generator, the charge was powerful enough to damage your machine a little.
Loc76-6	It seemed that the enemy tarried before manoeuvring but in the last moment he managed to duck the rockets, which flew by within a few centimetres from the body.
Loc76-7	The noise generator has never protected anybody from a rocket volley. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc76-8	Just one second before the explosion, you saw the distorted features of your opponent on the monitor - this was the last video signal that came from his robot. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc76-9	Your enemy's intuition failed this time. He activated the noise generator instead of manoeuvring, and the rockets hit the target, which was almost stationary. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc77-1	The power shield turned out to be vulnerable to the torpedo.
Loc77-2	The torpedo ignored the enemy's poor attempts to activate the power shield.
Loc77-3	A power shield against a torpedo? It's nonsense!
Loc77-4	Even an antirocket manoeuvre didn't make the torpedo wander from the target.
Loc77-5	It's hard to duck a torpedo. Almost impossible. Your enemy didn't manage it either.
Loc77-6	Though the enemy's antirocket manoeuvre was perfect, the torpedo hit him any way.
Loc77-7	The noise generator made the torpedo wander from the target but several fragments still shaved the enemy's robot.
Loc77-8	Damn it! The enemy was quick enough to activate the noise generator. The torpedo exploded within several meters from the target. But the explosion shook up the enemy any way.
Loc77-9	The torpedo almost hit the enemy but the noise generator did its black deed. Well, at least the shock wave warped the enemy's machine though not too much.
Loc78-1	The enemy activated the shield and the blaster did no harm to him.
Loc78-2	What a reaction! How did he manage to activate the shield?
Loc78-3	Humph... Bad luck! The enemy nicked your intentions and activated the shield.
Loc78-4	The enemy tried the antirocket manoeuvre but your blaster was faster.
Loc78-5	As skilful as you might be in zigzagging, nobody has escaped the blaster yet with the help of an antirocket manoeuvre!
Loc78-6	The blaster's powerful hit didn't allow the enemy to finish his antirocket manoeuvre.
Loc78-7	The enemy activated the noise generator but it didn't help him to escape the blaster.
Loc78-8	Noises can protect from torpedoes, of course, but the blaster is dreadful too and your enemy should keep it in mind.
Loc78-9	What a mercy! Despite the active noise generator your blaster caused serious damage to the enemy.
Loc79-1	The enemy activated the power field but it didn't help much to absorb the shock. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc79-2	The enemy's nerves snapped at last and he decided to activate the power shield. And all for nothing! The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc79-3	The protection field flashed in front of the enemy's robot. The enemy saw his mistake and tried to make a hairpin curve but it was too late. The rockets went home. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc79-4	The enemy's antirocket manoeuvre was well-done. Alas, all your rockets missed.
Loc79-5	Though the torpedo passed by due to the generator, the charge was powerful enough to damage your machine a little.
Loc79-6	It seemed that the enemy tarried before manoeuvring but in the last moment he managed to duck the rockets, which flew by within a few centimetres from the body.
Loc79-7	The noise generator has never protected anybody from a rocket volley. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc79-8	Just one second before the explosion, you saw the distorted features of your opponent on the monitor - this was the last video signal that came from his robot. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc79-9	Your enemy's intuition failed this time. He activated the noise generator instead of manoeuvring, and the rockets hit the target, which was almost stationary. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc80-1	The power shield turned out to be vulnerable to the torpedo.
Loc80-2	The torpedo ignored the enemy's poor attempts to activate the power shield.
Loc80-3	A power shield against a torpedo? It's nonsense!
Loc80-4	Even an antirocket manoeuvre didn't make the torpedo wander from the target.
Loc80-5	It's hard to duck a torpedo. Almost impossible. Your enemy didn't manage it either.
Loc80-6	Though the enemy's antirocket manoeuvre was perfect, the torpedo hit him any way.
Loc80-7	The noise generator made the torpedo wander from the target but several fragments still shaved the enemy's robot.
Loc80-8	Damn it! The enemy was quick enough to activate the noise generator. The torpedo exploded within several meters from the target. But the explosion shook up the enemy any way.
Loc80-9	The torpedo almost hit the enemy but the noise generator did its black deed. Well, at least the shock wave warped the enemy's machine though not too much.
Loc81-1	The enemy activated the shield and the blaster did no harm to him.
Loc81-2	What a reaction! How did he manage to activate the shield?
Loc81-3	Humph... Bad luck! The enemy nicked your intentions and activated the shield.
Loc81-4	The enemy tried the antirocket manoeuvre but your blaster was faster.
Loc81-5	As skilful as you might be in zigzagging, nobody has escaped the blaster yet with the help of an antirocket manoeuvre!
Loc81-6	The blaster's powerful hit didn't allow the enemy to finish his antirocket manoeuvre.
Loc81-7	The enemy activated the noise generator but it didn't help him to escape the blaster.
Loc81-8	Noises can protect from torpedoes, of course, but the blaster is dreadful too and your enemy should keep it in mind.
Loc81-9	What a mercy! Despite the active noise generator your blaster caused serious damage to the enemy.
Loc82-1	The enemy activated the power field but it didn't help much to absorb the shock. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc82-2	The enemy's nerves snapped at last and he decided to activate the power shield. And all for nothing! The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc82-3	The protection field flashed in front of the enemy's robot. The enemy saw his mistake and tried to make a hairpin curve but it was too late. The rockets went home. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc82-4	The enemy's antirocket manoeuvre was well-done. Alas, all your rockets missed.
Loc82-5	Though the torpedo passed by due to the generator, the charge was powerful enough to damage your machine a little.
Loc82-6	It seemed that the enemy tarried before manoeuvring but in the last moment he managed to duck the rockets, which flew by within a few centimetres from the body.
Loc82-7	The noise generator has never protected anybody from a rocket volley. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc82-8	Just one second before the explosion, you saw the distorted features of your opponent on the monitor - this was the last video signal that came from his robot. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc82-9	Your enemy's intuition failed this time. He activated the noise generator instead of manoeuvring, and the rockets hit the target, which was almost stationary. The rocket hit counter showed [p17].
Loc83-1	The power shield turned out to be vulnerable to the torpedo.
Loc83-2	The torpedo ignored the enemy's poor attempts to activate the power shield.
Loc83-3	A power shield against a torpedo? It's nonsense!
Loc83-4	Even an antirocket manoeuvre didn't make the torpedo wander from the target.
Loc83-5	It's hard to duck a torpedo. Almost impossible. Your enemy didn't manage it either.
Loc83-6	Though the enemy's antirocket manoeuvre was perfect, the torpedo hit him any way.
Loc83-7	The noise generator made the torpedo wander from the target but several fragments still shaved the enemy's robot.
Loc83-8	Damn it! The enemy was quick enough to activate the noise generator. The torpedo exploded within several meters from the target. But the explosion shook up the enemy any way.
Loc83-9	The torpedo almost hit the enemy but the noise generator did its black deed. Well, at least the shock wave warped the enemy's machine though not too much.
Loc84-1	Looking at the merry Faeyan company, you still couldn't figure out whose fans they were. Of course, you could try and join the conversation at a venture; if you are lucky, you fill find out everything you need during the talk. Or you could settle yourself at the nearby slot-machine and listen to the conversation without drawing anybody's attention.
Loc85-1	While you were gambling, they broadcast the interview with <clr>Zen Cha-Cha<clrEnd> on the bar stereovision. When the fans saw his face on the screen, they burst into invective and loud whistling. The barman set a hurried switch to another channel before they started rowing.
Loc85-2	Hardly two minutes passed before one of the fans too excited due to all the booze inside of him, jumped onto the table and started yelling insulting words addressed to <clr>Steel Silvester <clrEnd>. It took his less drunken friends a lot of effort to tug him off the table.
Loc85-4	You gave an ear to what they were talking about and heard two fans' conversation about the yesterday's fight with <clr>John "God" O'Damned<clrEnd>'s fan group. If one buys their gossiping, their up-and-downer could be compared to Armageddon.
Loc86-1	Soon there appeared one more fan group at the bar entrance yelling and praising <clr>Steel Silvester<clrEnd>'s valour. Your fan group roared in fury and flew at them with an obvious intention to knock their teeth in. The latter realised their inferior manpower and whistled off immediately. Their enemies didn't consider it worthwhile chasing such half-wits and went on with the booze-up.
Loc86-2	While you were torturing the slot-machine, two huge and uncommonly bosky thugs latched to the Gaalian passing by to the bar, and didn't let him go until he roared viva voce thrice that <clr>John "God" O'Damned<clrEnd> was a toy.
Loc86-4	Once again you gave your ear to the conversation and heard a fan asking his buddy: "Why are you silent, <clr>CHA-CHAffy<clrEnd> thoughts"?. And the latter answered: "Give me a break! I hate this <clr>Zen<clrEnd> thing!" And both of them nickered over their stupid joke.
Loc87-1	The power shield made a good defence against the blaster.
Loc87-2	The flash of the blaster's beam reached the power field and made you squint. But on the other hand, the field swallowed all its power and the machine was not damaged at all.
Loc87-3	You managed to be one jump ahead of the enemy's blaster shot. The attack is repelled successfully!
Loc87-4	The power shield provides poor protection from rockets. The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc87-5	Your mom told you to avoid activating the power shield when the rockets are approaching, didn't she? So, she was absolutely right! The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc87-6	The enemy's rockets rushed to your machine leaving a smoky trace behind them. Why the hell did you activate the power shield?! The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc87-7	The power shield is no obstacle for torpedoes.
Loc87-8	The torpedo went through the power shield as if there was nothing at all on its way. High-powered explosion shook your combat machine.
Loc87-9	The machine vibrated at the torpedo's terrible hit. Activating the power shield seemed to be a bad idea.
Loc88-1	Such a manoeuvre won't help you to escape the blaster.
Loc88-2	While giving your joystick a wrench and trying to veer, you felt how quickly your robot's jacketing became hot. It looked like the blaster got you.
Loc88-3	The blaster shot outran your ill-timed manoeuvre.
Loc88-4	That was a perfect manoeuvre. All the enemy's rockets missed.
Loc88-5	You ducked all the rockets manoeuvring elegantly and got a great tornado of applause on the stands.
Loc88-6	Rockets are dreadful, of course but it won't be a big problem to duck them for an experienced ranger.
Loc88-7	Your manoeuvre didn't misguide the torpedo's homing system.
Loc88-8	Alas, the configuration of the torpedo's homing system won't let you escape it just manoeuvring.
Loc88-9	Your machine that had just finished manoeuvring was nearly knocked over by the torpedo's high-powered hit.
Loc89-1	The generator didn't protect you from the blaster.
Loc89-2	Damn it, the enemy managed to outplay you. After you activated the noise generator, he remained cool and hit you with a blaster.
Loc89-3	Trying to misguide the enemy blaster beam with the help of the noise generator is rather insane!
Loc89-4	The generator is no protection against rockets.  The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc89-5	Don't trust the noise generator if enemy rockets are flying in your direction. The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc89-6	You saw the approaching rockets but it was too late to duck them. The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc89-7	The torpedo exploded nearby, so only several fragments reached the machine.
Loc89-8	The noise generator did its work perfectly and the torpedo turned up the soil of the playground aside of you. However, the explosion still shook you up a little.
Loc89-9	Though the torpedo passed by due to the generator, the charge was powerful enough to damage your machine a little.
Loc90-1	The power shield made a good defence against the blaster.
Loc90-2	The flash of the blaster's beam reached the power field and made you squint. But on the other hand, the field swallowed all its power and the machine was not damaged at all.
Loc90-3	You managed to be one jump ahead of the enemy's blaster shot. The attack is repelled successfully!
Loc90-4	The power shield provides poor protection from rockets. The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc90-5	Your mom told you to avoid activating the power shield when the rockets are approaching, didn't she? So, she was absolutely right! The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc90-6	The enemy's rockets rushed to your machine leaving a smoky trace behind them. Why the hell did you activate the power shield?! The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc90-7	The power shield is no obstacle for torpedoes.
Loc90-8	The torpedo went through the power shield as if there was nothing at all on its way. High-powered explosion shook your combat machine.
Loc90-9	The machine vibrated at the torpedo's terrible hit. Activating the power shield seemed to be a bad idea.
Loc91-1	Such a manoeuvre won't help you to escape the blaster.
Loc91-2	While giving your joystick a wrench and trying to veer, you felt how quickly your robot's jacketing became hot. It looked like the blaster got you.
Loc91-3	The blaster shot outran your ill-timed manoeuvre.
Loc91-4	That was a perfect manoeuvre. All the enemy's rockets missed.
Loc91-5	You ducked all the rockets manoeuvring elegantly and got a great tornado of applause on the stands.
Loc91-6	Rockets are dreadful, of course but it won't be a big problem to duck them for an experienced ranger.
Loc91-7	Your manoeuvre didn't misguide the torpedo's homing system.
Loc91-8	Alas, the configuration of the torpedo's homing system won't let you escape it just manoeuvring.
Loc91-9	Your machine that had just finished manoeuvring was nearly knocked over by the torpedo's high-powered hit.
Loc92-1	The generator didn't protect you from the blaster.
Loc92-2	Damn it, the enemy managed to outplay you. After you activated the noise generator, he remained cool and hit you with a blaster.
Loc92-3	Trying to misguide the enemy blaster beam with the help of the noise generator is rather insane!
Loc92-4	The generator is no protection against rockets.  The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc92-5	Don't trust the noise generator if enemy rockets are flying in your direction. The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc92-6	You saw the approaching rockets but it was too late to duck them. The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc92-7	The torpedo exploded nearby, so only several fragments reached the machine.
Loc92-8	The noise generator did its work perfectly and the torpedo turned up the soil of the playground aside of you. However, the explosion still shook you up a little.
Loc92-9	Though the torpedo passed by due to the generator, the charge was powerful enough to damage your machine a little.
Loc92-10	Despite the noise generator, the torpedo went home.
Loc93-1	The power shield made a good defence against the blaster.
Loc93-2	The flash of the blaster's beam reached the power field and made you squint. But on the other hand, the field swallowed all its power and the machine was not damaged at all.
Loc93-3	You managed to be one jump ahead of the enemy's blaster shot. The attack is repelled successfully!
Loc93-4	The power shield provides poor protection from rockets. The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc93-5	Your mom told you to avoid activating the power shield when the rockets are approaching, didn't she? So, she was absolutely right! The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc93-6	The enemy's rockets rushed to your machine leaving a smoky trace behind them. Why the hell did you activate the power shield?! The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc93-7	The power shield is no obstacle for torpedoes.
Loc93-8	The torpedo went through the power shield as if there was nothing at all on its way. High-powered explosion shook your combat machine.
Loc93-9	The machine vibrated at the torpedo's terrible hit. Activating the power shield seemed to be a bad idea.
Loc94-1	Such a manoeuvre won't help you to escape the blaster.
Loc94-2	While giving your joystick a wrench and trying to veer, you felt how quickly your robot's jacketing became hot. It looked like the blaster got you.
Loc94-3	The blaster shot outran your ill-timed manoeuvre.
Loc94-4	That was a perfect manoeuvre. All the enemy's rockets missed.
Loc94-5	You ducked all the rockets manoeuvring elegantly and got a great tornado of applause on the stands.
Loc94-6	Rockets are dreadful, of course but it won't be a big problem to duck them for an experienced ranger.
Loc94-7	Your manoeuvre didn't misguide the torpedo's homing system.
Loc94-8	Alas, the configuration of the torpedo's homing system won't let you escape it just manoeuvring.
Loc94-9	Your machine that had just finished manoeuvring was nearly knocked over by the torpedo's high-powered hit.
Loc95-1	The generator didn't protect you from the blaster.
Loc95-2	Damn it, the enemy managed to outplay you. After you activated the noise generator, he remained cool and hit you with a blaster.
Loc95-3	Trying to misguide the enemy blaster beam with the help of the noise generator is rather insane!
Loc95-4	The generator is no protection against rockets.  The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc95-5	Don't trust the noise generator if enemy rockets are flying in your direction. The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc95-6	You saw the approaching rockets but it was too late to duck them. The self-diagnostic system immediately defined the number of rockets that hit your machine. There turned out to be [p17] of them.
Loc95-7	The torpedo exploded nearby, so only several fragments reached the machine.
Loc95-8	The noise generator did its work perfectly and the torpedo turned up the soil of the playground aside of you. However, the explosion still shook you up a little.
Loc95-9	Though the torpedo passed by due to the generator, the charge was powerful enough to damage your machine a little.
Loc96-1	Unfortunately, you blew off all your charges and have nothing else to fight with. They announced your loss due to ammunition inferiority. 
*	
*	Your mission failed.
Loc98-1	- Damn <clr>pitiable Faeyan<clrEnd>! It's completely impossible <clr> to get him with rockets <clrEnd>. He is constantly manoeuvring in the most unimaginable way. He even manages to duck torpedoes! Even I, THE GALAXY CHAMPION AMONG MALOQS could do nothing to him! By the way, he <clr>fires rockets<clrEnd> with pretty damn good grouping. No less then two rockets per shot, bastard! Ooh, if only I met this Faeyan worm somewhere face to face! I would just tear his full-eyed chump off!
*	
*	Maloq's wild excitement made him jump to his feet and go berserk in complete fury. While the guards were trying to calm the rowdy down, you nipped away from the bar to escape your portion of kicking and went to bed. In the morning you freshened up quickly and went to the armoury.
Loc98-2	- This Cha-Cha beat me with a blaster! Can you imagine that?! To beat THE GALAXY CHAMPION AMONG MALOQS with a crappy blaster! <clr>This nasty Faeyan has an unusually powerful blaster <clrEnd>! He almost destroyed my robot with just two hits and smashed it with torpedo fragments. I didn't have time to do anything... I'm sure he bribed all the referees. Such blasters should be forbidden! Some crappy Zen...beat me, the Galaxy champion... with a crappy blaster... - the Galaxy champion among Maloqs became maudlin-drunk and the rest of his speech was completely thick.
*	
*	You could tap nothing else out of him, so you went to your room and had a good night's rest. You went to the armoury first thing in the morning.
Loc98-3	- He is tough, this <clr>Zen Cha-Cha<clrEnd>. I won't be surprised if he wins the tournament. He has some <clr>unique torpedoes <clrEnd>. Even the noise doesn't help to escape them sometimes! However, I let him have it also... I'm THE GALAXY CHAMPION AMONG MALOQS, whatever one might say. I bet, his robot's <clr>power field is hardly operational <clrEnd> after our fight. So <clr>it is almost exposed to the blaster <clrEnd>. May his next enemy use the blaster more often! Let's drink to it!
*	
*	You had one more drink but it turned out to be too much for your competitor. Hardly had he emptied his glass when his head dropped down onto the table, his face right into the ashtray. However, this case didn't revive him. You realised that the drunkard was no good any more and staggered to your room to have a rest. When you woke up in the morning, you went to the armoury first thing.
Loc99-1	- He is tough, this <clr>Steel Silvester <clrEnd>. I won't be surprised if he wins the tournament. He has some <clr>unique torpedoes <clrEnd>. Even the noise doesn't help to escape them sometimes! However, I let him have it also... I'm THE GALAXY CHAMPION AMONG MALOQS, whatever one might say. I bet, his robot's power field is hardly operational after our fight. So <clr>it is almost exposed to the blaster <clrEnd>. May his next enemy use the blaster more often! Let's drink to it!
*	
*	You had one more drink but it turned out to be too much for your competitor. Hardly had he emptied his glass when his head dropped down onto the table, his face right into the ashtray. However, this case didn't revive him. You realised that the drunkard was no good any more and staggered to your room to have a rest. When you woke up in the morning, you went to the armoury first thing.
Loc99-2	- He beat me with a blaster! Can you imagine that?! To beat THE GALAXY CHAMPION AMONG MALOQS with a crappy blaster! <clr>This Silvester has an unusually powerful blaster <clrEnd>! He almost destroyed my robot with just two hits and smashed it with torpedo fragments. I didn't have time to do anything... I'm sure he bribed all the referees. Such blasters should be forbidden! Some crappy Gaalian...beat me, the Galaxy champion... with a crappy blaster... - the Galaxy champion among Maloqs became maudlin-drunk and the rest of his speech was completely thick.
*	
*	You could tap nothing else out of him, so you went to your room and had a good night's rest. You went to the armoury first thing in the morning.
Loc99-3	- Damn <clr>Silvester<clrEnd>! He is incredibly skilful at robot managing and is constantly manoeuvring in the most unimaginable way. He even <clr>manages to duck torpedoes<clrEnd>! Even I, THE GALAXY CHAMPION AMONG MALOQS, could do nothing to him! By the way, he <clr>fires rockets<clrEnd> with pretty damn good grouping. No less then two rockets per shot, bastard! Ooh, if only I met this Human worm somewhere face to face! I would just wrench his arms and legs out!
*	
*	Maloq's wild excitement made him jump to his feet and get berserk in complete fury. While the guards were trying to calm the rowdy down, you nipped away from the bar to escape your portion of kicking and went to bed. In the morning you freshened up quickly and went to the armoury.
Loc100-1	The Peleng grinned and continued:
*	-  Alright, let's go along! <clr>John "God" O'Damned<clrEnd> is not the strongest opponent at this tournament. He <clr>fears torpedoes <clrEnd> more then anything else and activates the noise generator more often than he uses any other protection. <clr>O'Damned's favourite weapon is the blaster.<clrEnd>. He has a pretty upgraded model that causes much more damage when hits. Though, it can't get through the power field anyway.
*	
*	When shaking hands with you, the Peleng wished you good luck and said that from now on he would stake on you only. Next morning you went to the armoury up in arms.
Loc100-2	The Peleng grinned and continued:
*	- <clr>John "God" O'Damned<clrEnd> is a nimble lad. And very hard-working. He became so sharp at <clr>manoeuvring <clrEnd> due to earnest training that he even manages to duck torpedoes sometimes. Moreover, he is not only a real expert in escaping rockets but also is pretty good at <clr>shooting with rocket pistol<clrEnd>. And its navigator is upgraded to improve the grouping.
*	
*	When shaking hands with you, the Peleng wished you good luck and said that from now on he would stake on you only. Next morning you went to the armoury up in arms.
Loc100-3	The Peleng grinned and continued:
*	- <clr>John "God" O'Damned<clrEnd> is one of the most dangerous opponents and the main contender to the title. But he also has his weak points. His<clr>protection field generator is almost dead <clrEnd> after the previous fight. I think he will fear to activate it. <clr>O'Damned chose torpedoes <clrEnd> to be his main weapon during the fight. He included a number of the most up-to-date rockets into his inventory before the tournament. Sometimes they manage to overdo the noise generator.
*	
*	When shaking hands with you, the Peleng wished you good luck and said that from now on he would stake on you only. Next morning you went to the armoury up in arms.
Loc101-1	The Peleng grinned and continued:
*	-  Alright, let's go along! <clr>Zen Cha-Cha<clrEnd> is a nimble lad. And very hard-working. He became so sharp at <clr>manoeuvring <clrEnd> due to earnest training that he even manages to duck torpedoes sometimes. Moreover, he is not only a real expert in escaping rockets but also is pretty good at <clr>shooting with rocket pistol<clrEnd>. And its navigator is upgraded to improve the grouping
*	
*	When shaking hands with you, the Peleng wished you good luck and said that from now on he would stake on you only. Next morning you went to the armoury up in arms.
Loc101-2	The Peleng grinned and continued:
*	- <clr>Zen Cha-Cha<clrEnd> is not the strongest opponent at this tournament. He fears torpedoes more then anything else and <clr>activates the noise generator<clrEnd> more often then uses other protection. <clr>Cha-Cha's favourite weapon is the blaster.<clrEnd>. He has a pretty upgraded model that causes much more damage when hits. Though, it can't get through the power field anyway
*	
*	When shaking hands with you, the Peleng wished you good luck and said that from now on he would stake on you only. Next morning you went to the armoury up in arms.
Loc101-3	The Peleng grinned and continued:
*	- <clr>Zen Cha-Cha<clrEnd> is one of the most dangerous opponents and the main contender to the title. But he also has his weak points. His protection field <clr>generator is almost dead <clrEnd> after the previous fight. I think he will fear to activate it. <clr>Cha-Cha chose torpedoes <clrEnd> to be his main weapon during the fight. He included a number of the most up-to-date rockets into his inventory before the tournament. Sometimes they manage to overdo the noise generator.
*	
*	When shaking hands with you, the Peleng wished you good luck and said that from now on he would stake on you only. Next morning you went to the armoury up in arms.
Loc102-1	The Peleng grinned and continued:
*	- Alright, let's go along! <clr>Steel Silvester <clrEnd> is one of the most dangerous opponents and the main contender to the title. But he also has his weak points. His protection field <clr>generator is almost dead <clrEnd> after the previous fight. I think he will fear to activate it. <clr>Silvester chose torpedoes <clrEnd> to be his main weapon during the fight. He included a number of the most up-to-date rockets into his inventory before the tournament. Sometimes they manage to overdo the noise generator.
*	
*	When shaking hands with you, the Peleng wished you good luck and said that from now on he would stake on you only. Next morning you went to the armoury up in arms.
Loc102-2	The Peleng grinned and continued:
*	- <clr>Steel Silvester<clrEnd> is not the strongest opponent at this tournament. He fears torpedoes more then anything else and <clr>activates the noise generator<clrEnd> more often then uses other protection. <clr>Silvester's favourite weapon is the blaster.<clrEnd>. He has a pretty upgraded model that causes much more damage when hits. Though, it can't get through the power field anyway.
*	
*	When shaking hands with you, the Peleng wished you good luck and said that from now on he would stake on you only. Next morning you went to the armoury up in arms.
Loc102-3	The Peleng grinned and continued:
*	- <clr>Steel Silvester<clrEnd> is a nimble lad. And very hard-working. He became so sharp at <clr>manoeuvring <clrEnd> due to earnest training that he even manages to duck torpedoes sometimes. Moreover, he is not only a real expert in escaping rockets but also is pretty good at <clr>shooting with rocket pistol<clrEnd>. And its navigator is upgraded to improve the grouping
*	
*	When shaking hands with you, the Peleng wished you good luck and said that from now on he would stake on you only. Next morning you went to the armoury up in arms.
Loc103-1	- He beat me with a blaster! Can you imagine that?! To beat THE GALAXY CHAMPION AMONG MALOQS with a crappy blaster! This <clr> Gaalian has an unusually powerful blaster <clrEnd>! He almost destroyed my robot with just two hits and smashed it with torpedo fragments. I didn't have time to do anything... He bribed all the judges obviously. Such blasters should be forbidden! Some crappy Gaalian...beat me, the Galaxy champion... with a crappy blaster... - the Galaxy champion among Maloqs became maudlin-drunk and the rest of his speech was completely thick.
*	
*	You could tap nothing else out of him, so you went to your room and had a good night's rest. You went to the armoury first thing in the morning.
Loc103-2	- Damn <clr>Gaalian<clrEnd>! It's completely <clr> impossible to get him with rockets <clrEnd>. He is constantly manoeuvring in the most unimaginable way. He even manages to duck torpedoes! Even I, THE GALAXY CHAMPION AMONG MALOQS, could do nothing to him! By the way, he is <clr>pretty good at firing rockets<clrEnd>. No less then two rockets per shot, bastard! Ooh, if only I met this Gaalian freak somewhere face to face! I would just tear his dull champ off!
*	
*	Maloq's wild excitement made him jump to his feet and get berserk in complete fury. While the guards were trying to calm the rowdy down, you nipped away from the bar to escape your portion of kicking and went to bed. In the morning you freshened up quickly and went to the armoury.
Loc103-3	- He is tough, this <clr> John "God" O'Damned <clrEnd>. I won't be surprised if he wins the tournament. He has some <clr>unique torpedoes <clrEnd>. Even the noise doesn't help to escape them sometimes! However, I let him have it also... I'm THE GALAXY CHAMPION AMONG MALOQS, whatever one might say. I bet, I <clr>thrashed his power field pretty well<clrEnd>. So it is almost exposed to the blaster. May his next enemy use the blaster more often! Let's drink to it!
*	
*	You had one more drink but it turned out to be too much for your competitor. Hardly had he emptied his glass when his head dropped down onto the table, his face right into the ashtray. However, this case didn't revive him. You realised that the drunkard was no good any more and staggered to your room to have a rest. When you woke up in the morning, you went to the armoury first thing.
Path2	Acquaint yourself with the rules
Path3	Go to bed
Path3b	You had a good night's rest and are ready for any trials.
Path4	I know the rules already
Path5	I'd rather keep my skin. The money offered is not worthwhile taking such hazards.
Path6	Take the blaster charge
Path7	Take the rocket set
Path8	Take the torpedo
Path9	Take the blaster charge
Path10	Take the blaster charge
Path12	Take the rocket set
Path13	Take the rocket set
Path15	Take the torpedo
Path16	Take the torpedo
Path18	I want to change my ammunition lot
Path19	Here we go...
Path19b	It's time for your strike. Choose the weapon.
Path20b	Choose what enemy's weapon you will defend yourself from.
Path32	Shoot a torpedo
Path37-par1-crit	Your mom told you to avoid activating the power shield when the rockets are approaching, didn't she? So, she was absolutely right! The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path38-par1-crit	A dreadful torpedo shook your machine. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path39-par1-crit	The blaster shot outran your ill-timed manoeuvre. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path41-par1-crit	Your machine that had just finished manoeuvring was knocked over by the torpedo's high-powered hit. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path42-par1-crit	The enemy managed to outplay you. After you activated the noise generator, he remained cool and hit you with a blaster. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path45-par1-crit	You saw the approaching rockets but it was too late to duck them. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path47	The enemy is biting the dust at last! After the honour round in front of the elated stand, go to the boxes.
Path48b	After you carried the remainders of your BattleMech to the boxes, you left the stadium.
Path49	Money is never redundant. I'm ready for the fight
Path49b	After a short break during which the playground was put in order and the spectators staked again, you took your place of a pilot in the new combat machine and prepared for the new fight. The box doors closed slowly and you advanced to face your fate.
*	
*	It was your draw to be the first to attack. Choose the weapon for the attack.
Path50	Take the blaster charge
Path51	Take the rocket set
Path52	Take the torpedo
Path53	Activate the power shield
Path54	Manoeuvre to escape rockets
Path55	Activate the noise generator
Path56	Blaster fire
Path57	Rocket volley
Path59	With John "God" O'Damned
Path60	With Zen Cha-Cha
Path61	With Steel Silvester
Path62	Here we go...
Path62b	It's time for your strike. Choose the weapon.
Path63b	Choose what enemy's weapon you will defend yourself from.
Path64	The enemy is biting the dust at last! After the honour round in front of the elated stand, go to the boxes.
Path66	Blaster fire
Path67	Rocket volley
Path68	Shoot a torpedo
Path78	Activate the power shield
Path79	Manoeuvre to escape rockets
Path80	Activate the noise generator
Path82-par1-crit	Your mom told you to avoid activating the power shield when the rockets are approaching, didn't she? So, she was absolutely right! The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path84-par1-crit	A dreadful torpedo shook your machine. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path85-par1-crit	The blaster shot outran your ill-timed manoeuvre. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path86-par1-crit	Your machine that had just finished manoeuvring was knocked over by the torpedo's high-powered hit. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path88-par1-crit	The enemy managed to outplay you. After you activated the noise generator, he remained cool and hit you with a blaster. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path89-par1-crit	You saw the approaching rockets but it was too late to duck them. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path91	Here we go...
Path91b	Choose what enemy's weapon you will defend yourself from.
Path92b	It's time for your strike. Choose the weapon.
Path94	The enemy is biting the dust at last! After the honour round in front of the elated stand, go to the boxes.
Path95	Blaster fire
Path96	Rocket volley
Path97	Shoot a torpedo
Path98	Activate the power shield
Path99	Manoeuvre to escape rockets
Path100	Activate the noise generator
Path110-par1-crit	The enemy managed to outplay you. After you activated the noise generator, he remained cool and hit you with a blaster. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path111-par1-crit	You saw the approaching rockets but it was too late to duck them. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path114-par1-crit	Your machine that had just finished manoeuvring was knocked over by the torpedo's high-powered hit. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path115-par1-crit	The blaster shot outran your ill-timed manoeuvre. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path118-par1-crit	Your mom told you to avoid activating the power shield when the rockets are approaching, didn't she? So, she was absolutely right! The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path119-par1-crit	A dreadful torpedo shook your machine. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path120	Thank you. Now I know what I'm going to face
Path121	Go to the bar
Path122	Talk to the Maloq
Path123	Try to get closer with the fan group
Path124	Approach the Peleng
Path125	Let's drink to the victory of John "God" O'Damned, the greatest fighter at all times and among all nations!
Path126	I'd like to drink to our common idol Zen Cha-Cha!
Path127	I'm going to empty this glass to the victory of the strongest fighter. Of course, I mean the invincible Steel Silvester!
Path128	As a ranger, I don't err on the site of modesty, so I propose to drink to the future champ, that is, to me, the great ranger <Ranger>!
Path133	Oh, no. If you want to earn some money, tell me what you know and then you can stake on me easily.
Path133b	- Well...I propose, you refuse. Though it's a pity, of course, it could have been a stunning bargain, - the Peleng answered and turned away showing that the conversation was over.
*	
*	This crook's abhorrent snoot depressed your appetite completely and you went to bed. You went to the armoury first thing in the morning.
Path134	So speak. I'll give you <clr>50 cr<clrEnd>. You don't deserve more so far
Path136	Take your <clr>50 cr<clrEnd>, ramper
Path137	Look at this arrogant fool! You can earn a pot of dibs putting a stake on me!
Path139	Try to get the Maloq away from the bar
Path139b	You tried to talk him into going to his room and sleep himself sober but suddenly the Maloq took his hair down and plugged you in the eye with all the fury. Now it was you who needed medical help. 
*	
*	You went to your room, put a cold compress on your mouse and went to bed. You went to the armoury first thing in the morning.
Path140	Buy the Maloq a drink (<clr>50 cr<clrEnd>)
Path141	Alright, let's have another round, and you'll tell me what made you come down to such a condition... (order drinks for <clr>50 cr<clrEnd>)
Path143	Tell me how he beat you, and, upon my faith, I'll take the change out of him!
Path144b	Suddenly the Maloq kicked at me:
*	- Suddenly the Maloq boiled over me. Who the hell are you? You are not a shoulder to cry on!? Beat it or I'll stand up. And if I stand up, you'll lie down! 
*	
*	You decided that mixing up with that bully would cost too much, especially before the important competitions. So you whistled off from the bar and went to bed. You went to the armoury first thing in the morning.
Path145	Go to the boxes
Path146	Install the laser intensifier.
Path147	Install the upgraded rocket navigator
Path148	Install the heading on the torpedo tube
Path149	No, thank you, I don't need anything
Path153	Blaster fire
Path154	Rocket volley
Path155	Shoot a torpedo
Path165	Activate the power shield
Path166-par1-crit	A dreadful torpedo shook your machine. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path168-par1-crit	Your mom told you to avoid activating the power shield when the rockets are approaching, didn't she? So, she was absolutely right! The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path169	Manoeuvre to escape rockets
Path170	Activate the noise generator
Path173-par1-crit	Your machine that had just finished manoeuvring was knocked over by the torpedo's high-powered hit. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path174-par1-crit	You saw the approaching rockets but it was too late to duck them. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path175-par1-crit	The enemy managed to outplay you. After you activated the noise generator, he remained cool and hit you with a blaster. The explosion flash was the last thing you saw.
Path177b	After a short break during which the playground was put in order and the spectators staked again, you took your place of a pilot in the new combat machine and prepared for the new fight. The box doors closed slowly and you advanced to face your fate.
*	
*	Your enemy's draw was to be the first to attack. You need to do something for protection.
Path178b	Hardly had you left the playground followed by the wild roar of the elated stands when some too cheeky Peleng appeared as if from nowhere and stood on your way. He grinned arrogantly and said:
*	- I'm happy to congratulate the great ranger <Ranger> on his outstanding victory in the Intergalactic Tournament. However, I'm not going to waste my breath. Let's stick to business. Do you happen to know that beside the official combat robot competitions there are also backstreet fights? I must say, they stake much more during such fights. The winners earn good money. Actually, this is my offer. Would you like to have a try and take part in these fights? We guarantee, you'll be amply rewarded for your heroism! Let's go to the bar and I'll give you all the details.
Path179	No, thank you, I've already got my share of fighting. And I've had my fill of it too!
Path180	I give up!
Path181	I give up!
Path184	Money is never redundant. I'm ready for the fight
Path184b	The Peleng let no grass grow under his feet and took you to the boxes where you received a new combat robot. After you checked it, you were ready. The box gates opened at the referee's command letting you to the playground.
*	
*	It was your draw to be the first to attack. Choose the weapon for the attack.
Path185b	The Peleng let no grass grow under his feet and took you to the boxes where you received a new combat robot. After you checked it, you were ready. The box gates opened at the referee's command letting you to the playground
*	
*	Your enemy's draw was to be the first to attack. You need to do something for protection.
Path186	No, thank you, I've already got my share of fighting. And I've had my fill of it too!
Path187	Go out of the bar
Path188b	You need to do something for protection now.
Path196b	You tried to get the Maloq away from the bar, but that beef was immovable. Vice versa, the Maloq grasped your shirt and forced you to sit down to his table. He refused to listen to your expostulations, silently took a bottle of some muddy belly-wash from under the table, filled up your glass and forced it into your hand. You drank it empty without turning an eyelash. You had been around a lot and tried much more disgusting staff. The Maloq was watching you attentively and when there was not a drop left, gave a hum of satisfaction.
Path197b	The Peleng gave it a thought estimating different chances and possible gains.
*	- You are a hustler, aren't you?... A fly customer! - he stated after a long pause.
Path199b	You need to do something for protection now.
Path200b	You need to do something for protection now.
Path201b	Choose the weapon for the attack
Path202b	Choose the weapon for the attack
Path203b	Choose the weapon for the attack
Path204b	You need to do something for protection now.
Path205b	You need to do something for protection now.
Path206b	You need to do something for protection now.
Path207b	You need to do something for protection now.
Path208b	You need to do something for protection now.
Path209b	You need to do something for protection now.
Path210b	You need to do something for protection now.
Path211b	You need to do something for protection now.
Path212b	You need to do something for protection now.
Path213	Come to the fans
Path214	Insert <clr>50 cr<clrEnd> in the slot and listen to the conversation
Path215	Try to get closer with the fan group
Path216	Try to get closer with the fan group
Path217	Go on gambling and insert <clr>50 more cr<clrEnd>
Path218b	Choose the weapon for the attack
Path219b	Choose the weapon for the attack
Path220b	Choose the weapon for the attack
Path221b	Choose the weapon for the attack
Path222b	Choose the weapon for the attack
Path223b	Choose the weapon for the attack
Path224b	Choose the weapon for the attack
Path225b	Choose the weapon for the attack
Path226b	Choose the weapon for the attack
Path227	The enemy is biting the dust at last! After the honour round in front of the elated stand, go to the boxes.
Path228	The enemy is biting the dust at last! After the honour round in front of the elated stand, go to the boxes.
Path229	The enemy is biting the dust at last! After the honour round in front of the elated stand, go to the boxes.
Path230	The enemy is biting the dust at last! After the honour round in front of the elated stand, go to the boxes.
Path231	The enemy is biting the dust at last! After the honour round in front of the elated stand, go to the boxes.
Path232	The enemy is biting the dust at last! After the honour round in front of the elated stand, go to the boxes.
Path235	Come on
Path236	Come on
Path237	Come on
Path238	Come on
Path239b	The enemy blew off all his ammunition so they announced your victory due to ammunition superiority. After the honour round in front of the elated stands, you can go to the boxes.
Path240b	The enemy blew off all his ammunition so they announced your victory due to ammunition superiority. After the honour round in front of the elated stands, you can go to the boxes.
Path241b	The enemy blew off all his ammunition so they announced your victory due to ammunition superiority. After the honour round in front of the elated stands, you can go to the boxes.
Path243	Come on
Path261b	- We propose, you refuse. But I'm afraid nobody will moan on your grave, silly boy... - the irritated Peleng stood up and quickly left the bar. You had nothing to do but to go to bed. 
*	
*	You went to the armoury first thing in the morning.
