QuestDescription	As you know, <Ranger>, we faeyans are a peaceful race, so our warships generally use mercenaries from other planets. The recruitment system was worked out long ago. Only humans are recruited, since the gaals use mercenaries themselves, and pelengs and maloqs could turn our weapons against us at any second. We usually invite humans from the planet <ToPlanet> in the <ToStar> system onto our ships. But a misfortune has occurred - due to heavy military losses lately, the prestige of the profession has dropped sharply, and now it's not so easy to recruit conscripts. The chief commissar of the planet <ToPlanet>, however, was coping with this superbly, but recently he was awarded the Order of the Stooped with a Twist on the Back, and he was paralyzed with joy! The draft is in danger of falling through!!! You must arrive on the planet <ToPlanet> in the <ToStar> system no later than <Date> and help fulfill the draft plan. We are ready to pay you a bonus of <Money> cr for this little service.
QuestSuccessGovMessage	We believed in you, <Ranger>, and you didn't let us down. The recruits have already arrived to serve on our ships. By the way, by decision of the Collegium of Commissars you have been given the honorary title of Chief Lance Corporal of the planet <ToPlanet>. You may be proud and rejoice. And, of course, your travel allowance - as agreed, <Money> cr. Thank you so much for helping the galaxy!!!
Par1-1	Mechanics: drafted <> of [p6]
Par2-1	Signalmen: drafted <> of [p7]
Par3-1	Pilots: drafted <> of [p8]
Par4-1	Navigators: drafted <> of [p9]
Par5-1	Gunners: drafted <> of [p10]<br>
Par14-1	{[p14] mod 24} h left - prepare the report!
Par14-2	1 day and {[p14] mod 24} h left
Par14-3	2 days and {[p14] mod 24} h left
Par14-4	3 days and {[p14] mod 24} h left
Par14-5	4 days and {[p14] mod 24} h left
Par14-6	5 days and {[p14] mod 24} h left
Par14-7	6 days and {[p14] mod 24} h left
Par14-8	7 days left
Par14-crit	- Come on, report to me, how many conscripts have you drafted? Eh?! What are you mumbling there? You say you fulfilled the plan? Why didn't you report in time?!! Why? - the old maloq general kept asking, and you only kept silent in reply, realizing that the assignment had failed miserably. Farewell, <Money> cr...
Par23-crit	This pill turned out to be the last straw for your body. Regular intake of the tranquilizer exhausted you. The toxins deposited with every pill you swallowed filled your body, and you died without even noticing it.
Par24-1	Draft notices: <> - order urgently!
Par24-2	Draft notices: <> - should be enough for today
Par24-3	Draft notices: <> - enough for a couple of days
Par24-4	Draft notices: <> - we'll wrap lard in them
Par25-1	Am I dreaming all this?
Par25-2	Your eyes are closing, you are falling asleep
Par25-3	It would be nice to rest
Par25-4	Normal condition
Par25-5	You feel perky
Par25-6	You are full of energy
Par25-crit	What a disgrace - to fall asleep on your feet, fall, and while falling smash through a door with your head, which, torn off its hinges, broke the legs of two conscripts, knocked out the glass in a vacuum window and pinned the foot of General Private himself - the head of all the draft offices of the galaxy!!! 
*	"No, I'm not working in draft offices anymore," you firmly decided.
Par26-1	The human rights activists trust you
Par26-2	The human rights activists suspect you
Par26-3	The human rights activists dislike you
Par26-4	The human rights activists are rallying under your windows!
Par26-5	The human rights activists are ready to tear you apart
Par26-crit	"Something's not right here," you thought, looking at the door of your office, which was crumbling under the axes of activist human rights defenders. And only when these axes reached your skull did you realize that there is nothing more terrible than the wrath of fans of any kind and cut. They don't like bribe-takers and lawbreakers here...
Par27-1	Draft office account: <> cr
Par28-1	Your bank account: <> cr
Loc1-1	At the planet's spaceport you were met very ceremoniously - flowers, an orchestra, a red carpet right up to the ramp. This immediately put you on guard: if they greet you like this, then things with the draft are most likely bad...
Loc2-1	At the draft office your fears were confirmed when your deputy for conscription briefly brought you up to speed. 
*	
*	- The draft plan this time isn't very large. We need to draft {[p6]} mechanics, {[p7]} signalmen, {[p8]} pilots, {[p9]} navigators and {[p10]} gunners. We've already done some work and drafted several people ({[p1]+[p2]+[p3]+[p4]+[p5]}, to be exact) of various specialties. There are <clr>7<clrEnd> days left until the end of the draft. The draft office account holds representation funds of [p17] cr. There are still draft notices - [p24], but it wouldn't hurt to order more - what if they run out tomorrow, and then the whole working day goes down the drain. And also, I have to disappoint you - if you're tired, you won't get to rest. These 7 days we're all on tranquilizers and working around the clock without sleep, food or watching TV series! Just don't get carried away with taking the drugs - use them only in the most extreme cases, or you'll ruin your health.
Loc3-1	It's quiet and calm in the office, and most importantly - cozy. A desk with papers, a laptop, videophones, a wall-sized poster "Have You Signed Up as a Volunteer?", stands "They Disgrace the Honor of the Rangers" and, of course, "Our Pride". That's all the furnishing of your office. The soft armchair embraces your body, you want to relax and take a break from everything...
*	
*	All right, enough looking around - time to get things done!!!
Loc3-2	In your office you flopped into the comfortable armchair and closed your eyes. Eh, a couple of liters of beer right now, and off to the bathhouse! However, there's no time to rest - work awaits. You just need to remember why you came here...
Loc3-3	You sat in your armchair for a while, puffing out your cheeks and fixing an intent gaze on the visitor's chair opposite you. It's nice to feel like a big boss after all! But enough fun, time to get to work.
Loc3-4	You quickly looked through the mail lying on your desk. It turned out to be the usual spam - instructions for holding parades, an advertisement for a new boot polish cream, a reminder from command about the need to be vigilant when conducting draft activities in order to avoid information leaks through dominator spy channels, and also {[5..20]} letters from human rights activists demanding an end to the abuse of conscripts, the removal of bureaucratic red tape and strict adherence to the letter of the law.
*	
*	You irritably threw all the mail into the trash - you have more important things to do!
Loc4-1	In the corridor, as usual, there's a crowd and bustle, the noise is terrible. All you hear is: "...ended up in Markab...", "...and when will the gunners get their own cigarettes - I'm tired of bumming other people's?...", "...wow, our navigators are really getting tossed around..."
*	Doors open and close, letting in and out new crowds. 
*	On the left is the archive, on the right the medical board, straight down the corridor you can hear music and lively voices - that's the agitation brigade. Every now and then anyone who feels like it comes up to you with stupid questions like: "Is it true that all rangers are kept in cargo holds during a hyperjump?", "Where am I?", "What time is it?" etc.
Loc4-2	In the corridor, as usual, bustle reigns. Some new conscript is waving a draft notice and yelling indignantly that he has already served his time. "To the medical board, we'll sort it out there!" the sergeant at the duty desk says out of habit. 
*	
*	"That's right, no dodging the draft!" you thought. "If they brought you a notice, it means you must serve!!!"
Loc4-3	This time the corridor was rather deserted. Only the duty sergeant was dragging another hapless deserter to the medical board. He was trying to break free and shouting that he had a white ticket. 
*	
*	"He shouldn't do that," you thought about the conscript. "The sergeant doesn't understand such fancy words anyway..."
*	
*	In general, everything is fine here so far.
Loc4-4	Only now did you notice how dreary your corridor looks. The gray-green color of the walls is utterly depressing. It would be great to paint various military-themed pictures on the walls! A conscript comes to the draft office, and plasma tanks advance on him from all sides, dominator ships fly and combat robots charge!!! He'd immediately understand where he had ended up...
*	
*	"I must remember to toss this idea to the general!" you thought.
Loc5-1	The medical board smells of medicine, doctors in white, but already heavily blood-spattered coats scurry about. Somewhere behind a door some creature is screaming hysterically on an operating table. Pressed against the wall stand conscripts of different colors - pale as toadstools, white as chalk, green as pelengs, blue as plums. Each one tries to slip through without standing in the huge line - time, time, time... 
*	At your appearance the doctors all froze, as if on command.
*	
*	- Carry on, carry on, - you allowed in a fatherly way.
Loc5-2	The usual hum reigns at the medical board. Snatches of conversation can be heard: "Can you serve on a ship with flat feet?" - "Doctor, I have a hernia, can I get a white ticket?" - "Want to dodge, you scum?! And who's going to fight the dominators, me?!!" 
*	
*	You smiled with satisfaction - the work is in full swing!
Loc5-3	There were long lines to the doctors at the medical board. The doctors went about their business unhurriedly - after all, every conscript must be thoroughly examined before being sent into the meat grinder of the fight against the dominators! You can't send just anyone on such a mission, although unwritten instructions and ancient traditions oblige the doctors to rake absolutely everyone into the service. At your appearance work stopped altogether, as all the doctors stood at attention.
*	
*	- At ease! - you commanded, and the doctors returned to work.
Loc5-4	Everything is as usual at the medical board - conscripts stand in line and swap jokes, medics examine the sick, study their complexes and reflexes, take tests and deliver the diagnosis: "Fit!" 
*	
*	Actually, your presence here isn't really needed...
Loc7-1	The agitation brigade greeted you as usual with songs and dances, and posters like "The Enemy Shall Not Pass", "Our Cause Is Just, We Shall Win" and "Remember, Dominator, the Battle on the Ice!"
*	
*	The head of the agitation brigade - a faeyan by race, a peleng by nature - joyfully greeted you and reported on the situation, gesticulating and waving a balalaika. From his words you only understood "...F major in order of the third octave... ...what fourth position?.. ...lip-sync or backing track... ...watercolors on canvas..."
*	
*	- Everything is perfectly clear, - you interrupted him.
Loc7-2	Everything is as usual in the agitation brigade - someone is strumming rock-n-roll on a balalaika, someone is drawing a wall newspaper. It seems everyone is working. The faeyan, the head of the brigade, is awaiting your orders.
Loc7-3	You quietly crept up to one of the rooms and listened. From inside came a lively argument on the subject of how to properly make a "ruff" - first beer, then vodka, or the other way round, or at the same time. 
*	
*	- What a mess!!! - you yelled, jerking the door open.
*	
*	- We're discussing technical details in case of a raid on the bars! - wriggled out the faeyan, the head of the agitation brigade. - By the way, maybe we'll organize a raid, eh? The guys are getting stale...
Loc7-4	A working atmosphere reigned in the agitation brigade - the musicians were rehearsing a hyper-rock concert, several maloqs were trying to march, a couple of pelengs were composing a commercial, and the head of the brigade, a faeyan, was preparing a lecture on the topic "How We Can Defeat the Dominators".
Loc9-1	With enormous difficulty you managed to get through to the printing house. The head of the printing house, V.V. Od, with a face expressing absolutely nothing, said:
*	
*	- I can't give you many draft notices, I only have {[p17]}, they haven't printed more yet.
Loc10-1	- The subscriber you are calling is doing time and is temporarily unavailable, - you heard in reply.
*	- What do you mean unavailable? - you said indignantly.
*	- Available, available! Always available for you, commissar! - appeared the rector of the planetary university of the planet <ToPlanet>, one of the smartest people in the galaxy, Professor Dimwit. - How is your health, how are things at work?
*	- Everything's OK. 
*	- And what happened that made you turn to my insignificant person?
Loc11-1	- Dear commissar, - began a respectable-looking middle-aged man. - While all progressive humanity rushes to fight the dominators, certain individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where the real aces, potential <clr>pilots<clrEnd>, are hiding!
*	- Very interesting! - you replied. Of course - what a boost for the plan!
*	- And I will gladly hand over these deserters, - the man continued, - but you must promise me that the medical board will find some health problems in my son that are incompatible with military service. I don't want him to die in some senseless assault on a captured system!
*	"A tempting idea," you thought. "A few violations, but even closer to fulfilling the plan! Agree or not?"
Loc11-2	- Dear commissar, - began a short middle-aged woman. - While all progressive humanity rushes to fight the dominators, certain individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where the real aces, potential <clr>pilots<clrEnd>, are hiding!
*	- Very interesting! - you replied. Of course - what a boost for the plan!
*	- And I will gladly hand over these deserters, - she continued, - but you must promise me that my son will serve at a military base, not on a ship. He usually gets seasick on ships...
*	"A tempting idea," you thought. "A few violations, but even closer to fulfilling the plan! Agree or not?"
Loc12-1	- Dear commissar, - began a respectable-looking middle-aged man. - While all progressive humanity rushes to fight the dominators, certain individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where smart and educated people are hiding. These potential <clr>signalmen<clrEnd> do nothing but sit and tap messages to each other all day!
*	- Very interesting! - you replied. Of course - what a boost for the plan!
*	- And I will gladly hand over these deserters, - the man continued, - but you must promise me to take my son into service as a mechanic, not a gunner. I believe he was disqualified unfairly during the test! So what, he poured gasoline into the radiator...
*	"A tempting idea," you thought. "A few violations, but even closer to fulfilling the plan! Agree or not?"
Loc12-2	- Dear commissar, - began a short middle-aged woman. - While all progressive humanity rushes to fight the dominators, certain individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where smart and educated people are hiding. These potential <clr>signalmen<clrEnd> do nothing but sit and tap messages to each other all day!
*	- Very interesting! - you replied. Of course - what a boost for the plan!
*	- And I will gladly hand over these deserters, - she continued, - but you must promise me to send my son to the elite units of the construction battalion. It's better than dying in battles with the dominators, and at the same time my son will learn a good trade.
*	"A tempting idea," you thought. "A few violations, but even closer to fulfilling the plan! Agree or not?"
Loc13-1	- Dear commissar, - began a respectable-looking middle-aged man. - While all progressive humanity rushes to fight the dominators, certain individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where professional hitmen, potential <clr>gunners<clrEnd>, are hiding!
*	- Very interesting! - you replied. Of course - what a boost for the plan!
*	- And I will gladly hand over these deserters, - the man continued, - but you must promise me to make my son a military journalist. Not everyone has to die in battles with the dominators, someone has to toil on the information front too, right?!
*	"A tempting idea," you thought, "a few violations, but even closer to fulfilling the plan! Agree or not?"
Loc13-2	- Dear commissar, - began a short middle-aged woman. - While all progressive humanity rushes to fight the dominators, certain individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where professional hitmen, potential <clr>gunners<clrEnd>, are hiding!
*	- Very interesting! - you replied. Of course - what a boost for the plan!
*	- And I will gladly hand over these deserters, - she continued, - but you must promise me to get my son a job at a military factory so that he gets an exemption from the army.
*	"A tempting idea," you thought. "A few violations, but even closer to fulfilling the plan! Agree or not?"
Loc14-1	- Dear commissar, - began a respectable-looking middle-aged man. - While all progressive humanity rushes to fight the dominators, certain individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where smart and educated people who know their way around maps, potential <clr>navigators<clrEnd>, are hiding!
*	- Very interesting! - you replied. Of course - what a boost for the plan!
*	- And I will gladly hand over these deserters, - the man continued, - but you must promise me not to send my son into space, but to set him up as a secretary at headquarters.
*	"A tempting idea," you thought. "A few violations, but even closer to fulfilling the plan! Agree or not?"
Loc14-2	- Dear commissar, - began a short middle-aged woman. - While all progressive humanity rushes to fight the dominators, certain individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where smart and educated people who know their way around maps, potential <clr>navigators<clrEnd>, are hiding!
*	- Very interesting! - you replied. Of course - what a boost for the plan!
*	- And I will gladly hand over these deserters, - she continued, - but you must promise me to set my son up as an adjutant to some general. That will contribute more to his career growth than dangerous service on a warship.
*	"A tempting idea," you thought. "A few violations, but even closer to fulfilling the plan! Agree or not?"
Loc15-1	- Dear commissar, - began a respectable-looking middle-aged man. - While all progressive humanity rushes to fight the dominators, certain individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where real technical specialists, potential <clr>mechanics<clrEnd>, are hiding!
*	- Very interesting! - you replied. Of course - what a boost for the plan!
*	- And I will gladly hand over these deserters, - the man continued, - but you must promise me to send my son into space without passing the medical board - he has minor health problems.
*	"A tempting idea," you thought. "A few violations, but even closer to fulfilling the plan! Agree or not?"
Loc15-2	- Dear commissar, - began a short middle-aged woman. - While all progressive humanity rushes to fight the dominators, certain individuals are trying to evade their patriotic duty. I know perfectly well where real technical specialists, potential <clr>mechanics<clrEnd>, are hiding!
*	- Very interesting! - you replied. Of course - what a boost for the plan!
*	- And I will gladly hand over these deserters, - she continued, - but you must promise me to send my son to serve in the song and dance ensemble! The thing is, my son is an excellent singer and dancer, only for some reason no one but me believes it...
*	"A tempting idea," you thought. "A few violations, but even closer to fulfilling the plan! Agree or not?"
Loc22-1	- You need to draft no fewer than the planned number of conscripts of each of the five specialties: <clr>mechanics, signalmen, pilots, navigators and gunners<clrEnd>. The plan is: {[p6]} mechanics, {[p7]} signalmen, {[p8]} pilots, {[p9]} navigators and {[p10]} gunners. Draft notices are needed for conscription, there are [p24] in stock now, but you can order more. To attract potential conscripts, use the <clr>agitation brigade<clrEnd>. There are also not entirely legal ways of recruiting conscripts, but they must be used with caution - after all, all your actions will be constantly watched by the Committee of Defenders and Midfielders of the Rights of Humans and Other Mammals! Don't forget that the walls may have ears...
Loc22-2	- A strange question! - the deputy was surprised. - A draft notice is the only document that allows you to turn a free young man into a conscript, summon him to the medical board and subsequently send him to the expanses of open space. Accordingly, one draft notice is needed per conscript. The more conscripts drafted, the fewer notices are left. When the number of notices drops to <clr>50<clrEnd> or less, you need to urgently order them from the printing house (those civilian bureaucrats flatly refuse to send us notices if we have more than 50!). You can do this right from your office by videophone. True, there is one small nuance: notices are not used up during some activities. For example, during a mass expulsion of students, the university issues the notices to them, and when recruiting on a tip (well-wishing parents and informer services) the police bring the deserter conscripts straight from their hideouts in handcuffs directly to the draft office.
Loc22-3	- There are several ways to get additional conscripts, but they are all either not quite legal, or require material expenses. I know the following ways.
*	
*	1) It's no secret to anyone that a semi-legal party, the "Seventh-day Pacifists", operates on the planet <ToPlanet>. They carry out anti-war agitation and set up shelters in which deserters hide. We fight these manifestations of cowardice with all our might: for example, we plant our <clr>informers<clrEnd> in groups of deserters, who (not free of charge, of course) give away these shelters. The method is good, effective, and, generally, legal, it just requires certain material expenses. 
*	
*	2) <clr>Bar raids<clrEnd> work pretty well, though this is not an entirely lawful way of conducting the draft. The point is that our staff in civilian clothes go around bars, find potential conscripts, get them drunk, and while their brains are befuddled by some swill, make them sign all the papers. The method is, of course, very effective, but the Committee of Defenders and Midfielders completely disapproves of it. So if you have problems with them, better forget about bar raids. 
*	
*	3) An even more effective method, as illegal as it is costly, is <clr>recruiting expelled students<clrEnd>. If you can come to an agreement with the rector of the planetary university of the planet <ToPlanet>, and he expels more of his students, then they will all migrate into the ranks of our valiant Armed Forces.
Loc22-4	- The essence of the agitation brigade's work is that on your instructions it regularly holds various mass events, thereby raising the prestige of military service and attracting new conscripts. The system for holding these events was developed by a group of psychologists, and they are designed to attract people with certain psychophysical parameters. There are the following types of agitation events.
*	
*	By holding a <clr>parade<clrEnd>, you can count on an increase in the number of <clr>pilots<clrEnd> and <clr>mechanics<clrEnd> (people of these types often come to look at the hardware).
*	
*	<clr>Advertising<clrEnd> attracts <clr>signalmen<clrEnd> and <clr>navigators<clrEnd>, who sit glued to their visors both before service and during it.
*	
*	By giving <clr>lectures<clrEnd>, you will attract <clr>navigators<clrEnd> and <clr>pilots<clrEnd> (they must be precise, punctual and literate - in short, the intelligentsia).
*	
*	<clr>Hyper-rock concerts<clrEnd> are mostly attended by <clr>mechanics<clrEnd> and <clr>gunners<clrEnd> (these just like to have a good time and yell to their heart's content).
Loc23-1	This time there were no orchestras, no flowers, no red carpet at the spaceport. But your ship was in its place - waiting for you to leave the planet <ToPlanet>. Which you immediately did.
*	
*	Your mission has failed.
Loc25-1	- Hello, super-respected <Ranger>, great commissar of the planet <ToPlanet>! We, mere mortals, always pronounce your name with joy and trepidation!..
*	- Keep it short, if you can, - you cut off these grandiose utterances.
*	- Of course, of course!!! Forgive me! My poor father cannot manage the household at home by himself, and the drafting of his son into the ranks of the great and invincible warriors bringing light and liberation from the dominator yoke to all races will bring great suffering and pain to our whole family. Could you help me stay at home? And next time I pledge to go and conquer space...
*	- And who is your long-suffering father? - you inquired.
*	- My father is Mister Burzhuin - owner of factories, newspapers, steamships, casinos and a pirate cooperative. We will be very grateful to you for your assistance, and a sum of <clr>500 cr<clrEnd> will surely please you for such a small service. So, how about it?
Loc25-2	- Hello, deeply respected <Ranger>, great commissar of the planet <ToPlanet>! My poor father won't be able to manage the household if his son is drafted into the army. Could you help me stay at home? I ask not for selfish gain, but solely by the will of the father who sent me...
*	- And who is your long-suffering father? - you inquired.
*	- My father is Mister Bill Gates the Eighteenth - I hope his name speaks for itself. We will be very grateful to you for your assistance, and a sum of <clr>500 cr<clrEnd> for such a small service will surely please you. So, how about it?
Loc26-1	- Hello, I'm conscript Xerox - I work at the printing house, and every hour of working time is valued there. If you helped me get through the medical board without lines, I would give you some draft notices as friendly help.
Loc26-2	- Hello, I'm conscript Scanner - I work at the printing house, and every hour of working time is valued there. If you helped me get through the medical board without lines, I would give you some draft notices as friendly help.
Loc26-3	- Hello, I'm conscript M.S.Word - I work at the printing house, and every hour of working time is valued there. If you helped me get through the medical board without lines, I would give you some draft notices as friendly help.
Loc27-1	Day {7-([p14] div 24)} of the draft is over. Your deputy put a report on your desk.
*	 
*	In the past day {[p18]+[p19]+[p20]+[p21]+[p22]} people were drafted, here is the general information on the draft:
*	
*	<fix>
*	<format=left,16></format>Plan     Today      Total     Left
*	<format=left,15>Mechanics -</format>   <format=left,3>[p6]</format>      <format=left,3>[p18]</format>          <format=left,3>[p1]</format>        <format=left,3>[p37]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Signalmen -</format>   <format=left,3>[p7]</format>      <format=left,3>[p22]</format>          <format=left,3>[p2]</format>        <format=left,3>[p38]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Pilots -</format>   <format=left,3>[p8]</format>      <format=left,3>[p19]</format>          <format=left,3>[p3]</format>        <format=left,3>[p39]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Navigators -</format>   <format=left,3>[p9]</format>      <format=left,3>[p20]</format>          <format=left,3>[p4]</format>        <format=left,3>[p40]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Gunners -</format>   <format=left,3>[p10]</format>      <format=left,3>[p21]</format>          <format=left,3>[p5]</format>        <format=left,3>[p41]</format>
*	</fix>
*	
*	Today is the <clr>last<clrEnd> day of the draft! Start preparing the report.
Loc27-2	Day {7-([p14] div 24)} of the draft is over. Your deputy put a report on your desk.
*	 
*	In the past day {[p18]+[p19]+[p20]+[p21]+[p22]} people were drafted, here is the general information on the draft:
*	
*	<fix>
*	<format=left,16></format>Plan     Today      Total     Left
*	<format=left,15>Mechanics -</format>   <format=left,3>[p6]</format>      <format=left,3>[p18]</format>          <format=left,3>[p1]</format>        <format=left,3>[p37]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Signalmen -</format>   <format=left,3>[p7]</format>      <format=left,3>[p22]</format>          <format=left,3>[p2]</format>        <format=left,3>[p38]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Pilots -</format>   <format=left,3>[p8]</format>      <format=left,3>[p19]</format>          <format=left,3>[p3]</format>        <format=left,3>[p39]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Navigators -</format>   <format=left,3>[p9]</format>      <format=left,3>[p20]</format>          <format=left,3>[p4]</format>        <format=left,3>[p40]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Gunners -</format>   <format=left,3>[p10]</format>      <format=left,3>[p21]</format>          <format=left,3>[p5]</format>        <format=left,3>[p41]</format>
*	</fix>
*	
*	There are still {[p14] div 24} days until the end of the draft. With new strength into a new day!
Loc27-3	Day {7-([p14] div 24)} of the draft is over. Your deputy put a report on your desk.
*	 
*	In the past day {[p18]+[p19]+[p20]+[p21]+[p22]} people were drafted, here is the general information on the draft:
*	
*	<fix>
*	<format=left,16></format>Plan     Today      Total     Left
*	<format=left,15>Mechanics -</format>   <format=left,3>[p6]</format>      <format=left,3>[p18]</format>          <format=left,3>[p1]</format>        <format=left,3>[p37]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Signalmen -</format>   <format=left,3>[p7]</format>      <format=left,3>[p22]</format>          <format=left,3>[p2]</format>        <format=left,3>[p38]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Pilots -</format>   <format=left,3>[p8]</format>      <format=left,3>[p19]</format>          <format=left,3>[p3]</format>        <format=left,3>[p39]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Navigators -</format>   <format=left,3>[p9]</format>      <format=left,3>[p20]</format>          <format=left,3>[p4]</format>        <format=left,3>[p40]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Gunners -</format>   <format=left,3>[p10]</format>      <format=left,3>[p21]</format>          <format=left,3>[p5]</format>        <format=left,3>[p41]</format>
*	</fix>
*	
*	There are still {[p14] div 24} days until the end of the draft. There's still plenty of time!
Loc29-1	The commander had a huge office with a long table. A gigantic maloq sat majestically in an armchair as huge as himself.
*	- General, the draft... - you began timidly.
*	- There is no need to report the obvious, - he interrupted you. - I know everything perfectly well. <clr>The draft was conducted brilliantly<clrEnd>, there hasn't been anything like it on the planet <ToPlanet> for many years. These were truly 7 days that shook me, and therefore the whole world! Many thanks to you from the government and from me personally. You coped superbly with the task set. Vivat! Your reward of <Money> cr awaits you on the planet <ToPlanet>, and for my part I want to present you with {[p36]} cr - everything that is left in the draft office account!
Loc33-1	- Interesting, interesting. And what is this little business? - pronounced Dimwit.
*	"Maybe offer him a bribe - let him expel more of his students, and we just might fulfill the plan," you thought.
Loc33-2	- Interesting, interesting. And what is this little business? Going to try to slip me a bribe again? - pronounced Dimwit.
*	"Maybe I really should offer him a bribe - let him expel more of his students, and we just might fulfill the plan," you thought.
Loc35-1	- And why not. Our salary, us scientists, is small, and your financial help may come in very handy. So how much will you pay me for this small but gross violation of our laws? Keep in mind that the risk is not small, so the more you pay, the more students I will expel and send to you, - Dimwit switched to a whisper.
Loc36-1	- All right, remember my kindness, - V.V.Od suddenly softened, - just for you, for old times' sake, I'll allot some draft notices from my "emergency reserve". I've got about {[p17]} lying around somewhere. So here you go.
Loc38-1	- And how can we come to an agreement? - an expression of extreme interest in events appeared on V.V.Od's face.
Loc42-1	- And what sum can I count on? - V.V.Od's interest went beyond all conceivable limits.
Loc44-1	- Money transfer via the "West-Uni" system is the most universal and reliable way to receive money!!! - the voice of an advertising robot came from the videophone. - Even if you just want to move money from one pocket to another, it's most reliable to do it via the "West-Uni" system!!! The transfer rates are as follows:
*	
*	- <clr>up to 300<clrEnd> cr - <clr>5%<clrEnd> is deducted;
*	- <clr>300-900<clrEnd> cr - <clr>3%<clrEnd> is deducted;
*	- <clr>over 900<clrEnd> cr - <clr>2%<clrEnd> is deducted.
*	
*	How much to transfer?
Loc46-1	You took out the money, called over the head of the agitation brigade and told him:
*	
*	- Work with the informers.
*	
*	- No problem, - he replied, - are there any additional instructions?
Loc48-1	You called over the head of the agitation brigade and told him:
*	
*	- Work with the informers.
*	
*	- Excuse me, - said the head of the agitation brigade, - this service is paid, it costs <clr>at least 200<clrEnd> cr, and you can't afford it. Try again some other time when you have more money.
Loc49-1	It's day {7-([p14] div 24)} of the draft. Today {[p18]+[p19]+[p20]+[p21]+[p22]} people were drafted, here is the general information:
*	
*	<fix>
*	<format=left,16></format>Plan     Today      Total     Left
*	<format=left,15>Mechanics -</format>   <format=left,3>[p6]</format>      <format=left,3>[p18]</format>          <format=left,3>[p1]</format>        <format=left,3>[p37]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Signalmen -</format>   <format=left,3>[p7]</format>      <format=left,3>[p22]</format>          <format=left,3>[p2]</format>        <format=left,3>[p38]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Pilots -</format>   <format=left,3>[p8]</format>      <format=left,3>[p19]</format>          <format=left,3>[p3]</format>        <format=left,3>[p39]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Navigators -</format>   <format=left,3>[p9]</format>      <format=left,3>[p20]</format>          <format=left,3>[p4]</format>        <format=left,3>[p40]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Gunners -</format>   <format=left,3>[p10]</format>      <format=left,3>[p21]</format>          <format=left,3>[p5]</format>        <format=left,3>[p41]</format>
*	</fix>
*	
*	It's the <clr>second-to-last<clrEnd> day of the draft!
Loc49-2	It's day {7-([p14] div 24)} of the draft. Today {[p18]+[p19]+[p20]+[p21]+[p22]} people were drafted, here is the general information:
*	
*	<fix>
*	<format=left,16></format>Plan     Today      Total     Left
*	<format=left,15>Mechanics -</format>   <format=left,3>[p6]</format>      <format=left,3>[p18]</format>          <format=left,3>[p1]</format>        <format=left,3>[p37]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Signalmen -</format>   <format=left,3>[p7]</format>      <format=left,3>[p22]</format>          <format=left,3>[p2]</format>        <format=left,3>[p38]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Pilots -</format>   <format=left,3>[p8]</format>      <format=left,3>[p19]</format>          <format=left,3>[p3]</format>        <format=left,3>[p39]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Navigators -</format>   <format=left,3>[p9]</format>      <format=left,3>[p20]</format>          <format=left,3>[p4]</format>        <format=left,3>[p40]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Gunners -</format>   <format=left,3>[p10]</format>      <format=left,3>[p21]</format>          <format=left,3>[p5]</format>        <format=left,3>[p41]</format>
*	</fix>
*	
*	There are still {[p14] div 24} days until the end of the draft.
Loc49-3	It's day {7-([p14] div 24)} of the draft. Today {[p18]+[p19]+[p20]+[p21]+[p22]} people were drafted, here is the general information:
*	
*	<fix>
*	<format=left,16></format>Plan     Today      Total     Left
*	<format=left,15>Mechanics -</format>   <format=left,3>[p6]</format>      <format=left,3>[p18]</format>          <format=left,3>[p1]</format>        <format=left,3>[p37]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Signalmen -</format>   <format=left,3>[p7]</format>      <format=left,3>[p22]</format>          <format=left,3>[p2]</format>        <format=left,3>[p38]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Pilots -</format>   <format=left,3>[p8]</format>      <format=left,3>[p19]</format>          <format=left,3>[p3]</format>        <format=left,3>[p39]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Navigators -</format>   <format=left,3>[p9]</format>      <format=left,3>[p20]</format>          <format=left,3>[p4]</format>        <format=left,3>[p40]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Gunners -</format>   <format=left,3>[p10]</format>      <format=left,3>[p21]</format>          <format=left,3>[p5]</format>        <format=left,3>[p41]</format>
*	</fix>
*	
*	There are still {[p14] div 24} days left until the end of the draft.
Loc49-4	It's day {7-([p14] div 24)} of the draft. Today {[p18]+[p19]+[p20]+[p21]+[p22]} people were drafted, here is the general information:
*	
*	<fix>
*	<format=left,16></format>Plan     Today      Total     Left
*	<format=left,15>Mechanics -</format>   <format=left,3>[p6]</format>      <format=left,3>[p18]</format>          <format=left,3>[p1]</format>        <format=left,3>[p37]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Signalmen -</format>   <format=left,3>[p7]</format>      <format=left,3>[p22]</format>          <format=left,3>[p2]</format>        <format=left,3>[p38]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Pilots -</format>   <format=left,3>[p8]</format>      <format=left,3>[p19]</format>          <format=left,3>[p3]</format>        <format=left,3>[p39]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Navigators -</format>   <format=left,3>[p9]</format>      <format=left,3>[p20]</format>          <format=left,3>[p4]</format>        <format=left,3>[p40]</format>
*	<format=left,15>Gunners -</format>   <format=left,3>[p10]</format>      <format=left,3>[p21]</format>          <format=left,3>[p5]</format>        <format=left,3>[p41]</format>
*	</fix>
*	
*	Today is the <clr>last<clrEnd> day of the draft! Time to prepare the report.
Path2	I can't work in such inhuman conditions!!! Home, home, home...
Path3	Go to the draft office
Path4	Ask about the draft in more detail
Path5	Get to work
Path6	To the corridor
Path7	To the agitation brigade
Path8	To the medical board
Path9	To the deputy
Path9b	- They were just looking for you from the medical board. Or from the agitation brigade - I don't remember exactly...
Path11	Talk to the conscript's parents
Path16	Bar raid
Path17	Launch advertising
Path18	Organize a hyper-rock concert
Path19	Hold a parade
Path20	Give a lecture
Path22	Talk to the conscript who came up
Path23	Talk to the conscript who came in
Path24	All right, I'm going to my office, and you keep working!
Path25	Remind me of these draft rules once more
Path26	All right, I'm going to my office, and you keep working!
Path30	No bribes, get in line, you sons of bitches
Path31	Give me the notices - I'll help
Path32	I'll gladly help you
Path33	I'll gladly help you
Path34	I'll gladly help you
Path35	I'll gladly help you
Path36	I'll gladly help you
Path40	To the office
Path42	I don't take bribes - I'm hurt for the State
Path43	For that kind of money I'm ready to fly into space for you myself
Path44	I have no intention of breaking the law. We are able to fulfill the plan ourselves
Path45	I have no intention of breaking the law. We are able to fulfill the plan ourselves
Path46	I have no intention of breaking the law. We are able to fulfill the plan ourselves
Path47	I have no intention of breaking the law. We are able to fulfill the plan ourselves
Path48	I have no intention of breaking the law. We are able to fulfill the plan ourselves
Path50	To the deputy
Path50b	- Come in, come in. Have a seat. Coffee or tea? Or maybe a shot each?
Path51	Take a tranquilizer
Path51b	You took two pills, a blue one and a red one, out of the special medicines safe. "You take the blue pill - you wake up in your bed and believe it was a dream; you take the red pill - you enter reality, and I show you how deep the rabbit hole goes," you remembered the instructions of the senior doctor of the medical board, Doctor Morph, as you swallowed the red pill.
Path56	Order draft notices
Path57	Call the rector of the planetary university of the planet <ToPlanet>
Path58	To the office
Path61b	At the meeting you delivered a fiery speech:
*	
*	- At a time when spaceships are plowing... In short, the plan is in danger of falling through, we'll have to take emergency measures - tonight we're holding bar raids!
*	
*	Holding such a grandiose event, of course, began to give good results. Especially since the bars were full of customers that day. Only the human rights activists were displeased with your actions, and there were rather few draft notices...
Path63b	- And who's the smartest and best-read here? - you asked the faeyan, the head of the agitation brigade.
*	- I am, - he replied.
*	- Then the flag is in your mighty faeyan hands! A series of lectures must be given urgently!
*	
*	No sooner said than done. Lectures on the topic "Everyone to the Fight Against the Dominator Invaders" gave a good result.
Path64b	- Parade participants, dress ranks, attention! Eyes right! - you practiced in front of the mirror. - Commanding troops is my element, and a parade is the best way to show myself.
*	
*	A huge crowd of people gathered for the parade, everyone greeted the brave liberator warriors. Infantry and hardware marched by. The spectators shouted "Hurrah!" and other warlike slogans.
*	
*	Holding the parade would have brought positive results <clr>if there had been draft notices<clrEnd>.
Path65b	- Come on, sing "Shine, Bright Moon..." arranged for bass guitar or this one, from the classics - "Nescafe..." - you stopped the first agitator you came across. - Excellent. To the concert with a solo program.
*	
*	- Stop, - you held back the second one, who was trying to slip out the door behind you. - Come on, dance a lezginka in heavy metal style... Excellent - backup dancer.
*	
*	There's nothing easier than organizing a concert with the agitation brigade. And the results are instant, like in a lottery.
Path66b	- Launch the advertising! - you barked in your commanding voice.
*	
*	And the machine got going - the agitators instantly contacted all the mass media offices, ordered commercials and brochures, and put them on the air. The results were not long in coming, and conscripts poured into the draft office.
Path67	Transfer 100 cr to the fund of the Committee of Defenders and Midfielders
Path67b	The representatives of the Committee of Defenders and Midfielders were very grateful and even shed a tear.
Path70	What does the agitation brigade do?
Path72	What additional ways are there to attract conscripts?
Path73	Why are draft notices needed?
Path74b	- Excuse me, I'm on my lunch break. If it's not too much trouble - talk faster.
Path75b	- It seems to me you visit me quite often. No, no, don't think anything bad!!! I'm always glad to see you!
Path76b	- Good day to you, O great commissar of the planet <ToPlanet>, Ranger <Ranger>. Under your leadership our draft office is flourishing. I'm extremely busy right now, but for you I'll take a break and provide all-round help and support.
Path77b	- How good that you dropped in. Such a pleasant conversationalist doesn't visit these walls every day!!!
Path78b	- Have a seat, my dear! And all of you, out of the office! Commissar <Ranger> himself wants to talk to me!
Path79b	- They were just looking for you from the medical board. Or from the agitation brigade - I don't remember exactly...
Path80b	- Good day to you, commissar <Ranger>. How may I serve you? - your deputy asked.
Path81b	- Are you here on business or just to chat? Always glad! - the deputy was glad to see you, that was obvious.
Path82b	- I heard that the human rights activists have filed a complaint against you for improper work with the Fitness Book of Chords, - your deputy put on a look of surprise. - What insolence on their part!
Path83b	- Well? Ready to hand in the report? I see quite a lot of work has been done! - the deputy smiled at you good-naturedly. - The plan must be almost fulfilled, eh? May I congratulate you?
Path84b	- Don't get so upset over trifles. So the plan didn't work out. It happens. I remember back in '91... - your deputy rambled on, but you were only half listening to him.
Path85b	- Come in quickly, the news is just starting, - your deputy invited you.
Path86	I didn't get it, repeat from the very beginning!
Path87	To the report
Path88	To the report
Path89	To the report
Path90	To the report
Path91	To the report
Path104	All right, give me at least that many
Path105	To the corridor
Path108b	At the meeting you delivered a fiery speech:
*	
*	- At a time when spaceships are plowing... In short, the plan is in danger of falling through, we'll have to take emergency measures - tonight we're holding bar raids!
*	
*	The bars were overflowing, but you only wasted time and came to the attention of the human rights activists - what conscripts can there be <clr>without draft notices<clrEnd>?
Path109	To the corridor
Path112b	- Launch the advertising! - you barked in your commanding voice.
*	
*	And the machine got going - the agitators instantly contacted all the mass media offices, ordered commercials and brochures, and put them on the air. Unfortunately, you achieved no results this way - the <clr>lack of draft notices<clrEnd> took its toll.
Path113b	- Come on, sing "Shine, Bright Moon..." arranged for bass guitar or this one, from the classics - "Nescafe..." - you stopped the first agitator you came across. - Excellent. To the concert with a solo program.
*	
*	- Stop, - you held back the second one, who was trying to slip out the door behind you. - Come on, dance a lezginka in heavy metal style... Excellent - backup dancer.
*	
*	There's nothing easier than organizing a concert with the agitation brigade. Only there was no return from it - <clr>no draft notices<clrEnd>, no result!
Path114b	- Parade participants, dress ranks, attention! Eyes right! - you practiced in front of the mirror. - Commanding troops is my element, and a parade is the best way to show myself.
*	
*	A huge crowd of people gathered for the parade, everyone greeted the brave liberator warriors. Infantry and hardware marched by. The spectators shouted "Hurrah!" and other warlike slogans.
*	
*	Holding the parade brought positive results - conscripts began arriving at the draft office again. Only you turned out to have practically no draft notices to process them...
Path115b	- And who's the smartest and best-read here? - you asked the faeyan, the head of the agitation brigade.
*	- I am, - he replied.
*	- Then the flag is in your mighty faeyan hands! A series of lectures must be given urgently!
*	
*	No sooner said than done. Unfortunately, lectures on the topic "Everyone to the Fight Against the Dominator Invaders" brought absolutely no result due to the <clr>lack of draft notices<clrEnd>.
Path116	I just wanted to pay a courtesy visit. All the best
Path117	I have business
Path118	Politely say goodbye and disconnect
Path119	Offer a bribe
Path121b	- What kind of bribe can there be with pennies in your account?!! Bye. Come back when you get rich! Ha-ha-ha!
Path122b	- How dare you? - cried Professor Dimwit. - I have never taken bribes and do not intend to come to the attention of our just Committee of Defenders and Midfielders!!!
Path123	To my great regret, I have slight money troubles right now. But I sincerely hope for our further mutually beneficial cooperation
Path124	Offer 500 cr
Path124b	- For such big money I'll try to come up with something unusual... - muttered the rector. - Oh, I've got it! It's time to fight for cleanliness and hygiene! Today everyone who comes to the university without a change of shoes will be expelled!
*	
*	The rector's draconian measure gave stunning results - by evening [p11] mechanics, [p12] signalmen, [p13] pilots, [p15] navigators and [p16] gunners had been delivered from the university!
*	
*	- I hope this number of conscripts suits you, - Professor Dimwit told you that same evening, counting the money.
Path125	Offer 250 cr
Path125b	- I think I'll hold a colloquium on medieval gaalian philosophy today! - the rector decided. - I think this will let me send quite a few idlers and slackers to the army!
*	
*	Apparently the rector's colloquium turned out to be quite difficult, since by evening [p11] mechanics, [p12] signalmen, [p13] pilots, [p15] navigators and [p16] gunners had been delivered from the university. 
*	
*	- I hope this number of conscripts suits you, - Professor Dimwit told you that same evening, counting the money.
Path126	Offer 100 cr
Path126b	- I think I'll hold an unscheduled test on the mechanics of protective fields! - the rector decided. - Not the most difficult discipline, of course, but everyone who fails it will join the ranks of the armed forces!
*	
*	The professor kept his word - by evening [p11] mechanics, [p12] signalmen, [p13] pilots, [p15] navigators and [p16] gunners had been delivered from the university. 
*	
*	- I hope this number of conscripts suits you, - Professor Dimwit told you that same evening, counting the money.
Path127	What do you mean none? Come on, look more carefully in the warehouse!
Path127b	- What do you mean "look in the warehouse"? I don't even have a warehouse, - replied V.V.Od. - I told you in plain language: THERE ARE NO MORE DRAFT NOTICES!!! And if you have hearing problems - go to the doctors of your medical board - they'll clean out your little ears!
*	
*	Oh, these civilians - all they can do is swear and make a mess!
Path129	Thanks, you're a true friend
Path130	All right, keep printing for now. I'll drop by later
Path131	Maybe we can come to some arrangement?
Path132	Maybe we can come to some arrangement, and you'll toss me some more notices?
Path133b	- I said there are no more notices!!! - V.V.Od was starting to get furious. - Go mind your own business and don't keep me from minding mine!!!
Path134b	- What's with you? Don't you get it the first time? How many more times do I have to repeat that there are no notices!!! No-o-o!!! - V.V.Od's unwillingness to continue the conversation with you was obvious.
Path135	We already have an arrangement. Bye
Path141b	- All right, you've talked me into it, - V.V.Od smiled broadly, - for <clr>25<clrEnd> cr I'll give you a dozen or two notices. Don't think I take bribes, let's consider that you simply bought these notices from me! 
*	
*	Paying <clr>25<clrEnd> cr for {[p17]} - a good deal!
Path142b	V.V.Od literally flew into a rage at your offer.
*	- Are you trying to bribe me?! I don't give a damn about your money!!! I can give you twice as much myself just never to see your mug here again!!!
Path143	I can offer a small monetary reward for your contribution to the common cause if you help with draft notices
Path145	Actually, I've changed my mind. Bye
Path146	Offer <clr>25<clrEnd> cr
Path147	Offer <clr>100<clrEnd> cr
Path148	Offer <clr>50<clrEnd> cr
Path149b	V.V.Od literally flew into a rage at your offer.
*	- Are you trying to bribe me?! I don't give a damn about your money!!! I can give you twice as much myself just never to see your mug here again!!!
Path150b	- All right, you've talked me into it, - V.V.Od smiled broadly, - for <clr>50<clrEnd> cr I'll give you some notices from my secret stash. I hide this stash even from my wife, but I have no secrets from you. Don't think I take bribes, let's consider that you simply bought these notices from me. 
*	
*	Paying <clr>50<clrEnd> cr for {[p17]} - a good deal!
Path151b	V.V.Od literally flew into a rage at your offer.
*	- Are you trying to bribe me?! I don't give a damn about your money!!! I can give you twice as much myself just never to see your mug here again!!!
Path152b	- All right, you've talked me into it, - V.V.Od smiled broadly, - for <clr>100<clrEnd> cr I'll give you quite a lot of notices. I'll dig through everything and supply you with notices for a couple of days. Don't think I take bribes, let's consider that you simply bought these notices from me. 
*	
*	Paying <clr>100<clrEnd> cr for {[p17]} - a very good deal!
Path154	I think I got the wrong door! (go out into the corridor)
Path162	Transfer money from your account to the draft office account
Path164	Transfer 100 cr
Path164b	Transfer received. The commission charged by "West-Uni" is <clr>5<clrEnd> cr.
Path165	Transfer 250 cr
Path165b	Transfer received. The commission charged by "West-Uni" is <clr>13<clrEnd> cr.
Path166	Transfer 500 cr
Path166b	Transfer received. The commission charged by "West-Uni" is <clr>15<clrEnd> cr.
Path167	Transfer 1000 cr
Path167b	Transfer received. The commission charged by "West-Uni" is <clr>20<clrEnd> cr.
Path168	Transfer 2500 cr
Path168b	Transfer received. The commission charged by "West-Uni" is <clr>50<clrEnd> cr.
Path171	Use the services of informers
Path174	Search for everyone (200 cr)
Path175	Search hard for <clr>mechanics<clrEnd> (250 cr)
Path176	Search hard for <clr>signalmen<clrEnd> (250 cr)
Path177	Search hard for <clr>pilots<clrEnd> (250 cr)
Path178	Search hard for <clr>navigators<clrEnd> (250 cr)
Path179	Actually, call off the search for now
Path180	Search hard for <clr>gunners<clrEnd> (250 cr)
Path181	Cancel the transfer
Path183	Next
Path185b	- And who's the smartest and best-read here? - you asked the faeyan, the head of the agitation brigade.
*	- I am, - he replied.
*	- Then the flag is in your mighty faeyan hands! A series of lectures must be given urgently!
*	
*	No sooner said than done. Lectures on the topic "Everyone to the Fight Against the Dominator Invaders" gave a good result. Only it would have been even better if you hadn't had a terrible shortage of draft notices.
Path186b	- And who's the smartest and best-read here? - you asked the faeyan, the head of the agitation brigade.
*	- I am, - he replied.
*	- Then the flag is in your mighty faeyan hands! A series of lectures must be given urgently!
*	
*	No sooner said than done. Lectures on the topic "Everyone to the Fight Against the Dominator Invaders" gave a good result. Only it would have been even better if you hadn't had a shortage of draft notices.
Path187b	- Come on, sing "Shine, Bright Moon..." arranged for bass guitar or this one, from the classics - "Nescafe..." - you stopped the first agitator you came across. - Excellent. To the concert with a solo program.
*	
*	- Stop, - you held back the second one, who was trying to slip out the door behind you. - Come on, dance a lezginka in heavy metal style... Excellent - backup dancer.
*	
*	There's nothing easier than organizing a concert with the agitation brigade. And the results are instant, like in a lottery. Too bad the draft notices are running out, or the results would be even better...
Path188b	- Come on, sing "Shine, Bright Moon..." arranged for bass guitar or this one, from the classics - "Nescafe..." - you stopped the first agitator you came across. - Excellent. To the concert with a solo program.
*	
*	- Stop, - you held back the second one, who was trying to slip out the door behind you. - Come on, dance a lezginka in heavy metal style... Excellent - backup dancer.
*	
*	There's nothing easier than organizing a concert with the agitation brigade. And the results are instant, like in a lottery. Too bad there are almost no draft notices left, or the results would be even better...
Path189b	- Parade participants, dress ranks, attention! Eyes right! - you practiced in front of the mirror. - Commanding troops is my element, and a parade is the best way to show myself.
*	
*	A huge crowd of people gathered for the parade, everyone greeted the brave liberator warriors. Infantry and hardware marched by. The spectators shouted "Hurrah!" and other warlike slogans.
*	
*	Holding the parade brought positive results - conscripts began arriving at the draft office again.
Path190b	- Parade participants, dress ranks, attention! Eyes right! - you practiced in front of the mirror. - Commanding troops is my element, and a parade is the best way to show myself.
*	
*	A huge crowd of people gathered for the parade, everyone greeted the brave liberator warriors. Infantry and hardware marched by. The spectators shouted "Hurrah!" and other warlike slogans.
*	
*	Holding the parade brought positive results - conscripts began arriving at the draft office again. Only you turned out to have not very many draft notices to process them...
Path191b	At the meeting you delivered a fiery speech:
*	
*	- At a time when spaceships are plowing... In short, the plan is in danger of falling through, we'll have to take emergency measures - tonight we're holding bar raids!
*	
*	Holding such a grandiose event, of course, began to give good results. Especially since the bars were full of customers that day. Only the human rights activists were displeased with your actions...
Path192b	At the meeting you delivered a fiery speech:
*	
*	- At a time when spaceships are plowing... In short, the plan is in danger of falling through, we'll have to take emergency measures - tonight we're holding bar raids!
*	
*	Holding such a grandiose event, of course, began to give good results. Especially since the bars were full of customers that day. Only the human rights activists were displeased with your actions, and there were very few draft notices...
Path193b	- Launch the advertising! - you barked in your commanding voice.
*	
*	And the machine got going - the agitators instantly contacted all the mass media offices, ordered commercials and brochures, and put them on the air. The results were not long in coming, and conscripts poured into the draft office. There weren't even enough draft notices to process everyone willing...
Path194b	- Launch the advertising! - you barked in your commanding voice.
*	
*	And the machine got going - the agitators instantly contacted all the mass media offices, ordered commercials and brochures, and put them on the air. The results were not long in coming, and conscripts poured into the draft office. Only there was a catastrophic shortage of draft notices to process everyone willing...
Path195	Report to me on the progress of the draft!
Path196	To the office
Path197	To the corridor
Path198	To the corridor
